Chapter 344: Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beckstone was about to dodge, but he clenched his teeth and resisted the instinct to dodge.

Standing on the spot, he stretched his right palm outwards, his eyes flashing silver. A twisting silver whirlpool appeared out of nowhere onto his palm.

The whirlpool was as tall as half a man, sparkling with a faint silver light, as though it was forged out of infinite silver.

Boom!

The first Deep Swamp Croc crashed hard into the whirlpool. And then it straight up disappeared inside, vanishing without a trace.

It was closely followed by the second, the third…

Beckstone spun the whirlpool on his hand quickly, trying to block off all the Deep Swamp Crocs coming from all directions. But in the end, he couldn’t possibly block them all.

Finally.

Bang!

A shot of black thread slammed into his back, making his whole body jolt.

From far away, Garen gazed at the silver whirlpool in Beckstone’s hand. His expression wasn’t all that pretty either. The Deep Swamp Crocs that got engulfed in the whirlpool were being torn apart by an intense twisting energy. Although it was slow, they were losing contact with him.

He watched Beckstone, who had swept up five Deep Swamp Crocs, one after the other before the silver whirlpool finally broke down and scattered. Beckstone’s complexion looked slightly greenish as well, as though he just went through a terrible sickness.

The silver Totem Light on his body was being continuously assaulted by the black threads. The Deep Swamp Crocs imitated Angel’s strategy, attacking and biting the opponent non-stop and at high speeds. They meant to tire the opponent out, fully expressing the specialty of group battles.

But as soon as the whirlpool on his right hand vanished, Beckstone actually started releasing a whirlpool on his left hand instead. And his Totem Light didn’t show any signs of faltering despite the assault.

"Hmph!" Garen harrumphed coldly. The Dual Headed Salamander at his feet abruptly struck out a head, its bloody jaws lunging at Beckstone. The head was huge, the sharp teeth alone as tall as half a person, and one bite was enough to bite Beckstone into pieces. A few chews would turn him into scraps.

The shadow of the huge maw enveloped Beckstone completely.

Pheww…

The huge winds swept towards Beckstone fiercely, he was just about to raise the whirlpool and aim it at the huge mouth.

Roarr!!!

In an instant, an enormous roar sprayed from the large jaws, jolting his whole body until he went numb. The whirlpool in his hands scattered away in an instant, and he became disorientated and dizzy, his body weak. His ears couldn’t hear anything at all.

One of the Dual Headed Salamander’s abilities, Dragon’s Roar. It enabled them to easily catch prey despite their slow speeds, rendering all the prey’s senses useless after the tremor, so that the prey couldn’t sense danger approaching.

This terrifying ability allowed the Dual Headed Salamanders to conquer the skies since ancient times, even if they couldn’t fly. There simply weren’t any flying creatures that dared to fly past their skies.

The huge bloody maw aimed straight for Beckstone. The large open mouth was as tall as he was, and he could clearly see the countless sharp teeth inside. There were even scraps of blood and flesh on them.

Beckstone could almost smell the pungent odor.

Finally, two beams of silver light shot out of his eyes, and gathered into a cloud of silver light, blocking in front of the huge jaws.

The huge jaws collided with the silver light cloud, as tall as a man.

Bam!

As though it had crashed into something hard, the Dual Headed Salamander wailed and took two steps back.

The silver light also dimmed slightly, having evidently taken some damage. But the silver light rapidly melted, quickly revealing the contents inside.

A large silver hunting hound-like creature appeared in front of Beckstone’s eyes. The strangest part about it was that it didn’t have a hunting hound’s face. Instead, it was a fluid silver whirlpool, spinning continuously, as though its whole body only contained this silver fluid.

The silver whirlpool kept extending inwards, as though the deepest parts of its body could be seen through the head.

The whirlpool hound was as tall as a man, blocking in front of Beckstone, silver fur all over its body.

"A Whirlpool Beast?!" Beside them, Vanderman instantly recognized this creature. "To think he even created this sort of theoretical totem, who is this Beckstone?!"

"What’s a Whirlpool Beast? Can Cia win?" While he was unaware, Andel and Hathaway had walked up to Vanderman’s side, standing next to Maxilan and Edney.

Hathaway asked worriedly.

"The Whirlpool Beast is a unique high-level totem among the Animal Totems. It was a theoretical model made by Luminarist forgers in order to achieve manmade Spiritualization. It is known as the Animal Totem closest to Spiritualization. A normal Form Three totem is no match for it." Vanderman explained solemnly, "Its ability is to distort energy fields, it can swallow all creatures into its gut, digest them and then turn them into distortive power. Cia may have many Form Two totems, but once they go face to face, the power of the Whirlpool Beast isn’t something these Form Twos can compare to. Now it’s up to that Dual Headed Salamander to fight it."

"In that case, when it comes to actual ability, Cia is still weaker than that Beckstone?" Hathaway asked carefully.

"That’s right." Vanderman nodded.

"Then can anyone else interfere and help?"

Vanderman smiled futilely.

"I tried to connect to my power, but it’s not working. My two old friends are also only Form Two, they can’t step in. That’s Form Three power… and Du Qian…

"Master…" Hearing his words from where she sat in the shadows, Du Qian looked at her own grievous injuries and didn’t say anything for the moment.

　************

Garen’s expression was cold as he looked at the Whirlpool Beast in front of Beckstone.

"A Whirlpool Beast… Very well, it's rare to meet a powerful, legendary totem."

In the dozen or so seconds since then, seven or eight Deep Swamp Crocs had been swallowed by the whirlpool on the Whirlpool Beast’s face. The remaining Deep Swamp Crocs only dared to surround it from the outside, too afraid to approach it any longer.

If a Form One totem was just a normal creature with Totem Light, then a Form Two totem was an even stronger, faster creature with some special abilities. And a Form Three totem was something that utterly used these special abilities as their main power. The larger ones could already replace physical fighting completely and had overwhelming power.

The Whirlpool Beast was one such existence, and the Dual Headed Salamander was only strong in itself. When it came to their height of evolution, the Salamander was still lower than the Whirlpool Beast.

Garen stood on the Dual Headed Salamander’s back, his thoughts whirring quickly.

"This is the last blow, if you can withstand it, then I'll return Berlina to you," he said loudly.

"Do you keep your word?" Beckstone asked coldly.

"Of course." Garen nodded calmly.

"Then come at me." Beckstone straightened up, but he couldn't stop himself from cupping his hand over his mouth. With a gagging sound, blood began leaking out through his fingers.

Garen narrowed his eyes, and the Dual Headed Salamander raised its head to the sky, roaring.

Screee!!

The huge snake-like necks cast two black shadows under the sunlight.

The huge jaws on the right abruptly lunged down. There was a layer of faint red light on the edges of the giant teeth.

Pheww!

With a rustle of wind, the snake head moved at lightning speed, darting in front of Beckstone in an instant. The terrifying jaws stretched open immediately, chomping down instantly like a beast trap.

Beckstone was utterly focused, both hands gathering together to form a silver whirlpool. At the same time, the Whirlpool Beast also shot a silver fluid from its face, which was integrated into the silver whirlpool.

With all his power, he thrust the whirlpool upwards.

Ker-chak!!

A crisp sound abruptly reverberated across the whole area.

There were faint shrieks coming from beside the area, many exclamations of disbelief.

A huge white flying dragon had appeared soundlessly behind Beckstone. The white dragon gracefully lowered its long neck, its huge mouth biting Beckstone’s back from behind. The grey-white air kept emanating from its mouth, going against the silver fluid on Beckstone’s back.

He lowered his head to look at his waist in disbelief. He had evidently sensed the threat behind him beforehand, and had set a tactic there to protect himself, but the defense was nothing against this huge mouth and was instantly destroyed by something.

The silver light in his eyes trembled uncontrollably. Beckstone seemed to suffer an unbelievably intense pain.

The huge Dual Headed Salamander was directly in front of him, biting down onto the silver whirlpool with its huge mouth. Behind him was the equally huge white dragon, biting his waist.

Crack…

The Totem Light at his waist emitted tiny cracking sounds.

"It's over." Garen said mildly. "Unfortunately, you didn't manage to withstand this attack."

The whole field was quiet. No one had expected to see another huge Form Three totem hiding behind Beckstone, and judging by the light around it, it was even a Spiritualized totem creature.

Some people even started wondering if there was a Form Three totem user hiding somewhere. How else could one person control so many powerful totems?

Two giant creatures, each over ten meters long, one in front and one behind, one black and one white, dominated the field, like a horrific scene from a legend.

Garen leaped down lightly from the dragon's back, looking straight at Beckstone in front of him. Right now his face looks like a demon to everyone else, carrying a natural intimidation and terror. Surrounded by the beasts, his whole person had a vast, indescribable aura.

Nobody dared to make a sound, and they even tried to breathe softly, terrified of attracting the beasts’ attraction.

Just then, Beckstone suddenly began to laugh coldly.

"Hahahaha…" He lowered his face, obscuring his expression. Only his whole body was shaking with the laughter.

"I swear in my name, Beckstone Monalito, that everyone in this mansion, everyone present here, must die!!" At the last part, he raised his head abruptly, black veins crawling all over his face, like tiny snakes sprawled over his face.

"Sunflower!!!"

Baroom!!!

A flash of blinding gold light suddenly appeared from his body.

"Secret Spell of the Aurora!!" Beckstone’s fingers madly drew out glyphs in the air before him, each of different sizes and each rapidly vanishing after completion.

The air surrounding his body explosively gathered into a huge silhouette of a towering golden tree.

The golden tree was more than thirty meters tall, and amidst the lush golden leaves, there were tiny golden flowers, emitting a blinding golden light like the Sun.

Beckstone was like the roots of the tree, his body transparent to reveal the insides of the bark. His hands continuously drew out countless golden glyphs and tactics. Each faded golden tactic glyph seemed to be the tree's power source. The speed of his drawing had already clearly exceeded fifty per second. This had basically surpassed Master-level writing speeds, achieving an unprecedented level of speed.

Chapter 345: Battle 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the golden light, countless thin and long golden whips flew out from the center of the many golden flowers. Each whip was covered with sharp thorns, and they got thicker as they came, emitting a shocking heat. Some of the stones nearby melted rapidly, and the wood simply grew charred and began to burn. The grass quickly wilted, turning into ash.

"Sunflower…!!!" Angel hid in the shadows, her face a mask of dazed shock as she looked at the giant golden tree. "A Plant type totem!! It’s actually the three strongest Plant type totems!! It’s over… we’re done for…"

On the border of the estate, the two Masters who had just run out of the lab, Barr and Baphje, had also glimpsed this giant huge tree in the distance.

"This… this is… the Sunflower Tree!!?? Wasn’t it extinguished by the Royal Alliance a long time ago? Why is there still one now!?" Barr’s wrinkled old face was completely stunned.

Next to him, Baphje’s expression wasn’t any better. "As soon as the Sunflower Tree blooms, the area within three kilometers of it becomes restricted entry. It will only naturally open up again when the Sunflower Tree has destroyed all enemy creatures inside. This is one of the strongest abilities among the Form Three Spiritualizations. Which Master is playing the fool around here?"

Vanderman looked up at the golden tree, his gaze calm. Thinking back to everything that had happened in the past, he only had an unprecedented sense of fulfillment and quietude here in the face of death.

Du Qian quietly appeared beside him, her eyes full of gentleness as she leaned slightly on him.

"Master…"

"All these years, it’s been hard on you." Vanderman hugged Du Qian lightly. "You made many mistakes with me."

"I have no regrets." Du Qian said softly.

Vanderman laughed and looked at his son in the middle of the field.

"Cia, Du Qian and I will create an opening for you, you make sure to grasp the timing properly."

By then, the countless golden whips had finished growing and were headed for the two giant beasts.

Garen stood on the ground quietly, the surface of the earth charred pitch black underneath his feet. His expression didn’t change upon hearing Vanderman’s words.

"An opening? Not necessary. One of the strongest Plant Totems? Haha…"

He raised his hand slowly, and waved towards the sky.

Roar!!! Roar!!!

Two loud dragon roars came from the sky.

Everyone raised their heads unconsciously, looking at the air above the estate.

In the sky directly above them, two huge and graceful white dragons rapidly descended, surrounded by a grey-white light all over their bodies.

Their bodies, more than ten meters long, pressed down like two enormous boulders.

"Destroy him, White Dragon!" Garen’s cold voice sounded suddenly.

Before his words finished echoing, four huge beasts attacked simultaneously outside the golden light.

The grey-white Petrifying Spirit Light and the breaths crashed mercilessly into the blindingly bright golden whips of light. The Dual Headed Salamander glowed with the red light of life, biting voraciously towards the giant golden tree.

Brrr!!

They couldn't hear anything anymore. It was as though their ears had gone numb, the enormous sound waves making everyone go deaf.

The white beasts looked as though they were sprawling in the air above the estate, stopped in their tracks by the golden light as they continuously spewed out vast grey-white breaths.

The whole estate had utterly descended into a chaos of light, grey-white and golden light scattering everywhere, everything fell into reckless destruction.

Some people couldn't avoid it in time, turning directly into stone statues thanks to the Petrifying Breath, while others were brushed by the golden whips, and burst into flames until there was nothing left.

Explosions, buzzing and crashing, the tower collapsing, the screams and wails of the crowd, the roars and struggles of the totem beasts. Everything wove together.

The white estate utterly morphed into a sea of grey-white and gold. The huge fires burned, only to be utterly petrified in the next second.

Garen remained on the spot coolly, the Deep Swamp Crocs protecting Vanderman, Hathaway and the others. The Dual Headed Salamander was also guarding them closely, but since it had the red-armored woman Berlina in its mouth, it was attacked the least.

The three Petrifying White Dragons had already utterly destroyed the golden light whips’ defense, directly bringing the line of war to the golden Sunflower Tree. In the air, bunches of golden whips were constantly covered and dimmed by the Petrifying Breaths. It had grievously hurt two White Dragons as well, but there were too many Spiritualized Totems, three in total, and there was even a Dual-Headed Salamander with them. The four Form Three totems attacked him at once, and there was someone in charge of directing them. Even Beckstone couldn't hold them down any longer.

In the trunk of the tree, all the veins on Beckstone's body were bulging, and he was almost at his limit. His eyes, nose and ears were all bleeding, an indication that he had pushed his totem power to the maximum.

"It's over." Garen lowered his eyelids.

"It is indeed over." Beckstone raised his head, smiling eerily.

Just then, a black shadow appeared behind Garen.

It was Darian!

He was covered in blood, two grey-white hawk wings on his back. He raised both hands into blades and pierced for the back of Garen's head!

His palms had serrated white edges, and a faint white spirit light spread from it, as though it had a terrifying sharpness that could penetrate everything.

It was also Spiritualized!

"Assassination Secret Spell!!" Darian roared, and with a whoosh, his palms actually pierced right through Garen's protective Totem Light.

At the same time, a pitch black figure darted out of Garen's shadow, two pitch black scimitars in its hands aiming for Garen's lower body, ruthless and cruel.

Ker-chak!!

The Totem Light shattered.

Garen's expression was stunned.

Vanderman and the others beside the arena were also terrified, reaching out their hands and trying to yell, but they were already far too late.

In the tree trunk, Beckstone's expression was mild, his gaze on Garen like that of a dead person.

Barroom!!!

The enormous white spirit light was mixed with a hint of black stripes, and they exploded. Forming a cloud of white light more than ten meters in radius.

The white light scattered rapidly. Revealing the situation inside.

"How foolish, did you think you could beat me like that?"

Garen stretched out his right hand, chopping Darian’s neck with one hand and lifting him into the air. There was a cynical smile on his face.

There was also a middle-aged man dressed all in black lying on the ground before him. The man spat out blood and saliva, staring at Garen in disbelief.

"Impossible… you've revealed all your trump cards! How can you still have such strength!??"

"Who sent you?" Garen casually tossed away the unconscious and dying Darian, looking at the man in black in front of him.

There was a huge and terrifying power in his right hand. In that split second just now, he had turned around to meet their sneak attack. Powerful secret techniques mixed with that terrifying power disintegrated their attack the moment they made contact. Before the white light faded, each of them even took a palm hit, sending them straight to Death's door.

"My mission is to obtain Vanderman’s creature technique, I don't know anything else!" The man quickly revealed everything at once. He didn’t even have enough time to summon his totem before his Totem Light was utterly destroyed. This Form Three totem user seemed to be slightly strange, he felt weaker than regular Form Three totems users, as though he didn’t reach this level on his own.

This reminded Garen of a special force within the Obscuro Society’s inner circle -- the elite division.

The elite division was filled entirely with the best members, and like the military, it was an independent department. Jess was part of the military, and other than the marshalls as well as President Hellgate, he was the strongest in his level.

The power of the elite division was even weaker than the military, but it couldn’t be underestimated either. There was also a marshall overseeing everything, and apparently there were even two Elemental Generals like Jess. There were also many lieutenants and brigadiers, more than twice those in the military.

"Are you from the elite division?" Garen asked suddenly.

The man was instantly stunned.

"How did you know!?"

Garen smiled, reaching out his right hand suddenly and bending his finger to flick the center of the man’s brow.

Psst!

An arrow of blood shot out. The man collapsed backward, no longer any light in his eyes.

The golden light in the sky was slowly conquered by the grey-white breaths. This petrifying air was like a mist, mixed with the Petrifying White Dragon’s grey-white spirit light, vaguely covering most of the places where the estate was burning.

The fire was quickly extinguished, the burnt coal turning to grey-white stone.

Two Petrifying White Dragons flew circles over the estate, crying out piercingly.

On the ground, a White Dragon whose wing had been broken crouched next to the Dual Headed Salamander, quietly licking its wounds.

The whole estate fell silent.

Vanderman and the others also heaved a complete sigh of relief. The powerful sneak attack still couldn’t hurt Garen, nobody could see what on earth happened in the white light. But Garen evidently had some final trump card that he didn’t reveal, and he still won in the end.

Garen stood alone, surrounded by the beasts, his gaze looking at the gradually fading golden tree.

The countless golden light whips had utterly scattered away. Beckstone was vomiting blood, half kneeling on the ground, the silver light in his eyes blinking uncertainly.

Clap… clap… clap…

Garen walked towards Beckstone slowly.

"You’re still not coming out?" His gaze moved to Stone’s right. A bunch of specially protected totem users from the estate was standing there.

Those people looked stunned, as though completely lost as to why he would look their way. As they felt the huge beasts move their gazes to them at the same time, the totem users began to grow pale.

Garen lightly caressed the Petrifying White Dragon that was lowering its head.

He wasn’t affected by these people’s performance, merely looking in their direction calmly.

After a long time, a man in white walked out slowly from among them.

It was a very old middle-aged man, with an elderly face, at least in his fifties. He had a short white beard, his gaze complicated as he looked at Garen.

"Young man, there’s no need to start any conflicts between us, you have even more potential than Stone. Why don’t you join the noble Revolution? I can tell, you’re not on the Royal Alliance’s side."

He didn’t attempt to hide his words at all, making them rather toxic. Many people here were from the Royal Alliance, and all their gazes changed when they heard that.

Garen laughed coldly. The reason he didn’t kill Beckstone was because of this man. Now two of the Petrifying White Dragons were injured, both rather seriously. One of them had a damaged wing, and the other lost its limbs into a mess of blood and flesh. At battles of this level, Deep Swamp Crocs had no effect at all.

The middle-aged man here was evidently the secret protector of Beckstone and gang this whole time, Garen wasn’t sure if he could hold him back.

But Garen had achieved his motive. This battle had reduced Terraflor’s expectations for Beckstone. He might still be trained as before, but he will definitely not be as strong as he was in history.

This is the era of many heroes, the ones who couldn’t laugh to the end were all just passersby in history. A tiny decrease could bring even more changes.

Chapter 346: Battle 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s gaze kept shifting. Beckstone’s Plant Totem, Sunflower, was utterly damaged by the joint attack of four Form Three totems, and wouldn’t be easy to fix. The rarer the totem, and the higher it evolved to, the more difficult it was to repair, and the more substantial the funds required for repairs. Even if Plant Totems were supposed to be able to fix themselves naturally, it would take more than a couple of days.

That time period would be enough for him to advance to the next level.

"Cia." Suddenly, a voice came from the side. It was actually Viscount Vanderman, who was standing at the side.

This Viscount-lecturer, who was always stern and strict, suddenly looked a lot more relaxed, as though a heavy weight had been taken off his shoulders.

"Let them go." The Viscount’s expression was peaceful. His tone held a mild sigh and remembrance.

"You executioner!!" Beckstone straightened up from the ground, his emotions growing agitated. "For your so-called experiments, you killed several hundred people at least. Even Leanna!" This normally calm young man finally lost some of his steadiness. The veins all over his body kept expanding, as though his skin was covered with many earthworms and termites.

His voice was very loud, most of the survivors in the estate could hear it.

Thanks to Garen’s protection, there weren’t that many casualties in the estate. A few people were caught in the after ripples, but most survived.

"I’ll kill you sooner or later!! As revenge for Leanna!" Beckstone had nearly lost his sanity. His eyes actually returned to a regular person’s black, reddening slightly.

Right now, he had no Totem Light on him at all. All his totem power was used up in the Sunflower he activated last. He looked just like a normal young man.

"I once asked my teacher, when someone comes to a crossroads between their dreams and reality, how should they choose their own path?" Vanderman smiled bitterly. "In life, just make sure you don’t regret it many years from now. That was my teacher’s reply."

"I never regretted this path of mine." Vanderman closed his eyes slightly. "When I saw ordinary people suffering under the power of Totem Light, struggling, fighting back, wailing, but unable to do anything, I swore to myself, I will definitely come up with something that would allow ordinary people to fight totem power as well. This was my promise to my teacher, so, even if you kill me, I remain unrepentant."

"Nice words!" The middle-aged man in white chuckled coldly. "Out of those hundreds in the lab, can you truly say none died for your own bestial desires? Or rather, would you let everyone into the heart of your lab, to see just how many disgusting, dirty and bloody experiments you have hidden there?"

Vanderman couldn’t reply. Beside him, Du Qian hugged him tightly, sticking out a snake-like tongue to lick his face lightly.

"Even the woman who loves you the most was transfigured into this ugly form, neither man nor monster. Why won’t someone like you just die already!" The middle-aged man in white said loudly and coldly.

By then the whole estate had utterly fallen silent. The cold wind blew mournfully, bringing up the swathes of grey-white dust on the ground.

The others had long ago noticed this strange woman next to Vanderman. It was only upon hearing these words that some people noticed Du Qian’s lower body, hidden by her skirt, was actually a snake’s tail made of entangled tree roots.

Andel and Hathaway grew pale, as though they’d just heard the most absurd story. Seeing Du Qian’s irregularities now, both of them couldn’t help but lean away slightly. They were obviously frightened by Du Qian’s strange condition.

"Uncle wouldn’t do that, he’s not that sort of person…" Hathaway said softly, as though she could not accept such a drastic change at all.

The two Royal Alliance Masters’ expressions were ice cold. They were standing at the edge of the rubble and were surely in a far from a pleasant mood.

"Vanderman, you owe us an explanation!" Barr said coldly and loudly. Next to him, Baphje also looked displeased. There were so many totem users here, they just needed to control their totems to dig into the holes underneath the rubble for a look, and then they would know.

Soon enough, a few Sight Sharing totem users finally couldn’t hold back anymore, murmuring in tiny voices. Vanderman, their beloved lord, suddenly became a cold-blooded executioner. Most of these people found it hard to believe.

Yet others kept their gazes tightly on Garen in the middle, right now the person who truly had the right to talk was Garen. The Viscount’s son, who had nothing going for him, was now suddenly the person in charge of this whole area.

The murmurs and whispers pressed down their volume, as Garen’s gaze swept the area.

The beetles and Deep Swamp Crocs digging into the ground had already revealed Viscount Vanderman’s experimental location to him. Garen’s feelings were very complicated, the bloodiness of the underground lab was rare even to him.

"To think Vanderman is actually this sort of person."

"Several hundred people… just for his own experiments, he killed them just like that. There aren’t even several hundred of us here, are there?"

"Who knows when he might suddenly use us for his experiments?"

"Vanderman! To think you’re this sort of man!" Baphje reprimanded angrily, "I’ll report all of your sins completely! In front of His Majesty!!"

"Cough cough…" Vanderman suddenly started coughing intensely.

"Don’t say anymore!!" Du Qian started screaming, a sob in her voice. She supported the Viscount tightly, covering his mouth with her hand, trying to keep the blood from flowing out. "The master…" Before she knew it, her face was already covered with tears.

"The master performed experiments on his own body, just for the armor most of you are wearing, just so everyone can fight totem power, he experimented on his own body, he never had long to live! Why do you all still want to treat him like this!!!" Du Qian cried loudly, sobbing.

"Don’t say any more." The Viscount stopped Du Qian. Looking around him, the whispers from before had slowly quieted down.

It was true, without this new technique, most normal people would die as soon as they came into contact and fought with monsters. They wouldn’t be able to resist or even run. Thinking of that, most of them fell quiet.

Garen walked up, but Vanderman raised his hand to block him.

His eyes sparkled. Only at this close distance, did he truly detect the problems with the Viscount’s body, because it looked very normal, just like any other person. But the truth was that there seemed to be a whirlpool inside, sucking away all his body’s nutrients.

And because there was Totem Light separating it off, Garen’s shallow knowledge of totem research caused him to overlook it until now.

Looking at his son’s tortured expression, Vanderman smiled.

"It’s nothing, life is only several decades long anyway, and I never regretted my decision from back then. My only regret is that I hurt so many little children back then. I only understood how precious life is now that I’ve gotten old."

His gaze fell on Andel and Hathaway beside him.

"Cia, can you agree to two requests of mine?"

Garen nodded with a heavy heart. He had initially thought he could save Vanderman, as compensation for possessing his son’s body, but he didn’t know that Vanderman was already slated for an early death. He could sense it now, Vanderman was currently on his very last legs. Compared to before, his body seemed to be lacking the support of the most important something.

Vanderman’s gaze fell onto Beckstone. "Let them go, all the sins began with me." There was a hint of guilt in his eyes.

"I don’t need your pity!!" Beckstone roared, and couldn’t help but spray out another mouthful of blood.

Garen fell silent. Everyone was waiting for him quietly, waiting to see what sort of decision he would make.

After more than ten seconds, he finally raised his hand lightly.

Whoosh…

The Dual Headed Salamander opened its large mouth, spitting out the unconscious red-armored woman in its mouth and tossing her onto the ground next to Beckstone.

"Berlina!!" Beckstone propped his body up and stood, running over to Berlina. He then forcefully summoned a white Form One steed totem, putting Darian and Berlina on it one by one.

Having protected his companions, Beckstone’s hands lit up with golden flames again. He actually still wanted to fight.

"Stop!" The middle-aged man in white appeared in front of Beckstone as though he teleported there, and chopped Beckstone’s neck with the side of his hand lightly, rendering him unconscious. His palm didn’t seem to be hindered by the Totem Light at all, going straight through it.

"Hurry up and scram. Before I change my mind." Garen’s voice was deep.

The middle-aged man in white felt he was about as strong as Stone, and without the secret treasure Stone had, he could not release such a powerful totem like just now completely. Even the Sunflower Tree, that had the power of a secret treasure, failed, and he still didn’t know what Garen hid in that white light just now.

He mused over it for a bit, and decided to leave first. First, he needed to take the three under his protection back, to recover and recuperate.

"We’ll meet again in the future. My name is Challaha." He spoke slowly, and a sea-blue diamond-shaped crystal appeared beside him.

The crystal spun rapidly, slowly becoming slightly faint and translucent. All the three casualties and the man in white, Challaha, slowly became translucent, fading away.

Splash!

The crystal suddenly turned into an umbrella of shards, exploding apart.

The four of them also disappeared utterly.

"Challaha…" Garen licked his lips. It wasn’t that he didn’t want to make them stay, but he couldn’t see the extent of the man in white’s powers, and besides, now wasn’t the time to declare war on Terraflor. Beckstone was still very immature right now, and there were many people stronger than him in Terraflor. This immense organization wasn’t something regular little powers can fight against. To be able to stand opposite across Obscuro, Terraflor would at least have some peak-level fighters in charge.

And, this was one of Vanderman’s requests.

Garen’s gaze returned to Vanderman.

Vanderman’s expression was comforted, as he nodded at Garen.

"I still have one wish." He paused, his gaze falling on Hathaway. "While I lived, my biggest wish was to see the birth of your children, my grandchildren. For the sake of our Trejon family’s future, I can’t let the roots of the family die in my hands."

Garen suddenly had a bad feeling.

As expected, Vanderman’s next words proved his premonition utterly true.

"I hope, that you and Hathaway can get engaged." His expression was hopeful as he looked at Garen. "This is my last request, don’t reject it."

Chapter 347: Leave 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen looked towards Hathaway, who was lowering her head and red all the way up to her neck. This handsome cousin of his was now completely at a loss, like a young child.

"I understand. From this moment on, Cousin Hathaway is my fiancee." Garen looked calm. It was just leaving a bloodline for this body, this was something he was supposed to do in the original Acacia’s place anyway.

Boom!!!

Suddenly, the whole estate gave a huge tremor, and the ground shook violently.

Garen’s expression changed. He could feel a very powerful group of qi in the distance, and it was moving quickly towards the estate.

At the same time, the Crystal Derivator in his pocket was also growing hotter. This meant there was an Elemental General of his level nearby, and that person was rapidly approaching as well.

"It’s the people from the elite division!" Garen immediately deduced their origins. That unknown beast was probably their doing as well.

"Leave now." Vanderman seemed to have sensed the movement as well, his expression urgent. "Cia, you take everyone and leave here immediately. Du Qian, I’m relying on you."

"Don’t worry, master, I won’t disappoint you again." Du Qian wiped the tears from her face and nodded.

"After you complete your arrangements, you follow Cia from now on. You have Form Three power, so you’ll be of certain help to him." Vanderman told her softly.

Du Qian nodded lightly.

"What about you, uncle!!?" Hathaway took the initiative to ask.

"I still have arrangements to make." Vanderman smiled. He rubbed Hathaway’s head. "I watched you grow up, it’s such a pity I won’t be able to see the birth of your children with Cia…"

"Uncle, you can still live for a long time, don’t say such silly things." Hathaway interrupted him.

"Go… I’ll be over in a moment." Vanderman pushed Hathaway away.

Garen frowned.

"Father, I’ll stay with you."

"There’s no need, I’m activating an indiscriminatory attack that will hit everyone except for Du Qian and myself, you’ll only be a burden if you stay." Vanderman shook his head. "Go, take Hathaway with you."

He lowered his head again and coughed. He coughed out black blood, dripping down from the side of his palm.

Barr and Baphje had already been appointed leaders by all the totem users and were gathered together. It would be difficult for Vanderman to regain everyone’s trust now. The two old friends looked at Vanderman with complicated gazes, with confusion, unfamiliarity, but mostly pain.

"Go!" Baphje didn’t say anything else. He turned around and quickly left with a group of them.

"You take care." Barr sighed and finally spoke to Vanderman before turning around and taking some more people with him.

Boom!!

There was another deep collision sound, and the ground shook again.

The crowd rumbled. Baphje turned his head to look at Vanderman. As an old and close friend, now that his emotions had settled down somewhat, he could more or less understand how Vanderman felt back then. Between morality and friendship, he still leaned towards friendship, and his dislike for Vamderman also quieted down.

A relationship spanning decades, was not something that could be thrown away at the drop of the hat.

"The Trejons family is as good as gone." Barr said softly, sighing, "No matter how strong Vanderman’s son is, it should be the people from Obscuro outside. Their target is Vanderman."

Baphje stayed silent.

Even if Acacia suddenly became so strong, and although they didn’t know how they ended up in conflict with Beckstone and the others, the situation now was that two of Acacia’s Spiritualized beasts were grievously hurt, and the remaining power was nowhere near enough to deal with the incoming enemy.

Right now, they had to hurriedly leave the estate, and it was only after they were a distance away that they remembered to feel scared. That Acacia was decisive and would kill Beckstone and the others without hesitation.

Even if Darian and Berlina weren’t dead, they were seriously hurt. No one knew if Beckstone could recover, but even if he could, it would take a long time at least.

Although their relationship with Vanderman made them sure that Cia wouldn’t attack them, thinking about it now, if that young man acted on impulse…

*********

Watching his old friends leave, Vanderman then turned his eyes to his son, Cia.

"Go, leave here immediately and take these people with you."

There were still some regular survivors in the estate, and most of them were elderly who had followed the Viscount over the years. Right now they seemed lost too because most of them didn’t really care about the Viscount’s experiments. They didn’t know much about the experiments anyway, they just knew that their benefits, lives, and glory were all entwined with the Viscount, the Viscount’s everything was their everything.

These people had lived on the estate for generations and had basically integrated into the Trejons family.

There were slightly more than ten of them, including Maxilan and Edney.

These two had already become the leaders of this group. They looked at the Viscount calmly, awaiting his orders.

As for the rest of them, they were mostly dazed and lost.

"Go, all of you, go… Follow Cia, he is the Trejons family’s future. Where he is, that’s where the family’s base is!" Vanderman said loudly. "Du Qian, you take everyone and leave."

"Yes, master." Du Qian wiped her tears and clapped. Instantly, many root-like vines sprouted out of the ground, rapidly opening a round hole in the ground.

"Everyone get in first, follow this tunnel, and we can go straight to an exit ten kilometers away!" Du Qian said loudly.

Garen stood quietly at the side, his thoughts complicated.

Vanderman looked like he wasn’t going to live much longer, so Garen was considering if he should Empower him, maybe that way he could solve the problem of this serious side effect from the experiments.

"Father, I heard the Obscuro Society has a technique, it’s called Empowering, and it can heal most mysterious diseases…"

"I tried it a long time ago…" Vanderman said mildly. "It doesn’t work."

He looked at his son calmly.

"Go, there’s no time left. After all, I’m just a dying man." Vanderman’s face was unnaturally quiet, not at all like a man about to die.

Garen didn’t know what to say, and Hathaway and the others at the side didn’t know what to say either. All they could do was follow Du Qian’s arrangements and walked into the tree root cave one by one.

"Boss!" Leila hurriedly darted out of the corner of the rubble, rushing up to Garen. "Big Sis told me to tell you guys to leave immediately. She’s already lured that big fella outside, but she can only last five minutes tops!"

"Got it, tell Angel to leave as soon as she completes her mission, we’ll gather outside in a bit!" Garen nodded. "The others?"

"They’ve all gone out, but the situation right now isn’t great." Leila spoke quickly, "There are many monsters outside, they’re fighting with some monsters outside the estate, but it doesn’t look like it’ll last very long. What do we do now?"

Garen mused it over and was about to speak.

"You guys go too, leave from the underground tunnel." Vanderman’s voice interrupted.

Boom!!

It was another deep collision sound. It sounded like footsteps, or stomps, unnaturally closer than it was before.

"Go now!" Vanderman suddenly roared fiercely. The center of his brows lit up, and suddenly their surroundings were enveloped in a faint green light.

Garen was about to speak, when suddenly a riotous group came in through the main gate of the estate.

Most of them at the front were the totem users who insisted Vanderman was a sinful villain. The leader was a man in red robes.

He had been the estate’s patrol captain, Cardiff.

This group had been chased back, each of them pale and some embarrassed.

Cardiff was nearly fifty years old, and when he saw the people leaving through the tunnel, even he couldn’t help but grow flushed. He was pushed to the front by the others.

Garen looked at them coldly.

"Didn’t you guys go with Barr and Baphje? Why are you suddenly back again?"

Cardiff blushed all the way to the tips of his ears.

"We… we hope you can protect us so we can leave safely, sir."

"Why are you so polite to him! Those monsters outside must have been lured here by them too! It’s their responsibility to escort us out!" Someone yelled from behind him.

"If it weren’t for the estate’s experiments, there wouldn’t be such powerful monsters outside!"

"We are research students with the Royal East Totem Academy! According to the rules of the empire, Vanderman, you and your son have the responsibility to escort us out of here safely, and you have to make sure we’re not hurt by outside forces!"

Most of those who came back were cowardly, the braver ones were still with Barr and Baphje, because they weren’t willing to come back and plead. And the totem users who truly cared about their relationship with Vanderman were still here and were currently walking into the tunnel one by one.

There were only slightly over ten people who stayed behind, and only three totem users.

As for those who came back, they could tell at first glance that these were timid and cowardly.

Maxilan and Edney knew these people, they were never around when there was work or fighting to do, but they would definitely appear as long as there were benefits to reap. Some of them would even fight over their fallen totem user friends’ belongings. They had even been harshly reprimanded by the Viscount over that.

Garen looked at these people calmly. A few of them were the two Masters’ students, all of them came from noble families, their noses higher than their heads. They prioritized their own lives over everything else.

"Why do I need to protect you?"

"Why? We put our lives on the line for your Trejons family! We fought the monsters outside for so long! You still dare to ask such things?!" A young man with a thin face stepped out.

"You must atone for your sins!"

This person was merely a Form Two totem user, but he actually dared to forcefully stand in front of Garen, relying on his pride as a noble. Sensing Garen’s unfriendly gaze now, he shirked back a little but quickly straightened up again.

"Some of us have already escaped safely. I made the arrangements, as long as we can safely leave, all your Trejons family sins have nothing to do with us, and we won’t bother with them either. But if we don’t return, all of Kovistan will know that you, Vanderman, used innocent civilians in your experiments!!

"Let them go," Vanderman said mildly.

Chapter 348: Left 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Sir?" Maxilan and Edney were ready to unsheathe their swords to kill. They had long been displeased with this group of unscrupulous waste.

"Let them go," Vanderman Insisted, "After all, they were trapped here because of me. It’s natural to bear some grudges."

Garen got irritated; these aristocrats were really baffling. Even after he showed such a powerful attack, these people still dared to talk nonsense in front of him, thinking he wouldn’t dare violate the imperial laws openly. Do they not know that there was such thing as an assassination? Did they think the law was omnipotent?

Perhaps it was the same most of the time on Earth, but in such troubled times, the fledglings that had lived in peaceful areas all their lives, without experiencing the brutality of war in the outside world.

After being urged by Vanderman, the group soon went underground under Maxilan’s watch. Hathaway and Andel then went down, with the protection from Edney.

The last ones at the manor were Vanderman and Garen, while Du Qian was escorting the people safely through the passageway.

Garen gathered all his totems together and surrounded them.

As he had hinted, the newborn beetles on the periphery quickly spread and began searching in all directions for the aristocrats’ companions, whom they had claimed to be left behind.

"Cia" Vanderman stood softly on the edge of the passage, the green light surrounding him got stronger and stronger.

He carefully took out a goose-egg-sized oval-shaped ball and he handed it to Garen.

"This one is for you, this is the Green Vine Sphere, the ultimate weapon that I had originally developed for our lineage. Unfortunately, you can not use it now."

Garen took the ball. The ball’s body was green and black, its surface seemingly glowing with a faint gleam of green.

"Green Vine Sphere is the core culmination of my life’s work, it can continue to synthesize spore-like seeds, attaching onto other people and absorb that person’s strength and power to grow. When it reaches a growth threshold, it will become living body armor. The point is, this layer of armor can equip regular people with the properties of the Totem’s Light. " Venderman explained simply.

With his Green Vine Sphere out, his had a defeated look on his face.

"This is the main breeder of the family, and you have to plant it on your own body. As to the choice of nurturing it, to provide it with nutrients to grow, that will all depend on yourself. But you have to remember, this is the main body that controls all the other spores. You must have complete control over it.Only by controlling it you can muster an army full of powerful creatures! Of course, the strength of the armor would depend on the person being leeched ... "

He told Garen about the characteristics of the sphere slowly.

Garen now realized why the Obscuro Society want to seize the fruits of his research. Such an item can make the overall strength of the entire force even higher, far more than a form 3 totem user or Spiritualization Totem User could.

"... and in addition, some of the research records of my experiments, and some academic materials I used were placed here." Vanderman once again took out a small red key. "Go to the Imperial Kingdom, this key can open the basement of the manor I live in. If you are not interested, burn them."

"Plus, I still have an old friend who might be able to take care of you."

********************

Garen sat in the wagon, quietly fiddling with the red key in his hand.

Angel sighed and sat across from him, looking fairly worse for wear. The wound on her right shoulder was carefully bandaged by Lala.

"I heard about your family. Do you think I should call you Garen, or Acacia?"

"It's still Garen. I'm the head of Trejons now, I have the right to change my name," Garen said quietly.

He looked out of the window. In the direction of the manor, a glimmer of green shone against a giant chimpanzee behemoth. This huge behemoth was a full 20 meters in height, but it seemed to have no special ability and was also slow in movement. It pounded one and on, but its fist was completely blocked by a green film of light.

Aouhhh! !

A few punches could not break through the green egg shell-thick film. The gorilla raged with a ferocious roar after lifting its head.

The echo of the roar caused severe vibrations surrounding it, even as far as clearly reaching the carriage some tens of kilometers away.

"What the hell is that creature?" Angel saw the calm look on Garen’s face, which remained so, as if he had long been aware of the situation revolving the creature.

"The war behemoth." Calon coldly replied, "It is only large in size, but its actions are very slow. It’s also very difficult to control, only useful in sieges as it is almost equivalent to the existence of a siege vehicle. What is worth noting is that it is accompanied by Elite Guardian Unit. "

"Elite Guardian Unit?"

"Well, it's a squad that specializes in protecting war beasts from being killed in close combat. According to rank, a war behemoth should have a lieutenant-led Guardian unit present." Garen squinted his eyes slightly.

Speaking of which, Garen thought of Vanderman, who was still in the manor. Viscount knew that death was near, and as Garen and the rest entered the passageway, he sealed the entrance to face the advent of the enemy alone.

A general, who would typically possess two Form 3 totems or more, not to mention the other unit members, Garen’s totem was seriously injured this time. It simply couldn’t endure any more attacks. In case the white-robed man from Terraflor Society had in fact not left and was waiting for the right opportunity, and if both sides clashed again, the result will be very unfavorable. The opponent was targeting Vanderman. Without someone delaying him, there definitely would not be an escape.

"Sister Du Qian!"

"Sir Du Qian!"

A few anxious shouts were heard from afar.

Garen quickly jumped out of the carriage, he looked back only to see a green silhouette.

"Sorry Young Master, I need to accompany Master." A voice which hadn’t dissipated said.

Garen stood still and did not chase her. He knew Du Qian has been living for Vanderman. Her love for him was far too deep. From when they left, he had expected that Du Qian would not leave the manor so easily.

Maxilan and Hathaway gave chase, but to no avail, and they soon came back helplessly. When Garen looked at them, Hathaway shook her head and did not utter a word.

"Forget it, let’s get back on our journey." Garen fell silent for a while, then said. "All aboard the car!"

Hathaway was unwilling, but she did not protest.

The rest of the people who were outside the carriage also saved their words; as the new head of Trejons, his words were law.

A boom cracked skies above them soon after everyone re-embarked and rushed ahead.

The strong explosion was followed by a cloud of black smoke rising into the sky.

Garen sat in the carriage. He knew it was the last he would see of Vanderman, and although there was not much of a sense of belonging to the father he had called Vanderman, he still felt lonely inside.

Vanderman himself was a contradiction. He had played multiple roles; a kind father and a host, a ruthless aristocrat, and scientist, and the martyr who had given everything for his dreams and vows.

The team was crowded with a more than 20 people inside, quickly fleeing the Trejons Manor. From the rear, they followed the bank of Black Swan Lake and head towards deeper into the Kovitan Empire.

"What's your plan?" Angel asked from opposite Garen.

Garon exhaled lightly.

What’s next was not within his initial plan, but Obscuro and Terraflor Society will not let go of his parasitic breeder. Trouble will automatically come to their doorstep.

"Let's go to the capital," he whispered. "It is said that the Twelve Princesses were supposed to come, and it is certainly impossible to come back now."

"I've got some intel too." Angel drank the coffee Lala served quickly. "Going from this direction, we will soon reach the defensive checkpoint of the West Farm Border of Kovitan Empire, a defensive line carefully built by the Royal Alliance, a completely safe area for human beings. That area is much better guarded, and I would also be able to contact the war guild using my letter of introduction from Iron Tank City Branch President. "

"Not bad..."

"I heard that there were a total of three large regiments at Kovitan’s West Farm borders; the Hawks of Dawn, the Third Heavy Armor Regiment and the Navy Flag. The three regiments each occupy three strongholds, and from here."

Angel took out a map, pushed away the coffee, and opened the map on the desk.

Three positions have been marked separately, similar to the points of a triangle. They were displayed on a map of Kovitan that looked like a large cookie. Just on the lower left corner of the map area was the edge of the Green Lush District, which immediately led into the nearby location of the province of Vesice.

"Regiments? Do commoner forces have any effect?" Gallon doubted.

"No, it's all comprised of totem users from what I’ve heard from the totem users that came to the Manor from the capital." The Baddeck Empire in the southwest was exterminated, and a large number of surviving citizens of Baddeck poured into Kovitan. Among them, a lot of totem users from Baddeck joined the Kovitan Army out of spite." Angel shook her head," Even the moderately sized Baddek Empire got wiped out. Obscuro Society and these monsters are really cruel."

Garen fell silent.

He first looked under his own attribute pane.

'Strength 6.66. Agile 2.72. Vitality 2.82. Intellect 2.53. Potential 17221%. '

He previously accumulated more than two hundred potential points, but he spent more due to the evolution of two Petrifying White Dragons, and now was left with 172 points. Evolving the Petrifying White Dragon into a form 3 totem was a very economical proposition.

Unfortunately, he can no longer continue its evolution.

Garon had some regrets.

This time, in order to deal with the dangers he might encounter, he had decisively evolved two Petrifying Lizards, grew them to Petrifying White Dragons. He had three Petrifying White Dragons and a Dual-Headed Salamander, yet he barely suppressed Beckstone. His hidden trump card, the monstrous monster’s grip, also allowed him to endure the final ambush.

The monster grip had a substantial defense against totem light defenses, if this were any other totem user, perhaps this would be a normal trump card, only effective when the enemy came near.

But for Garen, the characteristic that weakened totems was simply complimentary to him.

As a Secret Technique Master, the totem’s light was his greatest obstacle, and now with a substantial reduction of this obstruction, his Secret Techniques finally were of some use.

Removing the totem light and totem user, the only threat left were strong ontology and special abilities.

It can be said that the monster grip gave him an important opportunity to pick up Secret Techniques again.

Garen recalled what happened when he transmigrated to this world.

Smoky pots, volcanoes, Endorian civilizations and more civilizations, city monsters.

Everything seems to be making clear that this world had a different general connection to the previous world.

Chapter 349: At the End 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Sitting in the wagon, Garen carefully arranged all the conditions that he knew. The core totem, Black-Striped White Tiger, had been repaired.

He intended to take advantage of the team’s lull period to upgrade the Black-Striped White Tiger into form 2 properly. He might seem surrounded by totems, but in the event of an ambush, or if he wanted more room for improvements down the road, nothing was as good as his core totem to upgrade.

Be it the Petrifying White Dragon or the Dual-headed Salamander, they had no way to be further upgraded, as they had reached the end of their genetic lineage.

The only proper direction of upgrade now was the core totem. Perhaps he would be able to collect all sorts of creatures and to test their evolutionary limits, but the time wasn't now.

As he was deep in thought, a faint signal suddenly got pinged in his brain.

"Found it?" He stood up. "You go along, I'm going out for a while, I'll catch up to you soon."

Angel nodded. "Be careful."

Gallon nodded, and jumped out of the carriage after opening the door.

The beetles’ reaction indicated that the target was not far away, and he should be able to reach it soon.

Once Garen got off the carriage, he suddenly turned into a gray shadow and went into the woods quickly, climbing along the towering trees up to the canopy before breaching the treeline.

Jiii! !

A Petrifying White Dragon was gliding low, just low enough to grab hold of Garen firmly.

*******************

Aquarius was standing on a hillside from afar, looking at Trejons Manor completely destroyed by the gorillas. Her heart expressed a kind of unspeakable pleasure.

She stood and was surrounded by a group of people, including both men and women, old and young, but they all had the same kind of smile.

These were the men whom she gathered amidst these troubled times. Five Type II Totem Users, all of whom were the best of the elites. Some of them are desperados from foreign enemies, some had been loyal servants of Aquarius for many years. There were also Obscuro Society members who weren't able to return after seceding.

One of them, the leader of the Green Share, knelt on one knee and reported to Aquarius.

"After the great apes left, we searched the vicinity of the manor for some time, and sure enough we captured some of the Kovitan noblemen who escaped from the manor, we found out some pretty good things from them."

"That's good, send it all to the warehouse." Aquarius was feeling good. "Vanderman is finally dead. Fighting him covertly and overtly for so many years, he was finally able to lay to rest. Fasa."

"Here," A man donning red hunting attire near her stood up.

"Send the news to the branch right away. Sequoia, how many people do we have now?"

Another woman in red stood up. "Fifteen form 2 totem users, thirty-two ordinary guards, most of them from Green Shade. Lieutenant Colonel Wen Rui has also arrived, and is now resting in the manor."

"Lieutenant Colonel Wen Rui, he has got quite a force behind him, just in time to support us." Aquarius nodded. "Unfortunately, our elite division is here, otherwise we could have looted more good items if we had left earlier."

"It's just that we were unclear of the situation; it felt like a war broke out in the manor previously, the specific situation is yet unknown." The girl in red whispered. "Maybe the elite division knows more about the situation, but the elite people always look down upon other departments, even us. They have also previously had some conflicts with Lieutenant Colonel Farr."

"They actually dared to go against the mighty Lieutenant Colonel Farr, do these people have water for brains?" Rose's face reveals a trace of disgust. "All these kids who never grew up!"

"Unfortunately, there aren't any influential people in our military to preside over the overall situation." Speaking of this, there was a sliver of hope on Aquarius’ face. "I hope that the sir isn't just a passerby ..."

Du ...

Suddenly, something in her arms vibrated slightly.

Aquarius hurriedly took out the derivator from the pocket inside her, which was a pale red, transparent crystal ball the size of the fist.

A line of Kovitan words slowly appeared on the crystal ball.

‘Your request has been approved. '

Aquarius' face suddenly looked ecstatic.

She was just bolstering a tryout attitude when she contacted for a request.

"It actually ... !!"

An unprecedented excitement gushed from the bottom of her heart, she, Aquarius Sembenita, was about to get rich! !

"Everyone! Bow down in unison !!"

She took a deep breath and shouted.

Wow!

Including her, they all knelt on one knee.

The reddish crystal ball was placed in front of her on a tree branch. Flashing on it were words establishing a connection.

*********************

Garen rode on the white dragon's back, watching the woods’ carriage lanes quickly receding below. He looked up and looked toward the direction of the beetles.

He thought about it for a moment, then fished out the derivator.

The derivator was restored to its original pink color after the activation from Lala’s empowerment.

As it was taken out, the crystal ball glowed with a slight red fluorescence.

On top of it were some continuous patterns of ripples.

'Communication requests: 3 found.'

"Three communication requests?" Garen was slightly surprised. The crystal’s latency situation had been completely resolved after empowering Lala. Now he can even maintain contact with other crystal balls.

He hesitated slightly. Then click on the option to allow the request.

Jiiii ...

Like the chime of a television signal. Three threads appeared simultaneously on the crystal ball screen.

'- Elite Division Lieutenant Colonel Charles. '

'- Lush Forest District, Brigadier General Canberra. '

'- Lush Forest District, Colonel Aquarius. '

"Aquarius?" Garen smiled oddly.

He tapped on Rose's contact request.

With a subtle click, the contact soon connected.

"I'm Jess, Colonel Aquarius, please immediately report your location."

****************

A small hill in the woods

Aquarius’ group looked over the moon as they knelt on one knee, facing the crystal ball.

Not only her, but the others got unusually excited when they learned that there was actually an elemental general in the Lush Forest District.

Elemental Generals!

They possess innate strength, with a wave of a hand, they could summon high combat power units. Being a commander was only one step away. Every elemental general was extremely powerful people. Their combat power was much higher than the luminescence.

To be an elemental general, they were all geniuses among geniuses, the elite among the elite!

Being a Brigadier General was once Aquarius’ biggest wish, and now she had actually met a real elemental general! This made her feel restless from excitement.

"I'm Jess, Colonel Aquarius, please report your location immediately." A low, hoarse voice came from inside the crystal ball.

"Dear General Jess, I am in a manor in the Trejons Territory. You can locate me directly from the crystal ball, not far from here." Aquarius’ voice trembled. Originally, someone at her level, who had not reached a general, would have had no way to come into contact with such a big shot. Unexpectedly, such opportunity had finally emerged.

"Fine. I'm consolidating resources, list it all that you have and report in." General Jess's voice sank indifferently, with a sense of oppression.

"Yes! Consider it done!" Immediately afterwards, she hesitated, "Please tell me, your Excellencies, we originally belonged to the Lieutenant Colonel Grely , but now the Lieutenant colonel is missing in action, the whole Lush Forest District is in a disarray. There is no unification or leadership. I plead that Your Excellency integrate the strengths within the Lush Forest to prevent anyone from taking advantage of the power vacuum. "

She paused, then continued. "In addition, about resources, I have unexpectedly come across a phantom workshop of some secret surgery, would you be interested ..."

She knew, however, that now that the heroes of the masses had lost their prominence, each province resembled headless flies, pushed around by swarming monsters everywhere. The lieutenants only cared to manage their own areas of jurisdiction, no one cared much about the remote areas of the province. The original lieutenant-general here was also killed in an assassination ordered by the king of Kovitan, during their siege on RAL.

Even the lieutenants are despised here, let alone the generals.

Several nearby generals ignored the situation here. Each had its own jurisdiction, problems were left unsolved, no one had the mood to care about these trivialities.

The Obscuro Society in Lush Forest District could barely protect themselves in each battle; the side division only had one brigadier-general holding on. As Kovitan Empire became more powerful, they had been longing for a strong leader to lead them. Unfortunately, this wish was too difficult to achieve.

No one was willing to pressure Kovitan for a Lush Forest that was so drained of resources.

Aquarius’ pressure was also growing. Now, finally, finally somebody cared about the entire Lush Forest District.

This finally made her feel a sense of relief.

"Secret Tactics? Phantom workshop?" Colonel Jess seemed to have never heard of them.

"This tactic is a curing technique that allows all the totem under you to be attached with a layer of bone defense. It is said that a special hard bone was found in the archaeological site by someone from the phantom workshop, " Aquarius hurriedly explained. "Phantom Workshop is Lush Forest's best workshop union."

"Understood, You shall look into it. Send the maximum resources you can manage to this location." The crystal ball suddenly showed a line of words. Impressively, it was the Black Swan Lake near the shore.

.

"Understood!" Rose hurriedly nodded.

"Well, I look forward to your performance. Colonel Aquarius. " General Jess's voice disappeared from the crystal ball shortly after.

Aquarius and others kneeling on the ground on one knee, took a long time before they slowly stood up.

She kept the crystal ball, and Aquarius turned back delightfully.

"Gentlemen, it is time for us to perform, although General Jess will not govern us as our direct superior, but as long as we seize this opportunity, we will be able to come under James and gain the protection of the general! We will not be repressed by the disgusting rubbish of the royal family!

"What are some of the resources that General Jess said he wanted? He did not give a conclusion." Sequoia could not help but speak out.

"This should be a test given to us. To only speak about a resource and not specify specifics, it would be to test our sincerity and loyalty. How many rare evolutionary crystals do we have now, Ravanu."

"Three ... ma’m, that's the treasure that you’ve got after so much trouble, it could catalyze the evolution of most totems and prepare to be used in your evolutionary totem. Giving it all away.... Do you ..." Ravanu was a black, dark-skinned man who stood out in distress.

"This is a crucial moment to show your determination!" Aquarius hurled her hand upwards energetically. "Send them all to the designated location, if there are spare unactivated totems of high quality, send two-thirds of them. Just leaving some for emergencies will do, the two sets of tactical formation and all the energy crystals in the store are to be sent to him."

Chapter 350: At the End 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"But Lieutenant Colonel! The two sets of tactical array were the trump cards your father prepared for you, just sending them in vain, what if ..." Green shade whispered.

"If you want to go big, you must first have a have the resolve and generosity!" Said Aquarius, narrowing her eyes. "When a general unexpectedly lacks resources, it is time for us to show our loyalty. These little things; it would have amounted to nothing at another place and time to him, there would have been many other people who wanted to send them over, I believe he would not even bat an eye, but now, it is different! We must seize this opportunity!

"Lieutenant-Colonel is wise! I think so too. For a general to actually require resources in Lush Forest district to be mobilized, it is certainly a special occasion, this is precisely the time to show our loyalty." An elderly totem user stood up and agreed with Aquarius’ plans.

"Not bad. So not only do we have to send resources, but we also have to send enough good resources!" Said Aquarius firmly.

***************

Garen looked at the crystal ball’s words as he ended the communication, his mood was exceptionally comfy.

Of the three communications requests, one of them was actually Aquarius.

He almost forgot that Aquarius was one of the heads here.

In addition to Aquarius, the other two communications, one was sent by the General from the elite division. He did not connect to it.

The last one came from one of the two generals he had contacted previously: Demetrius.

Garen thought for a moment, and casually opened the link.

The snapping sound lasted for a long time, and finally, after more than 10 seconds, the crystal ball a burst of coughing sounds came from the derivator.

"This is Demetrius, Jess, why did you only contact me now?"

"My crystal ball had some issues previously, is there anything?" Garen replied with a low tone.

"There is something, you are on your way to Kovitan, right? There were three generals there who are now missing, and now there is no leader in the whole branch. The commander wishes that you take over the branch for now." Demetrius said simply.

"Promote me? Are you kidding? The three generals are gone, do you think I can resist the forces behind those incidents?" Garen’s voice suddenly cooled down.

"The above is still satisfied with your performance in Iron Tank City, but with the death of a Grand Duke of White Dragonhawk, and also the emergence of King of the Skies, the commander is also furious." Demetrius explained. "What the commander meant is, for the time being, only for the time being, you can manage the Kovitan side temporarily, and not to clash with the King of Kovitan. As for the rest, you just need to wait quietly. The situation will change quickly. "

"Oh, a turn in tides?" Garen’s heart moved. "The king of Kovitan is a king of great caliber, strong and experienced, top notch strategies and decision-making, The turn in tides, you said ...?"

"Have the people in elite divisions reached you? The plan for this is their responsibility,I am not very clear myself. You can ask the elite division about the situation."

Demetrius pushed the responsibilities, "Try to exercise some restraint, avoid any conflicts. This is the wish of the commander. "

"Who's the supreme leader over there?" Jaron asked directly.

"Delouse, Delouse Jacques." Demetrius solemnly said the name.

Garen was finally startled. "The Kovitan Princess! She was also one of us!?"

"The plan was laid out many years ago, and the secret is only accessible for the general level, and you'd better keep it a little tight, though it's not far from success," Demetrius told.

"I know."

"By the way, are you sure you have no issues with the derivator? The people of the Obscuro are also in Kovitan. Do you want them to fix it for you?"

"Nothing, just a little issue."

"That's good."

Pap!

The contact was disconnected.

Garen sat on the back of the dragon, blowing cold air in the sky, but his heart fell cold.

Princess Delouse, King of Kovitan’s favorite princess, one would not even think she is of the Obscuro society, let alone the elite division’s leader.

"Iron Tank City, Kovitan, Ender , East Continent .... A really big chess set..." He squinted slightly.

As for Vanderman's technology, Demetrius did not mention that at this level, the most it could do was to raise base power. It did not affect the upper management at all.

When the core totem reaches the third form, the core and the totem user can merge for a short time, doubling their power and doubling their defense. All of the secondary totems do not have this ability.

While this technique is good for improving the underlying totem, it does not make a big difference at a high level. So, be it Obscuro Society or Terraflor Society, they were not very concerned about the Green Vine Sphere.

Mortals will remain a mortal, even with the properties of the totem’s light, in face of all kinds of advanced totems, it still didn’t possess much fighting power.

Originally, he was out, ready to kill Aquarius, but now he had temporarily suspended the idea. He intended to use General Jess' identity to loot all the silly Rose’s treasures, and then kill her. Was not a better choice?

Petrifying White Dragon’s wings soared forward, and soon it landed on the edge of the Swan Lake, on the forests which were broken and knocked down.

Laying on the ground was a few lavishly dressed aristocratic totem users. These people were the noblemen students who had previously escaped from the manor. They actually want to threaten Garen and Vanderman.

"Reckless bunch." Garen kicked a body of a noble and flipped it over.

The body’s neck was completely severed with a line of blood, with minimal effort, the head and body would separate, the head would roll to the other side.

The Petrifying White Dragon dual headed salamander respectfully laid beside Garen; there are several Deep Swamp Crocs around the edge.

After the brawl with Beckstone at the manor, the number of Deep Swamp Croc plummeted, leaving only six here. The beetles had only a dozen newborns.

Garon took out the green vine sphere; it was like a living thing, still continuing to stretch its green roots, tentacle constantly waving. It's like a ball of wool that got its thread everywhere.

He gently flicked green vine sphere.

Spherical surface suddenly popped out a few green lights, it fell on all around the totem’s body.

The green light attached to the body of the totem, then there were no movement.

Garon put away the green vine sphere, he had guessed that it might take some time for it to take effect, but also ordered these totems not to get rid of the green light spots.

He put on his hood, his whole person was now hidden under gray robes.

After the communication with elemental general Demeritus, Garen gained more understanding about the current situation.

He remembered that in the history he had seen, the king of Kovitan was assassinated and, and the entirety of the Kovitan suddenly collapsed. However, there was still a long period of time from the event in Iron Tank city. Now, it should be the completion phase of Obscuro's planning.

He was now primarily controlled by the derivator. Then, between choosing to upgrade the core totem and seizing control of the derivator, both ways were viable.

The main key to the control of the derivator is the resonant stone in his hand.

Garen was fiddling with the stone, it had completely changed now, and became much like an ordinary gray stone. In the hands of Garen, it was totally losing its semblance of the strange meat from before .

Garen has fiddled with it for so long with the powerful five senses and acumen honed by his Secret Techniques. He could faintly feel the secret this rock held.

Garen was slowly grasping the pattern of the frequency model of the resonant stone. As long as he thoroughly understood the resonance principle, he could have a more in-depth understanding and start research on the crystal derivator. Garen was very confident in this area. With enough research material and subject knowledge, he could use it to for evolution.

The core totem, black-striped white tiger, had crystal spots, with enough potential points, and was also repaired. Everything was ready, it was just a matter of when evolution began.

Garen sat by the Black Swan Lake. Looking across diagonally was the location of the original Vanderman Manor, charred beyond recognition. A fire was raging from within, destroying the wooden structure, releasing echoes of breaking timber periodically.

The great ape was now gone, so was the manor, without a trace of human life left.

The blaze was imprinted on the surface of the black lake, and a grey cloud above slowly shifted its way across the smoke filled sky.

.

Time passed with each second and minute.

Garen's totems were dispersed and hidden. The manor's fire was still burning, its intensity ever-increasing.

Garen faced the fire, quietly standing under a tree by the lake.

Soon, a buffalo with red metal skin laden with many black boxes of varying sizes walked out from the forest behind him.

Escorted by a number of young men and women wearing black armor, these people saw Garen standing by the lakeside, and suddenly held their tracks.

Leading the unit was a person wearing a delicate black dress, light brown hair, with a slim body and well-developed chest. The impressive Aquarius, as usual.

This enchanting woman had a pair of beautiful almond eyes, lips covered with light pink lipstick, ears adorned with white pearl earrings. At this point, she was puzzlingly looked at the gray robes by the lake.

"Excuse me, were you sent by His Excellency Jess to receive these resources?" She whispered.

"Dear goddess Aquarius, it’s been a while, it is really disappointing that you actually don’t recognize me."

The man in gray robe slowly turned around, removed his hood, revealing a smiling handsome face.

Aquarius’ eyes was first puzzled, then her pupils shrunk, it seems that she recalled something, her eyes became intense and stared speechless. She raised her hand, pointing at the man for a while, uttering nought a word.

Pap!

Garen snapped his fingers.

Surrounding his audience were a bunch of terrifying red eyes from within the dense forest, within the shadow of the woods. A looming aura of danger presided over them.

"How could you know this !!" Aquarius was was flustered, her gaze firm and staring at Garen opposite from her. "This is the place where General Jess will be meeting us, you are not Acacia !! Who are you?"

Garen spread his arms, the crystal derivator slowly floated from his hands, turning into a light red glimmer.

"Take a guess?" His voice at this time actually split into two, a hoarse voice, and another clear and bright, overlapping each other. It made one feel a sense of unnatural discomfort.

Aquarius was stone-cold. She heard one of the voices, the one that was the sound of General Jess.

"Let’s move!!"

Without hesitation, she shouted as she turned back swiftly.

Chapter 351: Resolve 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Fuu..."

"Fuu ..."

"Fuu ....."

Aquarius gasped for air as she unleashed four successive lightning movement tactics. They were pre-stored in the tactics chain of her ability, and used for escaping directly.

She was completely alone now, without any subordinates. She wasn’t very concerned with that at the moment though.

Just as her body halted, several Red Eyed Giant Wolves reappeared in the woods in front of her. Each of these giant wolves were about a man’s height and their bodies were covered in festering wounds; on a normal Giant Wolf, it would have been on the verge of keeling over.

"Damn it! They’re Vanderman's Rotten Giant Wolves!!" She paled as she sensed countless wolves around her, "The Green Vine Sphere! This is definitely the Green Vine Sphere! Only the Green Vine Sphere can control these experimental bodies scattered outside!"

She took two steps back, feeling a familiar howling again in the back, which was the roar of Rotten Giant Wolves.

The number of these wolves was overwhelming; this was obviously planned.

"I've got everything out! Don’t be so aggressive!" Aquarius called out.

Suddenly she spun to her left, and flung herself to the ground.

Krakk ! !

A huge hole was ripped out from the ground, and a large bite mark remained where she’d been standing. The beast had ferociously bitten a large patch of ground and quickly retreated, leaving behind a crater two meters wide.

Aquarius’ heart pounded wildly as she vigilantly observed her surroundings. Her subordinates has been left far behind when she’d used a few lightning movements.

She ground her teeth.

"As long as you help me delay that man, I will help settle everything else on your end... please last a little longer ..."

As she stood up, she was unusually embarrassed.

Her dress was streaked with soil, and soil was also streaked in her hair.

She thought for a moment, while she lightly dusted dirt off the back of her dress.

A silver light streaked out and landed in front of her, shapeshifting into a dark green Python. On each side of the python’s head was a pair of white feathered wings, which was rather strange.

"Get rid of the guy in the ground!" She mentally ordered.

The giant python immediately drilled downwards, disappearing into the ground.

Awoo!

A Rotten Giant Wolf leapt towards Aquarius unexpectedly, bringing a foul stench as it attempted to bite at Aquarius’ neck.

At the same time, another Rotten Giant Wolf rushed over from behind; more than ten Wolves were rushing forward at the same time from the surrounding dense forest.

Roar! ! !

A frenzied roar bellowed from Aquarius’ location. At the same time a wave of yellow energy blasted forth.

More than ten Rotten Giant Wolves were blown back by the shockwave and tumbled to the ground, where after struggling several times, they soon melted into puddles of pus.

Once again, a dozen Rotten Giant Wolves rushed at her from the forest.

Just as Aquarius thought to move, she’d been cornered by the giant wolves.

Garen leisurely strolled out of the woods, watching the rotten giant wolves surround Aquarius.

The Green Vine Sphere could control up to more than two hundred Rotten Giant Wolves; these experimental bodies were merely ordinary wolves covered in spores. Their power could only be considered a Type 1 totem beast, which wasn’t very strong. They were disposable though, which improved their feasibility.

Noticing that Aquarius had been completely surrounded by the Giant Wolves, the underground Dual-Headed Salamander was blocked by the winged python released by Aquarius, and both were tangled together. Garen was surprised.

"What about your derivator? Or your other totems? Why did you not bring them out?" He clapped his hands, a signal for the large pack of wolves to disband and disperse.

At the center, Aquarius looked dishevelled. The escape techniques stored in the tactic chains within her cuffs had all been used up. she glared at Garen.

"It’s impossible for you to be Acacia! Who are you, and why do you hold so much animosity against me?"

Garen chuckled.

"Did we not meet once long ago? I was Cia, how could you forget all of that? Cia, who wrote those love poems dedicated to you."

The Green Vine Sphere was able to control more than two hundred Rotten Giant Wolves, which Garen intended to be used as a general measure. The Dual-Headed Salamander had actually been suppressed by a strange python, which astonished Garen.

That strange python was obviously the opponent’s only Form 3 totem.

At this moment, Aquarius was in despair. All her Type 2 totems had just got through a war and were pretty much exhausted, leaving only her strongest green python, and her only Form 3 double-winged python, coupled with a tactics chains. These were all the means left to her, but in front of this man, it barely made a difference.

Her Form 3 double-winged python was currently being suppressed, and there were still several dangerous presences lurking close by, she could feel it.

Aquarius had had a keen sense of danger since an early age. This sense of danger had saved her too many times, so when she saw that dark robed man, she knew that her opponent had laid down a huge ambush and so she decisively abandoned her subordinates. She escaped alone using four consecutive lightning movements, which consumed almost all of her totems’ power. Even after fleeing hundreds of kilometers away, she still couldn’t shake this man off.

She faintly felt that this was her first time meeting this man.

The scenario ahead of her felt exactly the same as before; a scary opponent whom she could not escape from no matter how hard she tried. The same tall man was toying with her with an amused gaze.

"Keabo!! You are Keabo!!" She suddenly shouted loudly. "You dare attack me! My father will not forgive this! Never!"

Garen was stunned, as he did not expect that she would make such outlandish exclamations.

"Who is Keabo?" Before he even managed to open his mouth to ask the question, Aquarius had turned and fled, through the crevices in the trees towards the lake.

He raised his hand.

Jii!

A Deep Swamp Croc suddenly leapt out and tackled Aquarius. She tumbled to the ground and rolled over.

The woman panted for a while before attempting to stand up. The layer of green totem light around hers was splattered with viscous black mud. As though it had been on glass instead, the mud slowly slid off back onto the ground.

"What are you trying to do ?!" She stood still as she glowered at Garen.

Garen slowly walked towards her.

"I have to thank you for the supplies that you brought me. You’re from the elite department at Vandermann Manor aren’t you?"

"So what? You’re dead meat once they find out about this!" Aquarius spat hatefully, her voice faltering. "This time, the elite department is led by an actual Lieutenant General again and he has a strong backing. You still have time to retreat, and I will explain to the superiors that this was a misunderstanding."

"Retreat?" Garen could not help but chuckle. "Aquarius, I thought you were an intelligent woman, I didn’t expect that at such a crucial moment, you actually became so witless."

He suddenly spun about and delivered a side kick.

Bam!

His right leg blurred into a gray shadow and jabbed at Aquarius’ waist.

Aquarius tumbled like a gourd as she rolled on the ground a dozen times and crashed into a big tree. A large slab of bark fell from the impact of her collision. Leaves drifted from the tree’s branches like rain.

Aquarius had been protected by her Totem’s Light hence she wasn’t severely injured, and quickly stood back up.

Her hair was slovenly and her eyes were locked on the ground while she paid attention to Garen, in fear that he’d pull out tricks once more.

"Trying to summon your Form 3 totem?" Garen smiled. "Unfortunately ... my little baby is keeping it busy. It should be a while before a winner can be decided. "

"What the hell do you want?!" Aquarius withdrew and backed herself to the tree’s trunk. "My father is a Brigadier General in the Obscuro Society, he can give you money! He can give you anything you want! As long as you take me hostage, you can do a direct exchange!"

"That's not what I need, I only want you." Garen shook his head. Unexpectedly, he heard a woman's muffled shriek from the right.

He looked around, he unexpectedly saw another Aquarius being tackled by the Deep Swamp Croc.

Meanwhile, the Aquarius standing in front of the trunk gradually vanished.

.

"Oh? An illusion?" Garen had a stern face. "You sure have a lot of tricks up your sleeve. One simple lieutenant colonel almost fooled me."

His eyes opened wide, his iris suddenly glowed red and a circle of bloody symbols in his eyes flashed.

Aquarius shuddered under Garen’s glower. Her totem light suddenly dimmed and her defensive capabilities decreased sharply, by more than half.

Aquarius’ face paled. She spun about and bolted as fast as she could, similar to a frightened hare, into the bushes behind her.

Yet Garen was faster; his figure blurred into a gray shadow and he blocked her path with ease. He then stretched out his left hand and brushed gently against Aquarius’ forehead.

His palm and her Totem’s Light touched lightly.

Kacha!

The totem’s light suddenly shattered like glass into black and green fragments as it dissipated into thin air.

The weak rays weakened Aquarius’ Totem’s Light even further. As Garen was carrying the Green Vine Sphere, all his attacks carried the Totem’s Light properties. Soon, Aquarius’ Totem’s Light was completely shattered.

Bang bang! ! Aquarius was violently flung and her body bounced off the ground several times before crashing into a large green boulder. Her battered body tumbled aside.

She lay on the ground covered in moss and grass, her face swollen. As she was unable to stand back up, the impact must injured some part of her back.

"Don’t ... Please don’t kill me ... I don’t want to die!!" Aquarius futilely attempted to get up several times, and a suppressed sob was leaking into her voice. "Don’t ... Don’t kill me .... My father is a brigadier!"

Garen stopped in front of her, and he gazed at the sniffling and sobbing woman. She had completely lost all semblance to her previous bewitching appearance, and was now a mere human.

"For the person who led the elite department and led to Vanderman’s death in his own manor, it’s much too late to be speaking of this." He said lightly.

Aquarius, who wanted to push up her body, was still unable to lift herself.

"Don’t kill me, I can do a lot of favours for you ... A ton of them!!" She wailed and shrunk backwards, trying to maintain her distance from Garen.

As Garen looked upwards and gazed at the gray sky, he suddenly felt some inexplicable emotions.

"Didn’t you like me? I can be your lover! or your slave! Don’t kill me, don’t ..." Aquarius incoherently spoke.

Garen stood in front of her, quietly observing.

Poof!

Aquarius suddenly coughed up blood, her chest had been dyed red in an instant. Her face carried an blank look, as though she had no clue what had happened. She raised her hand and stared at the blood coating it.

Poof!

Yet another spurt of blood.

"No!! I don’t want to die!!"

She wailed loudly.

Jii! Jii! Jii !!

Soon, wounds appeared all over Aquarius, and blood streamed out as though it was from a morbid fountain.

"Mum ... Dad .... Uwaa .. where are you?" Aquarius cried aloud, she began to grope about with her hand aimlessly, her pretty almond eyes had almost completely dissolved, and she could not see anything; both her eyes had turned black.

"Mum ... Waa ..."

Garen stood silently in front of her as he watched her blood-streaked body. She was still searching with her hands on the ground, sobbing.

"The deepest feelings surface only in their most desperate moments." He tightened his dark robe and turned away.

Bam! ! !

A blast rang from behind him. Aquarius’ body exploded into a bloody mist, and her blood splattered the surrounding trees and grass, dying the vicinity red.

Chapter 352: Resolve 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Sitting within the caravan’s carriage, Garen quietly calculated the formula in front of him, lines of tiny alphanumeric formulas flowed from the tip of his pen, neatly written on a sheet of white paper.

The wagon’s wheels rolled slowly, its creak blending with the rustling sound of writing.

The morning light shimmered in from the window, and illuminated some of the darker parts within the carriage.

They’d arrived at a safe zone; outside the carriage was the heavily armored white horse cavalry that had escorted them. These cavalryman were led by a Form 1 Totem User, whose head was held high and his chest bulged as he rode on horseback in white armor. The handsome man displayed an aura of pride and bravery.

Garen glanced away from the side of the cavalry.

"We're about to reach the West Farm defense line right?" he murmured.

Angel shrugged as she sat opposite him,carefully moving her injured shoulder to answer the question.

"Even the patrol cavalry has appeared, we’re definitely closer. According to the map, we should arrive in the afternoon." She paused, "Leila talked to them for a while, and she asked a few questions regarding the defensive lines."

"Give me the details."

"The West Farm defensive line is mainly patrolled by totem users leading elite soldiers, and an outpost and fortress is built every two hundred kilometers for the stationing of totem users. Each fortress is run by a lieutenant-class totem user, with at least ten Form 2 totem users stationed. Almost all of humanity's most elite troops are stationed on this line of defense, "Angel explained while she removed the bandage from her shoulder.

"After they learnt of the fall of Vanderman Manor, the cavalrymen were also shocked. The Vanderman Manor was interdependent with the stronghold here and was one of the 68 front-line strongholds. Now that it had been destroyed, they need to look into recalibrating their defensive lines, and wait for reinforcement troops. "Angel clenched her teeth, peeled the bandage off and swiped a cotton swab dipped in alcohol to sterilize the wound.

"I heard ... Ughh ... I heard that not only was the Vanderman Manor destroyed, in the nearby Thousand Cranes Manor, nobody survived. This is possibly be a large move by the Obscuro Society" She endured the pain and re-wrapped her new bandage.

"Yes, news of the Iron Tank City incident has spread throughout the entire human safe zone. Not only the Grand Duke of Blackfield Dragonhawk, of hundreds of kingdoms in East Continent, thousands of cities of different sizes, only one hundred and eighty two cities survived and have now been divided into six safe areas. Do you know which are the six? "Angel spiritedly asked.

"Which six?" Garen smiled and calmly asked.

"You're calm," Angel glanced at him in surprise. "Iron Tank District, centered in Iron Tank city, is called black territory because it is protected by the Duke of the Blackfield, and the surrounding twelve cities were reconstructed around Iron Tank City."

"Then Prince Alexander of Glory City , brother to King of Ender and the eldest son of Prince Tangula, also known as the Black Prince, his glorious city is at the core, the surrounding ten cities are being rebuilt and they are forming a complete basin defense known as the dragonfield."

Angel sipped some water, then continued speaking.

"Another is Queen Jean Earnest, a peerless beauty once hailed as the never-withering flower. She is also an unexpectedly strong totem user. She’s taken the Avision city as the core. Adjacent to Trinity, this city is reputed with the revival of fifteen cities. The queen is hailed as the queen of blood by unimaginative poets, and the area she protects is known as the Avision City."

"Those are only three safe areas, what are the rest?" Garen asked while calculating the formula.

"There is also the kingdoms of the three great powers forming the central safe zone: Kovitan, Canbria and Ender.Those three kingdoms combined with the capital as the core, establishing a huge security zone .The Three Empire Defense Circle, as well as the Blackfield Dragonfield, Avision City and Iron Tank District are now the entire congregation of six safe havens for people in East Continents, the rest are nothing but wastelands, all of them mutants and wild creatures.

Garen smiled but did not speak; the so-called land of death was only the public view. In fact, Obscuro Society, as well as Terraflor Society’s congregation spots were definitely not wastelands at all.

"A troubled world breeds heroes, I suppose this is true," Leila whispered around the side of her cup of coffee. "I also heard from a sister in the cavalry that there were a lot of powerful totem users coming from within the community."

"I also heard about that, it is rather lively around, we Kovitan have several famous totem users." Angel suddenly got interested.

They promptly ignored Garen, and chattered together on the side.

Garen shook his head and continued calculating his own model equations. With some classic books from Aquarius, his understanding and research on totems deepened.

In the process of sensing the Resonant Stone, he secretly combined it with the totem aspect in his system of knowledge, also with a trace of other gains.

As long as he managed to sipher study notes and academic books from Cia's father Vanderman while in the capital, he should be able to raise his research knowledge by several levels. He would then be able to unlock the secrets of the Crystal Derivator.

Regardless, the study done by Vanderman had reached a very deep level. Compared to other fields of study, it was the Grand Obscuro of Obscuro Society, the old senile people over at Terraflor, and even the three great empires’ Three Departments. Each of these were decent but their research headed in different directions, which was the cause of the many problems attracted by Vanderman.

Garen believes that as long as he find the research knowledge, he would definitely find out the way to completely control the crystal derivator.

Most importantly though was the evolution of his Black-Striped White Tiger.

He dropped the pen and checked the Black-Striped White Tiger's condition in its storage device. On his left ring finger was a black crystal ring which also doubled as the Black-Striped White Tiger's storage device.

After the Black-Striped White Tiger had been released and it had gobbled up the patterned crystal in several bites, Garen returned it into the ring, in accordance with the rhythm of evolution.

Now he has to wait for five hours, until the crystal was completely digested and absorbed.

He took out his pocket watch and checked the time.

"Just five hours."

Ignoring the two chatting people on the side, Garen set his eyes straight on the totem pane below his vision.

'Black-Striped White Tiger: Form 1 totem, upgradable. Evolution success rate: 11%. Potential consumption point: 700%.

Ability: Tail whip, rupturing bite. '

Checking his potential points, after killing Aquarius and the rest of the low-level totem users, he now accumulated more than two hundred points.

According to Black-Striped White Tiger core totem evolution law, he needs to obtain more than 100 points for a large activation and evolution. The Black-Striped White Tiger could not undergo fragmented genetic evolution and could only continue to activate large fragments, which was also the reason for its high potential point consumption.

Garen did not hesitate, his eyes stared down at the Black-Striped White Tiger icon. Three seconds later.

The potential points were drained significantly, as though a flood had washed them away.

Within a few seconds, the potential points had dropped by hundreds of points.

Garen’s face twitched in strong disapproval, as those potential points had been accumulated over a long time, in case of a few unsuccessful successions. Even though the potential points would be returned, some of them would be left in Black-Striped White Tiger.

"What a brilliant move! If you’re still so lousy after evolution, don’t blame me if I swap you out." Garen coldly steeled his resolve.

Finally, a full five seconds later, the Black-Striped White Tiger's icon slowly blurred, and Garen refocused his vision. If he didn’t observe it so keenly, it would have to be done the same as before; the accumulation of 7 points at a time, which was a much slower process. That was incomparable to this process, which could complete his goals in a single attempt.

He now understood that the icon displayed the rate of evolutionary success, which was the highest gene fragment success rate. It also showed the potential consumption point of its display, which also happened to be the point of least potential consumption.

The amount of potential points rose by more than 120 points before it finally stopped.

The Black-Striped White Tiger icon blurred for some time, and quickly cleared up.

As it returned to the properties pane, it sharply rose again.

"A failure." Garron spat, and this time, he did not see any need for other crystals.

He calculated that he’d failed once and it consumed thirty-five potential points. This was extremely wasteful to him.

However, in order to start a big activation, it would require more than 120 points. He thought for a while before trying again.

The second time the Black-Striped White Tiger icon blurred, it cleared up faster than before, but there were no changes. Another 35 potential points had been wasted.

Garen had wasted 70 potential points, leaving him with only 130 potential points.

He persisted and tried once more.

The icon absorbed a large number of potential points, it started to blur, and then …

It failed again.

Garen groaned; he was now in an extremely bad mood. Almost 100 potential points had been dumped, yet not even a ripple of water had changed, which worsened his increasing irritation towards Black-Striped White Tiger.

Originally he’d thought that he was talented and that this evolution would be viable. He had not expected that he’d have been overconfident in himself.

Black-Striped White Tiger had undergone multiple trials by researchers and they had not been able to find an evolutionary approach, what were the chances that he would discover an evolutionary approach so easily?

Seeing that he did not have enough points to attempt evolution again, Garen thought. "Since the Black-Striped White Tiger doesn’t work, then I’ll have to resort to another plan .. The replacement of the core totem, aside from five years buffer period, there has to be another way...."

Now that he’d learnt a lot on totem knowledge and research, he’d accumulated most of the preliminary knowledge for this area.

Black-Striped White Tiger was his failed choice, he’d spent so much potential points yet his attempts were all unsuccessful. Even if it did evolve into a Form 2 totem, how strong could it become? At most it could be comparable to a Form 3, but what about actually evolving it to Form 3?

After careful consideration, Garon decided to give up the Black-Striped White Tiger, realising that he’d been too sure of himself at the start.

"Contacting the core totem approach, aside from waiting for five years, there is the complete destruction of Black-Striped White Tiger." Garen narrowed his eyes and he had decided to replace the core totem.

Destroying the core totem was a very difficult decision.

Destroying just the totem’s light of the core totem would injure the totem users as well, and their spirit would be affected. If the core totem was completely destroyed, especially if the five years adaptation period had not completed, the totem user would be strongly impacted and their body’s integration with the core totem would be seriously traumatized.

Simply put, the current Garen would be gravely weakened by the core totem’s destruction. Totem users were often weak, and the magnitude of this would cause 10% of people to die.

"It’s the price I’ll pay for choosing wrongly."

Chapter 353: Core 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"However, the timing we’ll change it to and what will we change is still a problem," Garen mulled while he remained seated.

An impossible plan lingered in his mind, and whether this plan would succeed depended on the research conclusions observed in this period of time.

"We’ll wait for a bit and see. If that plan succeeds, it won’t matter if it’s the Black-Striped White Tiger or other cores, or whether there even is a core totem, because it will all be irrelevant."

***********

Five days later…

Alone within the carriage, Garen stood in front of the laboratory equipment, gently shaking a test tube filled with pale yellow liquid.

The midday sunlight shone in from the outside and gave the interior an ethereal glow.

Garen carefully returned the test tube to the test tube rack, pipetted a drop of red liquid from a second test tube and released it into the first one.

Shh…

Instantly, black smoke curled out of the test tube while an intoxicatingly sweet smell slowly saturated the air.

"Success…" Garen nodded in satisfaction. "The Dual Headed Salamander serum that I separated using the centrifuge can probably be ridden of its toxicity this time.

He picked up the pale yellow liquid-filled test tube and shook it in sync with the clock, as though his hand contained an unknown regular pattern.

Rolling up his sleeves, Garen exposed his right arm, picked up the syringe he had prepared earlier and equipped the needle. He began to suck the serum out of the test tube. Only when all of the pale yellow liquid had been sucked into the syringe did he take it out of the test tube, before flicking the needle tip.

Tch!

Garen’s left hand pressed down the syringe plunger steadily as he pierced the needle directly into his vein at his wrist.

The needle was inserted into his bloodstream through his vein slowly, and the Dual Headed Salamander’s serum sample flowed into Garen’s blood. After a few moments, a strong rejection reaction suddenly occurred within Garen’s body.

He tossed the syringe away and remained standing in his initial position, while all the blood vessels in his body began to swell up slightly.

On his neck, his veins swelled up endlessly, as green blood vessels began to slowly appear on his handsome face. Garen began to gasp for air, while beads of sweat started to cover his entire forehead.

"I’ve research the serums of various creatures, such as the Dual Headed Salamander’s serum, wild creatures’ serum, and the Petrifying White Dragon’s serum. The wild creature totem’s serum used to give off the strongest rejection until now, where that property now lies with the Silver Totem that I control. Moreover, out of my Silver Totems, the Petrifying White Dragon’s blood toxicity is too strong, which means I can only choose the Dual Headed Salamander… I’ve diluted its concentration levels greatly, and also got rid of some of the toxic proteins, so the remaining serum is very weak now, and I should be able to succeed."

Garen grinded his teeth, feeling as though an inferno was rampaging within him.

The blood inside his body began to flow faster as it tried to expel the injected serum, but Garen suppressed this natural instinct.

The Peak State Secret Technique allowed him to control his own blood flow and physiological responses perfectly. He suppressed his body’s rejection reaction, allowing the injected serum to enter his circulation system quickly.

The serum entered his blood and quickly became more diluted, and much lighter as well.

After more than ten minutes, Garen sighed in relief slowly, and opened his tightly shut eyes.

"The first step… went as expected, and it was a success." He clenched his fist and felt a tingling sensation throughout his whole body, a sign that the Dual Headed Salamander’s serum had already assimilated into the circulation system of his body. This potent serum was like an incomparable poison to the average person, but for a strong and healthy Secret Technique user like himself, the harm caused by the serum could be controlled to an extent.

"As long as this plan succeeds, I will become the core totem, and the core totem will be myself!" Garen glanced at his right hand, and unconsciously thought of the gigantic city troll that he had once seen.

He found out through his research that when silver creatures were controlled by the Derivator, the area that was actually being controlled was the brain. Meanwhile, the remaining areas would not be controlled at all. After conducting many experiments, he made a mad decision.

That mad decision was the test that he was attempting right now.

After stowing the equipment used for the injection and the other experiment tools securely, Garen slowly sat down at his favourite seat in the carriage. He closed his eyes to visualise the situation inside himself.

The blood continued to circulate inside him, and by now he could clearly feel that there were some signs of unknown changes happening inside his own body.

The blood vessels through which the serum had flowed through had begun giving off a layer of gentle light. This layer of light flashed softly and did not bring any attention to itself, making it barely noticeable.

Garen rested for a while until he felt that his body had returned to normal, before finally relaxing.

The human body is a balanced circulatory system in itself, but right now, he wanted to destroy this system, in order to build an even stronger circulation.

"Lord Garen, it’s time for lunch," Lala called from outside.

The carriage troop had rushed a five-day journey and faced constant hurdles along the way, forcing the cavalry team to be replaced three times. After the three aristocrats joined their entourage, the head of the cavalry team was switched to a form two totem user, showing the government’s priorities on this matter.

"I’m coming," Garen stood up and exited the carriage.

After that, another six days passed.

In this period of time, after Garen had successfully performed an experiment with the serum, he began to regularly inject himself with the Dual Headed Salamander’s serum once a day.

His body gradually began to accept the toxicity of the serum, and under Garen’s control, the rejection reactions stopped as well, showing that his body had naturally adapted to the serum, and had quickly balanced itself simultaneously.

Garen did not waste extra attention on matters regarding the core totem. Instead, he repeatedly conditioned his body. After all, the situation concerning the Black-Striped White Tiger could not be rushed, and required him to wait patiently.

As for the Kovitan kingdom, they had finally arrived.

**************

The wheels on the carriage spun smoothly.

Garen sat in the driver’s seat and looked towards the faraway lands in front of him while the evening sunlight began to bask on his body, gilding him in golden rays.

On Garen’s left shoulder perched an owl with ashen feathers. The owl was over half a meter long, and its sharp claws tightened and loosened around Garen’s arm from time to time whenever it shifted its lower body.

This owl was the totem of Hunting Group member Ansa, but was merely an insignificant form two totem. Since its form one body was the easiest low-level state to evolve, it was evolved to form two. However, it only had one ability, which was its night vision observation. Although all owls possessed night vision abilities, this owl’s ability was slightly stronger, allowing it to see places that were especially dark.

Even though this grey owl was not especially useful, its claws were still unusually sharp.

Garen allowed Ansa to let the owl out so that he could play with it. These lesser ability totems did not consume a large amount of points when released, and were excellent to use for training purposes. Ansa did not object to this at all.

At the back of the front carriage, Angel sat at the end, holding up one knee, and playing with a black dagger in her hand. She looked disinterestedly at Garen as he played with the grey-feathered owl.

This expression had been plastered on her face for two whole days already, because Garen was utterly boring.

No one noticed that while the owl had stuck its claws into Garen’s arm and perched there, there was not a hint of totem light emitting from his arm.

Garen teased the owl while observing the changes that had occurred in his body.

He got rid of his totem light and placed the Green Vine Sphere inside the carriage. Afterwards, he made sure that he was alone and that there were no other creatures close by, so that he could come into contact with the totem beast like this. His predicted result had been spot on.

His own body had already achieved its own totem light attributes.

He analysed this carefully, and realised that it was probably because of a certain reason.

"If a totem user is covered in their totem light for a long period of time, their own bodies will eventually go through the same situation as mine. They will produce a resistance towards the totem light. The only difference is that I used my Secret Technique and the serum to speed up the process. The short-term two-in-one process caused by Spiritualization was probably the key element that quickened this process. However, I’m not the same as them…"

Garen stroked the owl’s smooth but slightly hard feathers, while he drifted off into deep thought.

"Regarding my current body, when compared to a totem, it probably has strength comparable to a form one totem right now. This excludes the totem light, the Green Vine Sphere, the Troll Grip, and only refers to my flesh body."

Garen swayed his hand gently to shake off the owl, prompting it to fly away.

"The first step is easy, I just need to have the blood controlling ability, strong physical fitness, plus a refined and toxin-free serum, in order to achieve this level. However, the second step will be much more troublesome," Garen continued to ponder.

While researching the Crystal Derivator and the Resonance Stone, he had managed to improve the feasibility of his previous plan to near perfection. Regardless if it was the empowering measures of the Obscuro Society or the specialized principle vibration of the Resonance Stone, as long as those things were combined with Garen’s plethora of knowledge and theory systems from both Earth and the Secret Technique world, the plans of the first step would be completed without a hitch.

Garen had never really prioritized the nurturing of core totems from the beginning; he had always been preparing this plan. Now, he had finally finished the first step.

Currently, his core totem, the Black-Striped White Tiger was not working, and Garen had finally decided that he would give up on it, and focus on completing his plan instead.

The goal of this plan was the allow his flesh body to be transformed completely so that it would possess Silver Totem characteristics, while remaining uncontrollable by others. This thought came to him while constantly chatting with Leila, and had slowly expanded from there.

He tapped his skin lightly, and realised that his strength was now almost on par with the totem light of a form one totem, except that it was of a slightly weaker grade.

The supposed form one totems were actually creatures who were covered by a layer of totem light on the surface. Most of the form one totems were like that, except that the strength of the totem light was decided by the totem itself.

Regarding the newfound totem light traits that he had acquired, Garen was not surprised at all. The Obscuro Society research knowledge that Leila brought along, as well as the bits of Vanderman’s research information he had acquired from the mansion had all mentioned this kind of supposed occurrences.

These occurrences referred to the traits that allowed living creatures to carry the totem light. All of these originated from the empowering process. However, the empowering process was an abnormal process, and Vanderman chose to perform this process on foreign bodies to provide them to people.

Meanwhile, the direction that Garen chose to follow, was the one that all researchers had always hoped to succeed in.

Indeed, it was to use the totem power to strengthen one’s own body.

This required a sufficiently strong flesh body, and it was a shame that no one in this world, including the normal people and those who belonged to the Master-level, had a body that was as strong as his own.

Chapter 354: Core 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Through Garen’s personal experience, he realised that for this process, a strong body was necessary, but a person’s control of their own blood circulation was even more important.

During his conversations with Leila, he had often mentioned that using Totem Light to strengthen a person’s body was always the end goal that the Obscuro Society members were working hard to achieve. Unfortunately, it had never resulted in a positive conclusion, and the Silver Totems were merely the products of a surprise accident.

Sitting in the middle of the carriage trope, Garen was unable to keep his thoughts from drifting. His current research information was lacking, and he lacked the confidence to complete his plan and carry it out fully. He had to wait until he received Vanderman’s information and gained access to the Royal Library before he could grasp the theories properly. However, the necessary preparations for the second step were almost done, except…

Garen’s thoughts returned to his current state of reluctance and physical aching. If he really managed to complete the second step of the plan, he would be able to reach a new and unprecedented point of progress.

But this came at a cost, and it was something that he found difficult to accept.

The strongest part of the Dual Headed Salamander is its heart. It is parasitical, strong, and possesses great specialized abilities, making it the core source of its power. Its extremely powerful heart was the key for the second step of the plan that Garen was about to conduct. However, this would mean losing an army-type Form Three Totem subordinate.

The carriage trope travelled through a monotonous stretch of rolling hills that had bare, rocky mountains on both sides. Gravel and large, cracked stones that blocked the road were scattered all over the ground.

The chilling wind gusted throughout the hills with a whistling noise, and the blinding sunlight did nothing to increase the temperature.

The cavalry team rode on the left side of the troop, clad in thick grey cloaks. They rode with their bodies bent forward against the wind, while their cloaks made flapping noises as they billowed around their bodies.

The wind continued to whistle loudly, forcing the captain of the cavalry team to shout over the noise. However, as his voice was completely deafened by the sound of the wind, he decided to just ride towards Garen and make hand signals, pointing towards the front.

Garen glanced in the direction that the captain pointed towards, and rode towards the front. In the mountainous areas in front, ashen-coloured stone steps sloped upwards towards the mountain’s peak.

The road of stone steps was like an grey snake whose head could not be seen, climbing up the surface of the mountain quietly, slithering and twisting around it.

The stone steps ascended into a bank of misty clouds, making it impossible to see where they ended. Both sides of the stone steps were surrounded by dark grey trees and ashen stones. It was unbelievably steep, and there were deformed pine trees growing out of certain places.

The strong winds forced Garen to squint, and as he looked from left to right, he realised that he could not see the tops of any of the mountains on both sides, while bare grey rocks could be seen everywhere.

The captain of the cavalry team was a middle-aged woman emitting an aura of fearlessness. She wore a helmet and was clad in full-bodied red armor. She got off her horse and strided towards them.

"This road leads all the way up, and once you reach the peak, the Kingdom will be there. We’re at the fork now, and you’ll be able to see the main road in a bit, where there will be more people. Please be careful, all of you. I won’t escort you any further, as there are checkpoints up ahead." The cavalry team captain had to shout loudly to be heard clearly.

Garen nodded, signalling that he understood.

The captain continued, saying: "This road is a small trail that we patrol, and the fastest way to reach the Kingdom. You’ll need to pass through three more checkpoints along the way. Since you’ll need to pay a toll later, do you have gold leaves on you? If you don’t have any I can lend you a few."

"We have some," nodded Garen.

"That’s good. My name is Kenna, and I’m the 19th branch captain of the Kingdom’s third defense line. If you face any problems, feel free to look for me. I can assist you with any minor troubles you may face," said the captain loudly.

"Thank you very much." Garen understood that the captain was trying to build rapport with them. After all, Andel and the other aristocrats with him were definitely not impersonators, and if they were coming to the Kingdom at this time, it was assured that there were people in the Kingdom looking after them. Thus, it was a good opportunity to gain extra connections.

The cavalry team captain rode away on her horse and turned her team around to leave.

The carriage troop continued to move forwards while Garen gathered everyone together in the largest carriage.

He waited until everyone had arrived before closing the carriage door, and temporarily stopping the carriage against the wall for a break.

"What are you planning to do next?" Garen looked at Andel. "Are you going over to your uncle’s place?"

"Mm-hmm, Big Sis Hathaway and I both have relatives in the Kingdom; my uncle used to be the junior garrison squad leader. Meanwhile, Big Sis Hathaway’s younger sister works in the Kingdom’s archives," Andel replied calmly.

"You’re not coming with me?" Hathaway furrowed her eyebrows. She immediately forgot her unmarried status, before looking at Garen with the same gaze she reserved for her elders. "I’m going to visit the Royal Guards for a while. In the Kingdom, we all have allocated lodgings. Right now you’re not safe yet, so it’s better if you move together with us." She could tell that Garen was planning to leave again.

Garen smiled. "Father has estates in the Kingdom as well, except that they aren’t in the urban district areas. They’re in more remote places instead where the environment is much quieter, which suits me better. I’ve already made preparations to go live there." He currently possessed a large number of Silver Totems, and was too afraid to take them into the Kingdom. He spent the entire journey here hiding them from the patrol teams, and was now physically and mentally exhausted.

Both the Dual Headed Salamander and the Petrifying White Dragon were too large. As for the Deep Swamp Croc, if it wasn’t for the West Farm’s sparse population and light defenses, as well as the cavalry team’s lack of warning signals, its tracks would have been noticed a long time ago.

Fortunately, the members of the patrol team were neither high leveled Totem Users nor researchers and could not tell the difference between Silver Totems and Primitive Totems, which allowed them to muddle through. This way, Garen could just make his Totems hide their Totem Light to the best of their abilities.

He had Three Petrifying White Dragons and one Dual Headed Salamander with him, all of which were high leveled Totems, but only the Dual Headed Salamander was brought along. The rest were left in the outer line of defense, because he did not dare to bring them inside.

He was convinced that in a larger kingdom, the number of strong individuals who could recognize Silver Totems would definitely be higher. Thus, it was better for him to lie low.

As for the Totem Light on his body, he did not dare to cover it, and only covered the Black-Striped White Tiger’s Totem Light.

"Father left some things in his house in the Kingdom, so I’m going there to take a look. Angel and the others, what are you planning to do next?"

"I’m going to the War Guild to catch up on the news. I want to see if I can find some good quests to earn some nurturing resources," said Angel indifferently.

Meanwhile Leila, who was standing on the other side, quietly said: "I have relatives in the Kingdom but I haven’t seen them for years, so I don’t know if I’ll be able to find them."

"Regarding the special resources for nurturing, I’ve prepared them for you already, and right now all you need is a large quantity of normal resources. This is fine as well. Just take it as a form of training," Garen nodded in agreement. "As the heir to the Trejons family, I’ll need an audience with His Majesty the Emperor. This is the compulsory procedure for the local aristocratic lords. Also, I think I’ll be able to meet Prynne and the others soon."

"So we’ll be separating here?" Angel raised her eyebrows.

"Yes."

Garen took a pen and quickly jotted down his address on a piece of paper, tore it off and handed it to Angel, before writing another note and giving it to Hathaway.

"The Trejons family has a household manager in the Kingdom as well. Big Bro Maxilan, Big Sis Edney, please contact my household members in the Kingdom, and add up all the household assets and strength that the entire household currently possesses."

"No problem," Edney nodded assuredly.

Maxilan hesitated for a moment. "We don’t know whether news regarding the old man has travelled to the Kingdom. The two masters Barr and Baphje…"

"It probably hasn’t," Garen shook his head. "If not, we would not have been received with such courtesy even when we had yet to return. This is still the initial aristocratic special treatment. Meanwhile, whether or not the two masters have returned is still a problem. This situation should be left as it is for the time being, I will handle it."

He pondered for a moment. This trip to the Kingdom was done hurriedly with many restrictions, and while a large amount of his strength was not allowed to be brought inside, Garen still had a goal in mind.

The Kovitan Emperor, Avic Sisman would probably be stabbed during this period of time. The remaining Obscuro Society members in the Kovitan Empire had all gathered in the Kingdom, and the fact that they gave up on the Silver Totems power meant that they did not just come here for a relaxing holiday.

The stabbing resulted in collapse of the entire Kovitan Empire, and the successful blaming of the Black Prince. What Garen planned to do was to gain more profit from this misfortune.

Beckstone from the Terraflor Society absolutely loathed him, and once the Obscuro Society members realised that he was impersonating Jess, it would definitely lead to a huge problem. Right now these two giants were in a hostile state, and the Royal Alliance of Luminarists was Garen’s only place of belonging. Regardless of the identity of his father Vanderman in this current world, or the territory where his household had always stood, all were condemned to return to the Royal Alliance of Luminarists.

The current Royal Alliance of Luminarists was still extremely strong and had not reached a state of weakness, even in the confusion caused by various Aberration Creatures attacking them while they were unprepared. Garen was unclear about the bottom line of the Obscuro Society, but the enemy knew him well and that had caused a serious loss. The three departments were not a force to be reckoned with as strong individuals and experts were abundant. This great war had lasted a duration of many years, and if not for the awakening of Hellgate, the Obscuro Society would not have been able to overthrow the Royal Alliance of Luminarists.

Beckstone had decided to slowly go through many things to increase his growth during this period of time. What Garen planned to do was to release his power, a little bit at a time, during his growth in this era.

The Obscuro Society and Royal Alliance of Luminarists were both large powers in this era, and Beckstone’s growth was a result that was carefully planned by the Terraflor Society. Almost every step included an abundance of profit-seeking opportunities.

However, to reap these benefits required one to possess a significant amount of strength beforehand.

The Royal Alliance of Luminarists was naturally the best choice. Since they were going to split sooner or later, and Garen though that he might as well keep some of their strength for himself.

Once he had separated from the rest, Garen made his way to the mansion that Vanderman had left in the outskirts, and stayed there.

There had always been a caretaker looking after the mansion, and the maids had cleaned it until it was entirely spotless. This made it possible for him to live there immediately, saving him a lot of trouble.

The Kingdom was built as a large city situated on mountainous peaks. All of the buildings were dark grey and round, and built on the peaks of three tall mountains, forming three Kingdom cities.

The three cities depended on each other but were also independent, and in the middle was a lofty cliff covered in a sea of white clouds.

The three cities were connected by a chain bridge and stone bridge respectively on top of an ashen coloured hill, looking as though three floating buildings had been embedded into the mountain tops.

The mansion where Garen resided was outside the three cities, situated on a wasteland outside the entry point.

There were a total of twelve roads leading into the Kingdom, and this mansion that was called ‘Blue Bay’ was situated near one of the roads. It was inaccessible to the people in the surroundings, and situated at the bottom of the first empire of the three cities. Further down was a barren mountainous wall that shielded the back of the empire.

Chapter 355: Mad Plan 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Night time

In the first empire, a large cluster of dark grey buildings were lit up with countless lamps, as though the mountain’s peak was covered in an abundance of candles.

The area at the bottom with the dimmest candlelight was on top of a straight, lofty stone wall.

An ashen coloured mansion was embedded in the middle of the stone wall, and a small straight lane on the left was the only road that led to the outside world.

It looked like someone had dug a hole in the stone wall and built a manor in the empty space, with a balcony railing that could only be seen from the precipice.

A tall man with short blonde hair rested his hands on the railing and leaned on it as he stood on the balcony quietly, watching the sea of white fog below him. The gusting wind blew towards him, causing his hair to be mussed up continuously . The white pajamas he wore were also blown backwards.

He swirled the blue alcohol in his hands, and took a small sip.

"The request for an audience has been sent in, so I’ll just have to wait for His Majesty to summon me. The Green Vine Sphere in my hands cannot be kept for much longer, and the people from the Royal Alliance of Luminarists will definitely want to acquire it. The type of benefits that I will be able to obtain all depend on my gaining abilities now. Avic Sisman is a wise young leader, and ever since he ascended the throne, the Kovitan Empire has been flourishing, and it’s steadily becoming the strongest power in the continent. A person like this will definitely give me a favourable answer but if I don’t sort this out properly, the other researchers will be worried."

Garen drank his alcohol and pondered silently.

"I don’t know when Beckstone will arrive here, but I know that this is an important place where he has to reach. Historically, after the incident at Vanderman’s manor, he only arrived at the Kovitan Empire one year later. Sequentially, that huge incident occurred, but he did not get injured in that situation. This time, he’d been badly beaten up by me, so the timeline is not very clear anymore…"

Garen shook his cup again, and finished the remainder of his alcohol in one gulp. The taste of the icy grape wine swirled around his mouth and on his tongue, before sliding down his throat. It tasted light and very sweet, just like grape juice that had been spiked with some alcohol.

"The other thing would be my bodily changes."

Garen bowed his head and looked at his arms, noticing that the topmost layer of skin had began to give off a light blue shade.

Regarding the changes of his own body, Garen had been preparing himself for this for a long time, and had even calculated the times he used the Derivator. This kind of transformation was similar to the Obscuro Society’s Empowerment, except that it was considered as an Empowerment that was not controlled by a Derivator, and the process was also different.

Garen was going in the direction of optimizing his own body structure, while the Obscuro Society was trying to use the Totem Light to transform their own bodies directly. They were unable to face the rejection reaction, so they simply chose to prioritise the Totem Light in a process that involved outside contamination and virus attacks.

Meanwhile, Garen’s choice involved the main body absorbing the Totem Light, and it was a process that required his own body to produce an adaptive evolution in itself. Both of them had different natures.

The former required the ‘virus’ that the Derivator used to control Totem Light. The latter would control everything by themselves, however the difficulty would increase exponentially. In Garen’s case, his physical body was extremely powerful, and greatly exceeded the expectations of the researchers in this world.

The first step of the transformation gave Garen’s body the characteristics of Totem Light, but needed refinement to be steadier. The second step of the transformation required him to attempt to exceed his limits completely.

The reason why he could not increase his Attribution Points was due to his physical body reaching its limit, hence it was unable to increase any further. But what would happen if he increased the limits of his physical body? Would a newer, higher tier limit emerge?

That was Garen’s current plan.

If he exceeded the limit, he would be able to obtain the ability to use his Potential Points to increase his Attributes once again. He had found a way to carry out this step a long time ago, but he’d only been able to implement it thoroughly after Leila had passed on many of the Obscuro Society’s core skills to him.

The act of transforming himself into a Core Totem was a mad thought in itself. Countless talented Luminarists from the Obscuro Society had died while researching in this direction, causing many future researchers to avoid this area and conduct their research without using outside sources.

Their biggest hardship was that they lacked control over their own bodies, which led them to think of using Crystal Derivators as an exterior form of control.

However, Garen was different. The first step was a success, which made him certain that this was the direction and path that were the most suitable for him.

"The requirements for the second step of the transformation have all been met. The derivation theories have also been understood, so I can begin my experiments tonight," Garen released the cup in front of him lightly, and let it fall into the sea of white clouds. "I hope for the best."

He turned around and walked out of the balcony.

The wine cup plunged into the clouds before disappearing soundlessly.

Behind the balcony was a spacious hall, and the dim table lamp there swayed gently. It was a candle enclosed by a cylindrical white cloth, and each of the four walls were adorned with a similar lamp.

On the wooden floor, a long rectangular wooden desk was placed exactly in the center, with two wicker chairs arranged beside it. The table and chairs were the same shade of brown, with a tinge of red.

Garen sat down on one of the chairs and picked up a pile of manuscripts that had been placed on the table. He picked up a pen and began editing and checking them.

After checking for a while, he put away the manuscripts, got up and walked towards the wall on the right. There was a white cabinet placed high on the wall, with two used, black coffee cups balanced on top.

Garen shifted the coffee cups and began brushing against the walls, before his palm pressed against something softly.

Ka-chak.

A square switch sunk into the wall, and the entire wall slowly split along a ‘Z’-shaped crack and opened inwards, revealing a dark passageway.

The arched passageway sloped downwards towards the right into the darkness.

Garen picked up the manuscripts and walked inside as though he was going down spiral stairs that wound towards the right. He walked on for an unknown span of time.

Within the dark passageway, the area in front of him was unexpectedly illuminated by white light.

It was a half-opened metal door.

Garen walked towards the front of the metal door, pushed it open gently, and walked inside.

The door suddenly opened wide, revealing a large, round stone hall.

The stone hall appeared unusually rough, and the stone wall had uneven marks. The entire stone hall was the size of a football field with only a little light illuminating the area, revealing specks of white dust on the ashen stone wall.

Garen walked through the metal door, and the position where he now stood at happened to be at the extreme right corner. He looked at the center of the area from a distance and noticed a black shadow collapsed there, as its soft breathing noises echoed within the stone hall.

On the four walls, only four lamps had been lit up, and the light from them was only enough to light up the four corners of the large hall, making it abnormally dim.

He took one of the lamps down from the wall, held it in his hand, and walked towards the center of the hall briskly.

The air in the hall was cool and felt as though a light breeze was blowing through, bringing a pungent rotten smell with it.

Garen walked across the solid yet uneven floor towards the center of the stone hall, and stood in front of the black shadow.

As the lamp cast light upon the black shadow, half of its large body was exposed.

The two necks and heads of the Dual Headed Salamander came into view.

Its ten meter long body was prostrated on the ground as though in deep sleep, while saliva leaked from the corners of both its mouths. It was the source of the disgusting stench.

Garen placed the wall lamp on the floor, reached his hand out to knock on the Dual Headed Salamander but received no response.

"This dosage should be sufficient."

He murmured quietly, before walking towards the middle of the Salamander’s body, where various strange instruments had been arranged on the floor beside.

There was an oddly-shaped glass container and a square cabinet with a red dot that would light up occasionally. Furthermore, a large plate holding multiple purple crystal rods soaking in blood, and a surgical package containing various metal appliances.

Garen took a small sharp knife out of the surgical package and sterilised it with the flame of the lamp. With his other hand, he picked up a black towel that had been soaked in alcohol.

He walked towards the Dual Headed Salamander’s abdomen, used the towel to wipe its abdominal scales unceremoniously. He then discarded the towel and grasping the scalpel in both hands, he stabbed downwards abruptly.

Tch!!

The scalpel was unable to penetrate its scales, but managed to pierce into the Salamander’s skin.

Garen turned his head upwards and glanced at the Salamander, noticing that the giant beast had already opened its eyes and was glaring at him now with unblinking brown-yellow pupils.

"Don’t move," Garen commanded the Dual Headed Salamander, as he held the scalpel down and sliced through quickly.

With his abnormal strength, the blade made a tearing noise as it was tugged across, before it sliced through the Dual Headed Salamander’s abdomen and cut it open.

A meter-long wound was suddenly opened, exposing the blood-red coloured muscle within.

Garen switched to a longer, larger knife, sterilised it with alcohol and wiped it clean. Following that, he stabbed into the wound crudely once more.

Skree...

Finally, the Dual Headed Salamander could not hold back its cries anymore.

Garen separated the flesh towards the bottom with his meter long, large knife, and tore the flesh apart fully, exposing its steaming abdominal cavity.

Blood trickled down its scales and dripped on the floor, filling up one of the indentations in the floor like a creek before forming a small round puddle.

Garen discarded the large knife and used both of his hands to press against the corners of the wound, before looking into the abdominal cavity where it was pitch-black, as a pungent rotten stench continuously wafted out from inside.

He used both of his hands to tear and widen the wound, before picking up the lamp and entering its body.

The inside of its abdomen was an oval-shaped flesh cavity with inner walls of smooth white muscles covered in continuously moving blood vessels.

In the center, a large heart was thumping and beating continuously. This heart, which was larger than the size of an average person, was connected to a large amount of blood vessels that resembled red coloured spider webs of varying thicknesses.

Garen avoided the blood vessels carefully by stepping on the soft abdominal walls, and walked towards the heart.

The steamy, rotten smell from his surroundings assaulted his nose continuously, while Garen bent forwards and avoided two forearm-sized blood vessels that were blocking his path. He crawled towards the front of the heart.

He put the lamp down and took out a small black dagger. Holding it in his right hand, he sliced the corner of its heart open in one swift movement.

Tch!

A small piece of heart muscle detached from the large heart, together with a large pool of blood.

Garen quickly retrieved the chunk of heart muscle and immediately looked at the Dual Headed Salamander’s wound. He noticed that it was beginning to repair itself at a rate observable with the naked eye. This type of terrifying regenerative abilities seemed to have affected the abdominal wound as well, as both sides of the wound were beginning to meld together.

Garen heard a closing sound behind him, and was shocked for a moment, before he turned back hastily and exited the abdominal cavity.

A crashing sound was heard as he dived out of the wound, his entire body stained red by blood.

"Cough cough…" His mouth and nose were saturated with the rotten stench from the abdominal cavity. Garen took a few deep breaths and saw that the Dual Headed Salamander’s abdominal wounds had completely healed.

However, the Salamander’s spirits seemed down, and possibly due to the injuries its heart had just suffered; its eyelids were drooping and almost closed, and it lay there listlessly.

Garen had no time to care for it. Instead, he held the heart muscle carefully in his hands, and placed it into a small crystal bottle that he had prepared earlier.

"This bottle of nutritional fluids should be able to maintain it for a while."

He covered the bottle and shook the light yellow fluids inside. He could see that this piece of heart muscle contained a specialized frequency that allowed it to naturally beat even though it had been detached from the heart.

"The source of all the secrets regarding the Dual Headed Salamander’s can be found in its heart. Its heart possesses strong hematopoietic abilities, unlike most living creatures which rely on bone marrow to produce blood," said Garen as he finally understood.

Chapter 356: Mad Plan 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He waited patiently while the blood from the heart muscle seeped into the fluids in the bottle, dying the interior of the small bottle a dark red. Only then did he twist the bottle cap open, used a pair of forceps to retrieve the heart muscle and put it inside another bottle filled with the same type of fluids.

The Dual Headed Salamander’s heart muscle possessed extremely high vitality, and over time it remained bright red without any sign of decay.

After Garen transferred the heart muscle, he walked towards the other side of the room where a pile of equipment and apparatus had been placed in a corner, and picked up a small cage covered with black cloth.

Suddenly, piercing squeaks were roused from the cage.

The black cloth on top of the cage was pulled off to reveal more than ten aberration mice with ashen coloured fur.

All of these mice had red eyes, and were frantically running around in the cage without stopping. Two of the mice even jumped up and tried to bite Garen’s hand, but were obstructed by the cage each time.

Garen opened the small door of the cage and shot his right hand in quickly, catching one of the mice and closing the small door.

It was time to proceed with the second test of the plan.

He anesthetized the little grey mouse and sliced its abdominal cavity open, before removing a identically shaped and sized piece of flesh from both the Salamander’s heart muscle and the mouse’s heart. He planted the Salamander’s heart muscle carefully into the mouse’s heart muscle.

The experiment was proceeding smoothly, and the heart muscle had been successfully implanted.

Next, Garen sewed up the wound and placed the little grey mouse in a cage by itself for observation.

The mouse that received a new heart muscle implant now seemed like it was dying. After the anaesthetic effect wore off, it began moving again, but its four paws could not stop shaking. It was only able to crawl a few steps forward before its whole body began to shiver.

Garen used the purple crystal rod that had been dipped in a blended blood mixture to feed the mouse.

This was a medicinal blood concoction tailored for the rejection reaction, and it had to be fed using a crystal rod to avoid adverse side effects.

After drinking a few drops of the blood concoction, the mouse finally calmed down again.

Garen crouched down beside the cage and took out his notebook to begin recording his experiment observations.

Bang!!

Suddenly a loud noise rang from the cage, as the mouse within suddenly exploded into a cloud of bloody mist, while slivers of its flesh and bone splattered everywhere.

Garen put his pen down.

"The first experimental mouse, failed."

After that, he continued with the second mouse.

Another ‘bang’ sounded, and the cage was filled with blood and bits of flesh once again.

Garen’s expression was unchanging as he continued with the third mouse, proceeding with the same heart muscle transplant again.

This mouse turned out better. Because he’d reduced the transplanted amount, the mouse appeared to be entirely normal, except that it was more energetic. It looked like this was the effect of the heart muscle.

Garen recorded the current ratio.

A few days passed, and he continued to stay in the underground space that Vanderman had dug out under of the manor. Not only were there instruments and containers here, there were also various experiment manuscripts and recorded data.

Garen studied every single piece of information.

Vanderman Trejons was a genius, a genius in his field of research.

He invented various techniques that even Totem Users had never dreamed of, and most of them were techniques that the Obscuro Society had tried to acquire using other methods. Although he had yet to achieve the level of a Crystal Derivator, he was already very close

While Garen flipped through the manuscripts, not only did he find research on the Green Vine Sphere, he also found various techniques such as organ transplantation, in vitro reproduction, and Totem power separation, amongst others.

Using these manuscripts and research information helped Garen’s theoretical knowledge to increase rapidly. Regarding the entire research system, he had also gained a deeper understanding.

*****************

Pap.

Garen placed the cup of black tea on the table, picked up a manuscript and read it intently. The rows of experimental data were like sacred cheat codes in his eyes, and were incredibly precious to him.

The table in the hall was piled with tall stacks of manuscripts and books that all contained copious amounts of officially released analysis, tests, results, and discussions.

Garen was unsure of the amount of data he had processed in the past few days. All of these were still elementary level, and Vanderman’s manuscripts filled up three underground rooms in total, which were arranged by difficulty and date respectively, and progressively increased, indicating that his research constantly went deeper.

Currently, what Garen was studying was merely the manuscripts and books from the first room. Right now, he was only able to understand the things from the first room as well.

Hours and minutes ticked by, as ashen rays glimmered from the balcony. Lala, dressed in her white servant’s skirt, walked in and took the empty coffee and tea cups, before placing some ready-made snacks on an empty space near the manuscripts.

She glanced at the manuscripts on the table. The data was completely foreign to her, and although she recognized the individual words inside, she could no longer comprehend them once they were strung together with a variety of terminological pronouns, which seemed extremely deep to her.

"Your afternoon tea cakes and cherry milkshake are here."

Lala murmured the sentence, and as she had expected, did not receive a reply. She shook her head and turned around to walk out before noticing that the fireplace was full of charcoal ashes again. She went to dispose of them while she was still in the room, as it would be troublesome once the rubbish truck had left.

Garen flipped through the manuscripts and read them attentively, subconsciously picking up a piece of cake and shoving it into his mouth.

Suddenly, his gaze shifted towards a moving red dot.

A thought stirred in his head as he steered his gaze towards the bottom quickly and looked towards his Skill Pane.

‘Biological engineering: Elementary level. (Theoretical framework has been established completely, Three phases overall, elementary, intermediate, advanced)’

Regarding his initial beginner-level biological engineering, after he had read all the experiment information and a large number of subject books, it had finally advanced to the elementary level. However, this was not the most important part. The most important part was that his Overall Framework had finally been established, which would allow him to use his Potential Points to speed up the learning process.

Putting the manuscripts down, Garen glanced at the back of his hand, and noticed that pale red lines were beginning to tinge the skin there, resembling strawberry milk of the highest quality.

"The Salamander’s blood is finally showing some effects."

After a long period of injecting dragon’s blood serum, Garen felt that his body had finally shown some changes and was no longer the same as before. There were no changes in his Attribute Pane, but that may have been because his abilities had yet to achieve proper quantitative change levels.

Garen returned to his thoughts and let go of the manuscripts. He was unwilling to proceed with such slow-paced research, because his Overall Framework system had been fully established. His theories were also sufficient, and all he needed was a large amount of experimental practice.

On the contrary, his advanced mathematics had recently been upgraded and had exceeded his biological engineering greatly; he had achieved the highest level. Furthermore, while he was researching the Resonance Stone, Garen had also discovered one of its hidden key principles.

The research progress of the Resonance Stone had gone through a tremendous upgrade, and Garen seemed to have figured out the transfer model of the resonance. It felt like he’d awoken the same obsession as when he first learned the Secret Techniques; once more, he was enduring sleepless nights as he immersed himself into his research.

After acquiring Vanderman’s various techniques, Garen immediately began researching the organ transplant procedures of this world. Compared to the other techniques, organ transplantations and other techniques were extremely mature skills.

The experiments conducted on the little grey mice during these few days, made Garen reminisce to the time when he first entered university and conducted experiments on creatures in the experiment labs.

"Tonight will be the crucial time for my self experiment. If I’m not careful and a problem occurs, it will definitely cause severe injuries," mused Garen. He put down the manuscripts in his hands and picked up a pen to begin checking the plans on his paper again.

Transforming a physical body into a Totem worked when the dragon blood serum was in effect, but once the injections stopped, would return to its original state quickly. Garen had thought of this mad plan early on.

If he could possess a heart as strong as the Dual Headed Salamander, his limits could then be exceeded once again.

But how would he get such a strong heart?

After perusing various sources of information and experiment data, as well as the organ transplantation techniques he had received from Vanderman, a mad thought appeared in Garen’s mind.

He could transplant a strong creature’s organ into his own body and use the resonance principle to absorb the original organ’s energy vitality. It seemed like a viable decision.

Thus, he began to experiment on the Dual Headed Salamander’s heart muscles, transplanting it from time to time to note various side effects and dangerous reactions. He then prepared relieving medicines, and adjusting the different dosages.

The mouse that had received a successful heart muscle transplant now possessed the characteristics of Totem Light. Its body had also undergone changes of a certain degree, and was currently much stronger and more muscular than it was initially. Its strength and speed were now two times of that of a regular grey mouse.

This gave Garen some hope.

However, the mortality rate was still quite high, at about 70%. This was the main reason why he was hesitant to make his next move.

It was just as he’d predicted. The organ transplantation technique would produce a large amount of blood during the heart muscle transplantation. Meanwhile, as the nutrients were being absorbed, the produced blood would continuously mix into the test subject’s body.

The Dual Headed Salamander’s heart naturally possessed haemopoietic abilities, and this was the key reason why Garen had chosen it.

If the transplantation succeeded, Garen assumed that his own flesh body would possess abilities similar to a Totem, and the Totem Light would no longer be an obstacle to himself. Meanwhile, with the Dual Headed Salamander’s strong haemopoietic abilities, his physical limits would probably be increased slowly as well.

"But I’m not worried about the ‘if’s’, I’m only worried about the ‘what if’s’. Although I’m an ultimate Secret Technique User and fighter, my vitality has reached its limits, and I don’t know what I should do about this transplant surgery. To think of completing this heart and heart muscle transplant, the difficulty required…"

"Once I’ve been anaesthetized, I won’t be able to command anything. But if I don’t use anaesthesia, the tremendous pain will cause the blood in my body to flow faster, causing spasm reactions. Even if I was able to endure the pain of the surgery, a successful transplantation would still be difficult to achieve."

But once he succeeded, Garen inferred that similar to the outcome of the little grey mouse’s transplantation,he would be able to achieve a permanent Totem Light effect, which may exceed his physical limits at the same time.

By then, he would become a Core Totem himself, and the Core Totem would be him. Moreover, he would be able to use his Potential Points to increase his own Attributes. When that time came, minor side effects would not matter at all.

While Garen was hesitating, his gaze glanced slightly towards the shadow of Lala in the next room.

Lala had already been fully empowered by him, and two days ago he had tried to use his Potential Points to evolve Lala. Regretfully, Empowered Human Totems seemed to not have any abilities that could be evolved, and this cemented Garen’s thoughts to transplant his own organs.

"Is there a type of medicine that can be used to only make humans lose their sense of pain, without worrying about muscle spasms, increasing blood flow or other natural reactions?" Garen queried mentally.

Suddenly, both of his eyes gleamed, as though he had concocted an idea.

"I remember Reylan once mentioned that the Obscuro Society was also conducting these kinds of experiments. Some of the higher-leveled ones attempted to empower their own bodies, but as they were unable to trust others, decided to find a type of medicine that could get rid of their sense of pain instead, which would enable them to perform surgery on themselves. This type of medicine is commonly used on the battlefield, to make the soldiers forget their suffering, and should probably be found with the pharmacists in the Royal Alliance of Luminarists. The only problem is that it has stronger side effects, but it is definitely something that will yield good results. Maybe I could use the Green Vine Sphere to propose my requests at the same time."

Chapter 357: Audience and Surgery 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After thorough consideration, Garen devoured his dinner and requested Lala to enquire about His Majesty the Emperor’s reply. He then buried his head in the books and manuscripts once more, in which information about the practices and experiments had been recorded.

During the following days, the imperial palace officer stationed at the checkpoint still had no messages to relay.

Garen went to the capital to stroll around for a few rounds, but the streets remained eerily quiet except for a few passersby. The capital was governed by military law, and the entry and exit checkpoints all required troublesome licenses that had to be reviewed, because of materials that were under a unified management. The entire area was empty and quiet.

Until the sixth day.

Finally, the audit for an audience was accepted, and His Majesty the King had decided to summon him, but only for a duration of ten minutes.

***********************

Sitting within the white carriage passing through the checkpoint, Garen did not pull the curtains open. Instead, he sat in the middle of the carriage quietly, concentrating with his eyes closed.

The front and back of the carriage were accompanied by other carriages, and inside those carriages were other local aristocrats that were here to have an audience with the king just like himself. If it was not for the Green Vine Sphere, Garen assumed that as a local lord who had lost his power and influence, there was no way that he would have been able to receive an audience with the king.

He sat inside the carriage and carefully considered the exchanges and requests that he wanted to bring up during the audience with the king. Giving the Green Vine Sphere over was something that he had thought about properly before this. Out of the three emperors, the Kovitan Emperor had the strongest ambition and the best attitude. Hence, passing it to him would probably yield the highest profits.

However, there was another problem that would be troublesome to solve: the stabbing of the Kovitan Emperor by the Obscuro Society. Their actions would be successful this time, and he needed to warn His Majesty, but…

Warning him immediately was definitely out of the question; if an outsider aristocrat appeared out of the blue and told the king to his face that his wife was a spy without any proof, any sentence would be considered light in comparison to being convicted and jailed in a death sentence prison for false accusation.

Moreover, even if he managed to successfully uncover them, there would come a time when he would face the exposure of his own identity, and the Obscuro Society would definitely retaliate by going after his head. Even the Royal Alliance of Luminarists might not be able to protect him then.

He spent the entire journey pondering, and did not notice when the carriage had stopped. The sound of music echoed distantly behind him, and it sounded like it was coming from a violin or some other string-type instrument.

"You should get down now," the guard who was also the driver reminded him.

Garen pulled the carriage door open and jumped out of the carriage. He stood at the end of a quiet street, and in front of him stood a black, pencil shaped stone door. The large stone door was half opened, and on the inside, it lead to a spacious corridor that stretched into an open air garden far away.

A row of guards on duty stood to the left side of the corridor, and all of them were clad from head to toe in black armor, which made them look strong and solemn.

The music that Garen had heard earlier was coming from a large black fort on his left. It could still be heard faintly, from the area where the royal palace hall was located.

"Let’s go." The dispatched officer was a tall, handsome young man who wore a white wig on his head, and a red waistcoat over his white undershirt. He glanced past Garen, before turning around and walking out of the corridor first.

Garen noticed that the aristocrats who disembarked from the remaining two carriages did not stop at this entrance, but went to the other two entry points instead.

"Aren’t they coming to have an audience with His Majesty as well?"

The handsome man glanced at Garen.

"You should be honoured that His Majesty decided to summon only you today. The others were summoned by Her Royal Highness the Princess."

Garen nodded and followed the man as he walked through the corridor.

The two man walked briskly through the black corridor. The entire corridor was slightly more than seven meters tall and wide, and unusually broad, and as they walked across the smooth black stone floors, the sound of soft, crisp footsteps could be heard.

They passed through the corridor and walked into the front of the open air garden.

The garden was blooming with an abundance of fresh red, yellow, and white flowers. Most of them were white, and the white ones were giant flowers the size of washbasins. A group of girls in resplendent clothes were chatting noisily in the flower garden. No one knew what they were chatting about, but they seemed unusually happy. Some of the girls were even sitting on top of the giant washbasin sized white flowers, and it was amazing that none of them fell on the floor.

When the girls saw the handsome man who was leading the way, they waved at him enthusiastically, showing signs of familiarity.

The man answered them politely, and seemed to be unusually calm against the girls’ ambiguous gazes.

Garen followed behind him. Even though his current Acacia body was just as handsome, in comparison to the man, he was still somewhat lacking. He was immediately overlooked by the girls.

Compared to the man’s bright, eye-catching clothes, Garen’s grey robes were not worth looking at in the slightest.

After they passed through the flower garden, they ended up at another long cloister.

He did not know how far they’d walked before they arrived in front of a five meter tall black door.

"You can just wait here. About half an hour later, His Majesty will arrive. Remember, you have only ten minutes," reminded the handsome man briskly, before he turned around and left.

Garen did not mind. During this chaotic period, he could see that there were lots of people who wished to have an audience with the king.

He waited in front of the main door quietly. On the left side of the cloister stood guards in full-bodied black armor. Unlike the others, these guards were clad in armor that was significantly heavier and held black guns in their hands as they stood against the wall like sculptures.

About twenty minutes later, a well-built, middle-aged man walked over in long strides. He was wearing pure white tights with silver inserts in the borders, with a white cloak billowing behind him. He held a golden whip in his hand, as if he had just returned from horse riding.

Wherever he walked passed, all of the guards on duty would kneel down on one knee.

This man’s age was not older than thirty years, and a smile was present on his face. He had a mild-looking expression and a black beard covered his chin and connected to his sideburns, making it difficult to differentiate between his beard and his hair. His back was slightly hunched, but he walked steadily. His appearance was neither handsome nor particularly majestic, making him seem like a normal passerby that one would encounter on the streets.

Garen knelt down on one knee immediately. He had seen a black and white picture of the king before he arrived, and recognized that this man was the Kovitan Emperor Avic Sisman.

"Your Majesty," Garen bowed his head and looked away from the king’s face as a sign of courtesy.

King Avic was followed by a group of people who seemed like they were preparing to enter the room with him to discuss important matters.

"Come in."

Avic answered gently, and entered the main door that had been opened by the guards.

Garen stood up and followed him into the room.

Inside the brightly lit room, the walls were engraved with intricate and beautiful golden floral decorations, while a large floor-length painting was plastered against the wall on the opposite side of the main door. It was a painting of Avic standing on the palace balcony with a sword in his hand.

A few rows of yellow wooden sofas were arranged in an arc shape in the middle of the room. There were also two rectangular shaped bookshelves on the right, both of which were filled with various books with gold-rimmed borders.

"Have a seat." Avic seemed like a regular host who was attending to a guest in his house, as he pointed towards the sofa.

Garen looked at the other people and realised that none of them entered the room, except for Avic and himself who had just walked inside.

The people who had followed them bowed and curtsied outside the door, before closing the door carefully.

Only then did Garen sit down quietly, on Avic’s right hand side.

"The trust you have in the Royal Alliance of Luminarists and the Kovitan Empire signifies the trust in myself, Avic. Regarding the tragedy that befell Viscount Vanderman, when I heard of it, my heart grieved and I despaired. Your father contributed a great amount of effort and time into his research, but his treatment and attitudes towards the people were unnecessarily brutal at times. The impact caused by these incidents were horrifying. You understand what I mean, right?" Avic brought up the main subject immediately. He was not a Totem User and merely a normal person, but to be able to run such a vast empire meant that he naturally possessed his own expertise and abilities.

"I understand," Garen nodded. "Honestly, my requests are very simple. Iwish to visit the Royal Databank to find some information that I need. At the same time, I would like to request Your Majesty for access to the pharmacy to find some medicine that I need.

"Are you still a Form one Totem User?" Avic asked suddenly.

"Yes." Garen was surprised at Avic’s sudden change of topics, but he answered immediately anyway.

"Would you like a better Core Totem? Or a stronger Secondary Totem? You have an interest towards medicine, so you should go to the Secret Service. They have more content regarding those topics over there," replied Avic with a gentle smile.

"Secret Service?"

"That’s right. Although the interior strength of our Kovitan Empire may not be considered powerful, and may actually be extremely weak, it would not be difficult to allow you to become part of it. Inside, the pharmaceutical knowledge that you’re interested in and the various techniques… Well… I’ve heard that the moment you arrived at the capital, you spent all of your time holed up in your manor without going anywhere else, right? Well, that place has the techniques that you’re so interested about."

Garen hesitated. He was unclear about what the Secret Service was actually like, but he’d heard about the three departments of the Royal Alliance of Luminarists a long time ago. Each of these three departments were managed by different countries but they worked with each other, and their powers were intertwined, meaning that each country possessed varying amounts of power.

"Honestly, our Kovitan Empire sits at the most important position in the national departments. We are not considered weak in the Geometry Service, but since the Secret Service remains in the domain of Daniela, it is better for us not to infiltrate. You know as well that the three departments are represented by interest groups of aristocrats from various countries. Inside the Secret Service, Earl Senda is our only representative that possesses some influence."

"But even if I joined, it would not cause any effect, right?" Garen asked hesitantly.

"Of course it wouldn’t be just you alone. Nothing can be accomplished overnight, because everything needs a development process," Avic answered with a smile. "A research-type Forger joining their ranks would definitely be a huge support for Earl Senda."

"Your Majesty gives me too much credit," Garen quickly bowed his head humbly.

"Your father contributed an immense deal towards the Kovitan Empire, and by right I should be rewarding you greatly. However, the unfortunate part is that the news about the cruel experiments performed by the Trejons household have been spread everywhere," Avic answered softly. "Regarding your previous requests, I promise to grant all of them to you. As an extra reward, I will personally present you with the inheritance to nurture the Black Storm Doves. I hope you will not mind that."

"Black Storm Doves?!" Garen was shocked. This was the name of a Form three Totem, and this type of Form three Totem was one that he had heard of before. A Form three Totem that would be able to cause a storm, was a rare Form three Totem that did not prioritise body evolution, yet could cause strong tornadoes and were truly terrifying. This kind of inherited power was usually only passed down within royal families, and was extremely precious.

This inheritance could truly be something that he could depend on, and would help him rebuild an even more powerful Trejons household.

Garen was undeniably shocked by Avic’s generous gifts.

"Thank you very much, Your Majesty."

"Good, our time is almost over. There will be a masquerade party at the palace later. If you’re interested, you can go over to the etiquette officer and choose a mask. I need to go change my clothes now," Avic said while smiling.

Chapter 358: Audience and Surgery 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen quickly retrieved the Green Vine Sphere, and respectfully handed it in.

Avic took it.

"Not bad. Go and have a good rest. You can directly report to me if anything happens. Let me give you a warrant which would allow you to directly retrieve what I’ve promised from the Royal Treasury." He quickly wrote a warrant, tore it and passed it to Garen. He then bowed his head to examine the Green Vine Sphere.

Garen took the warrant, bowed, and walked out the study.

After exiting the study, he wiped beads of sweat off his forehead.

In the study, there were multiple strong, colossal energies lurking in the dark, forcing pressure on him. Once something was amiss, there was a possibility he would be instantly destroyed. He couldn’t assess the extent of strength of the energies, but they definitely were not below third form.

As this was a matter of national safety, it was natural that there were exceptional powers on guard.

This was the gathering point of the strongest forces throughout the whole of Kovitan, the capital. A large majority of the Obscuro Society’s generals were gathered here as well. The power of the Elemental Generals wouldn’t be considered very strong here.

Moreover, Garen did not bring along the three Petrifying White Dragons. They were too far away to help. If a skirmish happened, he certainly wouldn’t be able to escape.

This fact made him miss the martial arts world that he was previously in. Martial arts was real individual strength. It wouldn’t be diminished by being apart. A person’s strength also wouldn’t be heavily reduced because of damage to totems.

He shook his head as he enquired of the herald at the door, who respectfully brought him towards the royal treasury.

According to his plan, by combining Vanderman’s technique with part of Obscuro’s principle modification techniques, he would have to face a huge risk in the transplant process. Even if he could perfectly control blood flow and had immensely strong vitals, it wouldn’t make a difference. The other difficulty would be that in order to adapt thoroughly, he had to be on the same frequency with the Dual Headed Salamander.

Luckily, after Garen’s experimentation, he had preliminarily identified one of the most effective methods.

He followed the herald directly to the royal treasury. After the chemist in charge asked of Garen’s request, he was given twelve tubes of glory potions and a tube of light potion, which recovers large amounts of totem light.

All of these were crafted by top chemists and stored for over a hundred years, concentrating them for much stronger effects. Especially the light potion. There was a totem user who diluted the potion and distributed it to five hundred other totem users. All of them managed to fully recover their totem light within half a day.

Once a totem user’s totem light was exhausted, it would affect transfusion to the totem, causing injury to both the totem user and the totem. The light potion, which could quickly recover and repair totems, was considered a rare totem recovery method.

Garen was preparing for emergencies, where he could use it to quickly recover his totem light. If he got hurt, at least this could be used for self-preservation.

On the other hand, the glory potion was something that he wanted. It could completely lull all pains. It allowed people to soldier on without fear of life and death, or in other words, act as an advanced stimulant. As the glory potion did not have any side effects, it wouldn’t cause harm to people compared to other stimulants. Hence, it could be used again and again compared to low level stimulants.

After obtaining what he came for and a permit to enter the Royal Databank, Garen also received a black, hexagon insignia from Avic. He then took his leave from the palace.

As for the Black Storm Doves inheritance, after going through sorting, it would be sent to Garen’s manor within two days.

　　*********************

Under bright yellow light.

As he carefully applied a special type of grease on both of his hands, Garen looked at the death row inmate lying before him. This was already the fifteenth death row inmate to be used for his transplant experiments.

He’d used his family’s wealth to bribe the warden of Kingdom Prison to obtain the bodies of twenty death row inmates every month.

For the past two months, he’d consistently practiced with the Dual Head Salamander’s cardiac transplant, becoming more and more skilled at it. At the same time, he’d experimented on his own body by transplanting small amounts of myocardium into his body. However, this always triggered strong rejection from his body.

Under the effects of medication and the cleansing effect of Dragon Blood, Garen meditated with his martial arts and was gradually able to connect with the transplanted myocardium. He slowly understood the process that he had to go through.

As a whole, it gave him a newfound understanding towards the transplant procedures.

"A very successful surgery." Garen wiped off the disinfectant grease on his hands with a wet towel. "This is the fifth. If things go according to plan, my heart will be much stronger than the average person’s. I will become abnormally energetic and there might even be further changes to my body. All of the effects should be positive, since I have decent impurity cleaning skills."

Glancing at the inmate’s expanding and relaxing chest, it was certain that she was no longer in danger.

As he left the operating table, Garen habitually looked at his attribute pane.

There was a huge increase to his potential points. Within these couple of months, his potential points had gradually increased to more than than three hundred points. It was obviously caused by the Petrifying White Dragon’s relentless hunts. In the beginning, Garen still had interest in his increase in potential points, but soon he grew completely numb. The potential points were constantly increasing, but he had no place to use them.

The limits of the body determined that he couldn’t use them to level up his body. Yet at the same time, he felt it wasn’t worth it to use them to upgrade silver totems.

"What’s up boss?" As he left the lab, Garen saw a white-haired man waiting for him outside the door.

The man was called Komodo, initially a death row inmate. After the successful experiment, he decided to follow Garen as a token of thanks for giving him a second chance in life. Naturally, Garen did not fully trust an inmate’s loyalty, but he wasn’t too worried after the empowerment.

Komodo volunteered to be empowered, and currently acted as Garen’s right hand man in his underground lab.

Komodo had a strong physique. Compared to others who would be considered tall at 1.8 meters, he was two meters tall. The flesh all over his body was tanned, and he had scars everywhere. His right wrist was chopped off in a battle, and currently in its place was a retractable alloy blade.

"Very successful. This inmate is really strong. Although she’s a female, you can rarely find such a strong body even among men. She might be on par with you." As Garen briefly explained, he strode towards the biggest underground cave.

Vanderman’s lab was huge. This was the originally the Kingdom’s air raid shelter, but it had been deserted. The lab only occupied a corner of the vast underground air raid shelter.

"This is the third success this month. Boss, you are getting more and more skilled." Komodo smiled. "But Boss, am I really able to injure the monsters out there?" There was doubt in him.

"Of course." Garen turned a corner. "Didn’t you try?"

"No."

"Go try it when you’re free. After i finish with my experimentations, I’ll appeal for your pardon. I am a nobleman. I should have the authority to keep the lives of a few inmates." Garen promised.

"Thank you boss!!" Komodo was delighted.

"Have you prepared the various equipments?"

"Yes, it is ready. The nutrient pool has been refilled as well. This time I switched to the biggest one. Miss Lala has been complaining that the expenditures have been too huge. The family’s finances are becoming a little tight." Komodo replied immediately.

"Let’s officially begin tonight." Garen pushed open the door of the biggest underground cave, and entered.

Komodo followed behind. Right in front of their eyes was a gigantic creature crouching in the biggest nutrient pool.

The giant salamander had two heads and his huge body was like a hill. It quietly laid in the pool, and every breath created a mild breeze in the cave.

Although he has seen the creature multiple times, Komodo’s legs still shook. Although he was still delighted by the promise, he still couldn’t resist the immense threat of the creature.

Komodo consciously went to check the oil level of the lamp on the wall, as an opportunity to keep a distance from the creature.

Garen went towards the dual headed salamander instead and raised his head to look at the giant creature.

"Tonight might be a new beginning for me.." Garen gently stroked the salamander’s skin.

He had been relentlessly pursuing the combination of martial arts and totems. From the ancient notes about Endor and his baffling arrival at this world, there was definitely some form of connection between martial arts and totems.

He took out his pocket watch and looked at the time 4:23pm. 　

He left the pocket watch on the table. Garen immersed his two hands into white disinfectant liquid. The liquid was like boiling soup but Garen’s expression remained steady.

He removed his hands when they turned slightly red, then dried his hands. He diluted the glory potion according to proportion.

The surgery wasn’t difficult. The difficult part was controlling blood flow after the transplant. Immense accuracy was required. Even for an apex martial artist like Garen, he had to put in a lot of effort for the transplant.

The person receiving the transplant had to have strong endurance. He had to endure pain that would kill a normal human. Moreover, without precise control of blood flow, the most the inmates could obtain from a successful experiment was a stronger physique and totem-natured change in strength. It wouldn’t have much change on their actual power.

For normal people it might be worthless. But for Garen, with the ability to increase his body’s limit through potential points in addition to having the skills to control the resonance stone, he could definitely surpass the limits of his body.

Moreover by relying on the pinnacle of martial arts, he had grasped the principles of the resonance stone. He estimated that even the Obscuro Society’s people could not reach this level in resonance stone techniques.

Martial artists really had strong senses.

According to procedures, Garen started to adjust his blood flow and body state, then closed his eyes to rest.

Once the surgery was a success, the array of martial arts from the previous world would be of use. At the same time, a new path would be opened.

He recalled the legends of the warlocks he had heard of in the previous world. Although the warlocks of the fairy tales appeared exorbitantly strong, a huge chunk of them could be distorted as the stories were passed on. But there were some among them that seemed to possess the power of totem users.

Thinking about it now, the martial art world and the totem world seemed to have an association with each other.

"Tonight will determine our success…"

Tonight’s transplant would determine whether martial arts and totems could combine perfectly.

Chapter 359: Transplant 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kovitan’s Palace

King Avic sat sideways on the throne with his face rested on one hand, as he looked at the reporting ministers and noblemen. Boredom and disinterest was written all over his face.

"... to date, there is a severe resource shortage throughout the empire. There is no food supply and we are relying on the surrounding warehouses. This will not last for long. I suggest building terraces in the surrounding hills. If we do not execute this plan as soon as possible, we will face severe consequences." The agriculture minister was a short white-bearded man. Although he had a wrinkled figure, his voice was full of energy.

"I oppose!" The military minister stood up to speak. He was a middle-aged fierce looking man. "The uses of weaponry totems are incredibly varied. If we continue like that, we will have depleted all our stored resources within a few years. Our primary mission should be forming squads to secure new resource points. Not doing that will cause us to be unable to withstand the attacks of monsters and all will be for naught."

"Is there a possibility to take the flesh of the foreign creatures as meat?" The industrial minister suggested. "I’ve heard that there were totem users who directly ate the flesh of the creatures, but there weren’t any problems."

"We can give this a shot." Avic tapped the armrest of his throne with his fingers. "Health department, do some tests and get back to me with the results within a month."

"Yes, your majesty." The health minister bowed his head.

"Your majesty, Dragonfield Black Prince will be arriving at the kingdom’s capital in two months. What level of protocol should we greet him with?" The protocol minister asked.

"Protocol?" Avic furrowed his brows. "The black prince established Dragonfield. In this era of chaos, his position should be only slightly weaker than mine. Welcoming him excessively would be detrimental, but it wouldn’t be polite to take him lightly as well. Greet him according to the Foreign Prince Protocol. As long as has not ascended the throne, he is not the King of Dragonfield."

He paused. "The Black Prince’s visit will heavily facilitate the alliance between Dragonfield and Kovitan. Although Dragonwell used to be Kovitan’s vassal state, it is different now. Ministers, please be attentive towards your behavior."

Following after that were the daily trivial discussions. There were some faults with the kingdom’s drainage system which required funding. The repair of the air defence network totem needed more resources and workers. There were a few children of nobles who got into fights on the streets and what should be done about it.

The more Avic listened, the more he frowned. Gazing at the chaotic meeting hall, he took up his golden scepter beside the throne, and exited through the right.

　　********************

Garen sat to the side of the dual headed salamander. He set up a table and a chair beside the nutrient pool. As he was waiting for time to pass, he was organizing the reports on his desk.

The flickering of light from the lampshade caused the shadows on his face to shake.

He carefully looked at the asset statistics in his hand.

Out of all of Trejon household’s foreign businesses and their two manors, only twelve farms were still operating. The majority of their wineries, bands and mines were unable to operate because of the creatures. As they were located out of West Farm’s line of defense, giving them up was the only option.

In the kingdom, other than the manor he was staying in, there were three other bungalows and a long closed down totem repair shop.

Because of his recent heavy spending, he sold off some of his family businesses. Two out of the three bungalows were sold, leaving only one bungalow and the totem repair shop, which was not worth much.

Military resources were currently being heavily controlled by the government. Hence, nothing could be sold in the shop and its only value was the land.

Lala, who acted as a maid, was the one governing the assets. She made everything concise and neat.

Not only were the assets were in a depressing state, the family guard too was dismal.

Maxilan and Edney led the family guard. The household initially had two second form totem users and fifteen first form totem users. These forces had independently nurtured over the years. The battle at Vanderman’s manor had heavily depleted the forces; some of them had ran away, while only a minority who felt a sense of belonging to the Trejon’s household had remained.

Their current forces were only made up of ten first form totem users. Led by Maxilan and Edney respectively, they took part in the kingdom’s defence circle patrol mission for some hard-earned money. Only on the weekends did they return to the manor to report to Garen.

Instead, it was the Hunting Group who managed to enlist in different departments in the war guild once they reached the capital. Because of their alliance with Garen, they became the biggest influence in the Trejon’s household apart from Garen.

Garen placed the family status reports at a side, and finally looked at the two invitations at the bottom. The two invitations were from Earl Baxy and Viscount Lavel.

The Trejon’s household had a certain level of network and kinship in the capital. The noblemen often had abnormally complicated marriage relationships. Earl Baxy’s wife was Vanderman’s cousin’s sister’s daughter. One of their daughters had married to Vanderman, becoming his second wife. Both parties maintained a close relationship.

Viscount Lavel was Vanderman’s brother’s adopted son, who’d managed to climb the social ladder with the family’s support. His roots were in the Royal Luminarist Academy, where he was one of the vice chancellors. There were rumors about his intimacy with the Royal family’s third princess, and there would be a wedding soon. 　

"These are the typical nobleman households." Garen’s head hurt as he thought about these family relationships. The nobleman circle was not big. In order to preserve the noble bloodline, marriages would often be between one another, or with royalty of other kingdoms. Because of this, there would be relationships between noblemen everywhere, like a spider web. By tracing the Trejon’s bloodline, there could even be a connection with the king.

"Complicated network." Garen thought for a moment, and threw the invitation aside.

After thoroughly clarifying all the matters, Garen lifted his watch and looked at the time, 5:12pm.

Calmly, he stood up and walked towards the edge of the nutrient pool. He crouched down and tapped lightly.

Piak!

With a crisp sound, a stone on the edge of the pool slowly lit up.

At the same time, a total four white lights coming from four stones illuminated around the round-shaped nutrient pool.

In a flash, straight white beams shot out from the tip of the rocks. They met in the air above the pool and merged into a single point.

The beams fluctuated slightly, letting out a hissing electrical sound, and illuminated the whole underground cave.

The dual headed salamander opened its eyes and looked up. The glaring white light narrowed its eyes. It moved its body slightly, then returned to its calm state.

He laid out the transplant apparatus on the table and started to use disinfectant grease to sterilize them. Then he got ready the diluted glory potion and anti-inflammatory drugs, gauze, bandages, suture needles and other instruments that may be of use.

The preparations were complete.

With his eyes shut, he stood still on the ground. As he meditated, he slowly operated his Divine Statue Technique. According to the subtle sense of the resonance stone, he carefully sensed the dual headed salamander’s frequency.

In the process of sensing the resonance stone, Garen realized that in fact all beings, including all plants and humans, had their own unique resonance frequency. Only by finding that resonance frequency could numerous unimaginable key functions be realized.

In the past few days, he had sensed many times, finally able to faintly grasp the dual headed salamander’s unique frequency. This was the frequency of the vibration of its life force. The dual head salamander’s life force vibration seemed to be in sync with its heartbeat. But in fact, every heartbeat was completely different from the subtle vibrations. One beat contains thirty five totally different vibration frequencies.

These thirty five frequencies combined to form a unified vibration. There was no interference between the frequencies. All of them were independently clear and distinct.

Some of the vibrations had big frequencies, close to the rate of a heartbeat. Some of them were small, they could beat up to a thousand times in one heartbeat.

As Garen quietly sensed the thirty five different vibrations, he gradually stopped operating the Divine Statue Technique. After a moment, he abruptly opened his eyes.

Taking the surgical band from the table, he plugged in the necessary surgical apparatus. He strapped the band to his arm by winding a few loops. Garen directly walked into the surgical pool which was surrounded by white beams.

At the same time in the underground cave, Komodo quickly turned and leave according to Garen’s previous orders. If he continue to stayed there, there might be danger. Furthermore, as there were preset defence tactics, there was no need for an outsider’s protection.

He bowed towards Garen’s direction from a distance, then quickly turned and left the underground cave.

Garen drew his surgical knife and carved a deep wound on the dual headed salamander’s abdomen. Scarlet blood instantly flowed out from the wound and dripped into the nutrient pool. It dissolved into the white nutrient liquid.

Shriekk!!

Garen applied force, slashing the knife from top to bottom, opening a wound at the salamander’s abdomen. The length of the wound was more than a man’s height.

He put down the knife and held the edge of the wounds with both his hands, and gave it a fierce tug. The wound completely tore open and he squeezed his whole body in.

In the fishy and stuffy salamander belly, the huge, heavy beating sound of the heart filled his ears. The sound of beating was abnormally muted.

Garen passed the arteries and veins with familiarity, and once again arrived at the heart, which was about a man’s height.

He withdrew a tube of diluted glory potion from his surgical band. After filling a syringe with it, he injected it into the salamander’s arteries.

He then withdrew another tube, and injected it into his carotid artery.

As he injected the cool potion into his neck, there was a faint sense of excitement in Garen’s heart. It was as if his senses were abnormally alert, much more than usual.

He felt numbness spreading throughout his body. It was as if there was a thick layer of stratum corneum on his skin. He completely lost his sense of touch.

Garen stood still for a couple of minutes, waiting for the effects of the drug to kick in.

After he was sure that the drug was in full effect, he then took up the surgical knife and made gentle cuts on the surface of the salamander’s heart.

A dual headed salamander’s heart had unique hematopoietic abilities. It was a unique, machine-like biological tissue, which was a humongous source of life, endurance and strength for the salamander’s gigantic body.

Garen carefully removed some flesh on the surface of the heart. The removed flesh was around the size of a man’s head.

Chapter 360: Transplant 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He slowly released a wave of white gold aura, carefully sensing the structure of the dual headed salamander’s heart. Then he started to make tiny carvings on the piece of flesh with a small knife.

Only the dual headed salamander’s powerful life force and strong regenerative abilities helped it to withstand such severe damage. Any other being would have died at its first heart injury.

The knife carefully carved at the entrance and exits of the arteries and veins. For some of the internal places that couldn’t be contacted, he applied force with his martial arts to empty the flesh.

Garen closed his eyes, not looking at the piece of flesh in his hand. He relied on the white gold aura for sensing and to be his eyes for the surgery.

Heavy amounts of blood flowed through his fingers, due to large amounts of torn flesh stuck between them. As time passed by, some of the blood coagulated on the surface of his hands, forming a thick layer of scab.

Garen wasn’t sure if the plan would succeed. He intended to create a smaller heart with the tissues of the dual headed salamander’s heart, then transplant it into his body. Without doubt, it was a whimsical thought.

The Obscuro Society had provided the guidance in technique, while martial arts and the resonance stone had cleared the path forward.

After multiple experimentations on humans and animals, it was clear to Garen that even without following the resonance steps, there was still a chance of survival after the transplant. Without a doubt, that was his biggest safety net.

The heart in his hand was gradually coming into form.

Shortly, Garen’s hands gradually stopped moving. He took out a tube of ointment and applied a uniform layer on the inside and outside of the formed heart. This ointment stopped the growth of wounds. He’d experimented many times with it previously and the effect was decent. A few experiments on the inmates had succeeded because of the ointment.

As the heart stopped showing signs of regeneration, Garen crossed his legs and sat down. He took off the surgical band and placed it on the floor. He had an astonishing degree of control of his body’s blood flow.

With a shock throughout his body, the clothes on his body tore into shreds and flew apart.

Garen sat naked on the flesh-like ground. He lifted the surgical knife with one hand and plunged it into his chest.

He followed his ribline and slit across his chest. A bloody wound tore open across his chest, like a bloody, ferocious mouth.

No blood was flowing out. His elite-level martial arts and white gold aura was controlling his arteries, preventing blood from leaking out.

At the instant the wound was slit open, the blood on the surface of the wound quickly coagulated, plugging the wound.

As carefully visualized internally, he placed the salamander’s heart into the right side of his chest, symmetrical to his original heart.

Next was the vascular graft, quickly moving every blood vessel from the original heart to the new one.

Garen’s was incredibly strong in martial arts. His trained body could be commanded easily. Connecting his heart was much easier than the rest.

Under the effects of the glory potion, there was no sense of pain. Garen skillfully began to move the blood vessels. After moving an artery, he would move the corresponding veins. Then, he would control his blood flow to start circulating through the newly stitched blood vessels.

Due to his superhuman regenerative abilities, every stitched blood vessel would quickly condense together. 　　

The process was much easier than Garen expected. The Divine Statue Technique’s self healing abilities allowed him to easily complete the stitching perfectly.

Every blood vessel from the original heart was moved over to connect to the new heart.

Garen was in deep focus, as though he was performing surgery on others instead. Without looking at his two hands, he quickly and accurately made stitches on his chest.

Not even a drop of blood from his body had been wasted.

As minutes and seconds passed, beads of sweat gradually appeared on Garen’s forehead. His hands were also becoming more skillful and fast.

The heart wasn’t linked to many blood vessels - only eight of them. But due to the structural change, it affected the smaller arterioles and venules. Some of them weren’t long enough and he had to move the salamander’s heart to compromise.

As the transplant progressed, the position of the salamander’s heart gradually moved towards the left side of his chest, closing in on the original heart.

As the beads of sweat on his face increased, some of them trickled down his temple.

The fifteen minutes that had passed wasn’t a long time, but the transplant felt like years.

Finally, Garen lightly stitched the last vein. The salamander’s heart had completely replaced the original heart at the left thoracic cavity.

However, there were no signs of beating. The body’s blood flow was completely reliant on Garen’s martial arts techniques, and his life force was depleting.

For an average person, once the heart stops beating, he would go into shock and the brain would stagnate, causing him to lose his sanity. But Garen was a zenith-level martial artist, hence he could rely on his aura that he accumulated daily to promote blood flow. In the meantime, he squeezed the salamander’s heart lightly to imitate the pumping of the heart.

It heavily reduced the depletion of aura. However, it was still depleting quickly.

After Garen’s multiple surgeries on the inmates, he knew that this was the most important stage. He quickly raised his head and slit opened a passage on the salamander’s gigantic heart with his surgical knife. His whole body then entered into the heart.

The passage quickly stitched back together, leaving only a small trickle of blood.

As he immersed himself into the dragon’s blood, an incredibly strong fishy smell surrounded his skin and body from all sides.

If he hadn’t been injecting himself with dragon blood serum for a long time and had formed some resistance, he would’ve been poisoned to death in a short while.

The salamander’s heart beat non stop. The loud, continuous beat indicated its strong life force.

The strong beat caused the heart in Garen’s chest to mildly beat, similar to its rhythm.

In the atrium and ventricle of the heart, blood flowed in and out, creating a huge spiral. It caught Garen’s body and held him in the center.

The salamander’s heart structure was totally different from a man’s heart. It had one atrium on the left and one ventricle on the right, forming two equally large spaces. It was like two balls that were closed to each other.

Garen curled his body as he was suspended in the center of the heart.

He could only see red as he opened his eyes. His nose and mouth were filled with blood, preventing him from breathing.

According to the plan, Garen quietly meditated, sensing the resonance of the dual headed salamander’s life force. He controlled the strength of his totem and started to imitate the dual headed salamander’s resonance frequency.

As the salamander’s heart agitated him, Garen barely held onto his senses. As he was immersed in the resonance frequency, he had to arrive at the same frequency in order to activate the transplanted heart.

Under the same frequency, high energy units would transfer energy to low energy units. This was a unique form of energy transfer. Garen previously learnt this on Earth, but he applied on his current world to transfer energy.

Whether it’s the salamander’s heart or the resonance stone’s nest, both seemed to be operating on this principle. It was only their frequency that was abnormally complicated.

Using his strong martial arts, Garen accurately manipulated his blood flow and totem force to slowly beat in time with the salamander’s heart.

As time passed by, Garen’s body was fully coated in blood.

He closed off his five senses, completely forgetting the flow of time as he immersed himself completely into the resonance frequency.

This form of resonance frequency was undoubtedly as difficult as a miracle to the totem users of this world. However, to Garen who has reached the zenith of martial arts, it was merely about controlling his own body. Martial artists had stepped onto this field while they controlled the usage of forces a long time ago. This resonance was just relatively harder.

Gradually, he fell into a deep state of semi-consciousness. The dragon blood continuously replenished him with nutrients and oxygen, while also taking away metabolic waste.

Garen was like a foetus in the womb, sinky slowly towards the deepest realm of consciousness as he synchronized with the resonance. He lost track of time. One hour passed, then two hours, five hours, one day, two days….

Garen was completely unaware until the resonance became a natural habit. It was initially the dragon heart which propelled the resonance, but now he’d finally achieved complete harmony with it.

He completely entered a deep state of slumber.

　　**********

The sky was blood red.

Garen stood alone on the edge of a barren cliff. Below was a deserted city with broken walls and old towers with no sign of population. A layer of mist blanketed the silent city.

"Sheesh!!!!"

Garen raised his head and opened his mouth to let out a deafening scream.

He realized he was no longer human, but a gigantic, black-scaled dual headed salamander.

He couldn’t control his body. It was as though he merely a bystander within in the dual headed salamander’s body, observing the surroundings.

Between the two heads, only one had vision. The other was merely decor.

The dual headed salamander’s body wouldn’t have been considered huge. At only three metres tall, it could be only considered as a youth.

He turned around and stomped his feet on the ground as he walked towards the back of the cliff.

Behind the cliff was a black building. It was completely empty, without even a shadow within. The cold wind gusting through the holes of the building made some whimpering noises.

Among the buildings, a tall black clock tower stood silently in the middle of the dead town.

The dual headed salamander stared at the clock tower. It was in extreme hunger. Hunger pangs continuously arose from its stomach, clouding its mind.

"Food...food…" Garen felt that this was the only single thought in the dual headed salamander’s mind. It kept on repeating over and over again.

Step by step, it heavily plodded towards the back of the cliff. It was heading towards the black city on the slope.

Garen’s thinking ability felt numbed. All he could do was silently stare through the dual headed salamander’s vision.

It squeezed into a huge black metal door in the city. The door was carved with fine patterns, and had two heavy metal rings.

Entering the black metal door, there was a quiet, black plaza right in front. On the right hand side was a leafless tree. Its countless leafless branches stretched out into the sky, looking dry and desperate.

The dual headed salamander hungrily walked forward until it reached the foot of the tree. It sniffed at the trunk. The trunk gave off a dry and liquidless smell.

It was an unusual feeling. Garen felt that the salamander could actually smell the smell of water.

The salamander finally could not control itself. It reached over and landed a big bite on the trunk of the tree.

Crack.

Bitter. Waterless. After reluctantly swallowing it, the salamander felt even hungrier.

He gave up on the tree and walked towards the buildings, which looked like a temple area. They were all in black without any colors. Under the faint red sunlight, it gave off a strange feeling.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Suddenly, heavy footsteps were heard from outside.

It was as if a gigantic creature was walking around in the temple area.

They heavy footsteps could be heard from thousands of metres away.

The dual headed salamander fearfully stopped. It hesitated on the plaza. It wanted to enter but didn’t dare to move forward.

However, it could no longer hold in its hunger. He raised his head and looked at the giant, ten-metre tall black metal door with black-reddish rust stains. One of its heads strongly pushed opened the door.

Creak….

Whooo….

Garen abruptly opened his eyes.

The only thing he could see was red. He had finally regained consciousness.

Chapter 361: Success 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He still lay in the blood of the dual headed salamander. He was floating in the blood between the arteries and veins; two different levels of oxygenated blood that looked as though they were separated by a thin invisible film. As arterial blood flowed through this area, it became venous blood.

Garen released a white golden aura, and felt his heart rate slowly synchronising with that of the dual headed salamander, beating at the same frequency. A strange sense of affection and intimacy was birthed.

It was as though there was an unusual connection between him and the dual headed salamander.

His own heart grew stronger in the resonance of their heartbeat frequency. As his heart continuously beat with the help of the salamander’s heart, an unknown energy surged to his heart, causing the initially rejected transplanted heart to slowly come to life.

Garen released an aura, and sensed the foreign blood flowing around him. The vital energy and blood flowed from the heart of the dual headed salamander and circulated all throughout its body. An extremely complicated and detailed map of the blood vessels appeared in his mind.

He closed his eyes again. His heart had not been completely activated yet, and still needed to rely on the continuous resonance of the salamander’s heartbeat. Not only that, as the blood pumping out of his new heart was a combination of the salamander’s blood and his own merged as one, an adaptation process within his own body was required.

Garen carefully examined his own body. Once there was a reaction in any part of the body, he would immediately employ the secret technique to make adjustments throughout his body.

This process was extremely dangerous. Different from the simple surgical procedures done on the prisoners previously, Garen needed to be on alert for any signs of rejection while keeping up the resonance of the heartbeat.

If he were to falter at any time, it could result in his immediate death.

Although he had already predicted this step through simulation modeling, he was only aware of how critical and difficult it truly was after he had personally reached this stage. It wasn’t like what he had previously deduced.

If a rejection occurred, it would affect the resonance achieved by both hearts beating in sync. If not resolved immediately, Garen would suffer from the double blow of hypoxia and bodily reaction; it would either end up with him suffocating to death or death due to the disturbance of vital energy and blood.

In the underground caverns.

The dual headed salamander lay in nutrient fluid that was slightly reddened. It’s eyes were slightly closed. The creature’s body gave off a feeling as if it was way past it’s prime; it seemed to have aged.

At the top of its body, four white beams of light converged into a white light ball, evenly covering the body with white light. Even so, the scales on the salamander dulled slowly, losing the sheen it once had.

Sssss…

The dual headed salamander let out a long breath of air, opened its eyes to quickly survey its surroundings, and continued to close them.

At the edge of the nutrient pool, Komodo was washing the floor while holding onto a basin.

He took a sideway glance at the salamander, then zeroed in on the abdominal wound that had already healed; shaking his head.

"Lord is crazy…It has been 3 days…could it be that he had already…"His face was filled with traces of worry.

Since Garen had saved him from the death row, he had pledged his loyalty to this thick piece of ham. If anything had happened to this thick piece of ham, he would definitely be unlucky too.

It was also an unspoken fact that he did not have the status of a freeman, and that he was part of the private property of Trejon’s clan leader. If the clan leader were to ever lose power, his future would also be bleak.

Hua!

He poured the remaining water onto the ground and mopped vigorously.

Well, it was no use thinking about all these now. Let’s just work earnestly.

Day by day, time flew by…

The fourth day.

Komodo began adding lamp oil to the lights on the wall. He had a look at the dual headed salamander in the nutrient pool; nothing seemed to have happened, the only difference seemed to be in how the giant beast had aged significantly.

The fifth day.

Komodo placed two letters on the edge of the table, glanced at the giant beast that exhibited no trace of movement, and walked out.

The sixth day…

The seventh day…

The eighth day…

The ninth day.

Ba dum!!!

The entire cavern was sounded with a dull thud, as if it came from the vibrations of a giant drum.

Komodo who was stifling a yawn awakened immediately from the shock. He stood up and surveyed his surroundings.

"An earthquake?!?!"

Splash! In the nutrient pool, the dual headed salamander elongated its neck and gasped in anguish, but there was no sound.

Its huge body was trembling slightly, it seemed to be suffering from a violent convulsion.

Ba dum!!!

Another dull heartbeat reverberated from its body. This huge beast had aged significantly in comparison to 9 days before, leaving only a bag of bones. After a few frantic roars, it collapsed heavily and panted with difficulty.

At the center of the beast’s heart, Garen opened his eyes. A large and powerful surge of energy he had never experienced before sprung up all over at different parts of his body.

The resonance of the salamander’s heart weakened with each second.

Garen’s heart on the other hand, was pumping with an massive force of life and vitality; it was just like new life, containing an unlimited amount of energy.

He held both of his hands interchangeably; the thick layer of blood scab congealed on his skin fell away with force.

All of a sudden within his body, a strange route of blood flow caught his attention.

Garen sensed the spontaneous route of the blood flow and felt a sense of vague familiarity.

Suddenly, he remembered something.

"Is this…!? The secret technique roadmap!!!"

His eyes snapped open, and he began to observe the spontaneous route his blood flow had naturally taken on within his body. These complex yet delicate routes were either fast or slow, and mapped out a complicated, three-dimensional blood and vital energy roadmap. It also had an inexplicable resonance in frequency.

The weirder thing was, Garen realized that roadmap was similar to a secret technique that he had practiced before.

This is…the Myriad Water Jasper technique?!!"He finally remembered. This roadmap was from the previous world; he got this top level secret technique from an exchange with Celine.

This secret technique was one of the branches of Neptune Fist, a legendary ancient martial arts organization. Celine did not mention how it came about, only mentioning that this was one out of the three oldest techniques there.

What surprised Garen the most was, his body was currently operating the Myriad Water Jasper technique’s first layer of vital energy and blood roadmap automatically.

Different from common folk, the vital energy and blood from his body had dual headed salamander characteristics. When he operated the first layer of the Myriad Water Jasper technique, mini cyclones were formed in the blood, reverberating throughout the blood vessels with great speed.

"Secret technique…Totems…" Garen had a vague hypothesis in his mind.

The Myriad Water Jasper technique has 5 layers to it. It was incompatible with the Divine Statue technique as the roadmaps were in conflict; he was only able to master the first layer, and it was only for the sharp force that the method offered.

And now his vital energy and blood were employing this technique naturally. Garen felt his Divine Statue technique depleting; the strong network constructed by the secret technique’s vital energy and blood was currently being dissolved by this bizarre Myriad Water Jasper technique.

"My Divine Statue technique…" Garen had no time for regret; he immediately checked the attribute pane at the bottom of his field of vision.

Right behind the attribute pane, a clear black and red symbol appeared. It consisted of 3 small black and red dots lined up in a triangular formation.

"Activate ancient memory of dual headed salamander, the body in question is going through changes. Myriad Water Jasper technique is going through mutation due to resonance.

Garen sensed the constant flow of the technique in his body. The heart constructed from the salamander produced a huge amount of fresh blood; at the same time, the salamander’s blood was also absorbed through the skin pores in large amounts, all sucked in by the Myriad Water Jasper technique. While all of these things were going on, an invisible and delicate force was generated.

This force appeared like countless invisible whirlpools, densely covering the entire area of Garen’s body.

It completely covered Garen; spreading out at the same time. It affected the giant dual headed salamander’s body.

Days passed.

Dual headed salamander appeared completely dried up. Its large volume of vital energy and blood was close to being sucked dry; its whole body weakly laying in the nutrient pool, void of any movement.

It could feel near its heart –the point of convergence of vital energy and blood, there seemed to be a black hole that was continuously swallowing up all its blood. This black hole had even grown bigger and bigger, its absorbing power becoming stronger and stronger.

Sssss!

It growled weakly; both eyes slowly dimming, losing its color.

In the underground cavern, Komodo looked from afar at the beast on the brink of death; his eyes full of shock.

The dual headed salamander’s chest suddenly expanded like it had a huge red growth.

The growth had a heart beat that was continuously pounding, a red fluorescent light vaguely appearing.

As the red fluorescent light around the growth grew brighter and brighter, the light in the eyes of the dual headed salamander grew dimmer and dimmer.

"What is this…! My God…"Komodo took a few consecutive steps back, almost backing up against the entrance of the cavern.

Finally, the growth expanded till its limit. It shrunk fiercely all of a sudden, as if all of the red light was sucked into a center.

Then, there was no light.

Ripppp!!!

A blood red, fresh rip appeared on the abdomen of the salamander.

A pair of bloody hands stretched out and grabbed both sides of the open wound.

Garen slowly walked out from the opening; his body covered in blood scabs. He looked like a bloody devil returning from hell.

He looked at the nutrient fluid below that had turned clear; the water reflected his current appearance.

The man staring back at him was completely blood red; his features were unrecognizable, so was his face. Only the 3 red glowing dots between his brows was as clear as day.

"I have succeeded. Secret techniques and totems, I knew they had some kind of connection."He muttered, reaching out his hands to touch the place in between his brows. The red lights were coming out from 3 birthmark-like red dots.

These red dots could not be felt through touch, and had the nature of normal skin. The 3 red lights were lined up like a triangle, and had an unusually neat placement.

This was just a physical change.

Garen was more concerned with the changes happening on the inside.

He looked towards the attribute pane at the bottom of his field of vision.

"Strength 6.66. Agility 3.11. Vitality 2.97. Intelligence 2.53. Potential 41128%. Possess the qualities of a luminarist.

Secret technique – Myriad Water Jasper Technique, Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills."

The moment he saw the attribute pane, he finally took a long sigh of relief.

He knew, he has finally achieved his goal.

Breaking limits, breaking past the limitations of his being; this was a road that no one treaded on before. Talking about that, Sylphalan was just like him; they both chose to modify themselves.

Once Garen finished his thoughts, he brought back to memory his attributes from before – Agility was at 2.72. Vitality was 2.82; both increased. Although the difference was not huge, it was an improvement. Being able to increase right after reaching his limit; this was a huge buff.

At the same time, his body possessed totem light attributes; he had achieved his goal successfully.

The weakened and greatly aged giant beast had already closed its eyes quietly; not a sound was heard.

Garen reached out his hand and slowly stroked its fragile scales; there was a trace of sadness in his heart. He knew it was him that had completely sucked the essence of the salamander’s blood until he was dry. Also, this dual headed salamander had used his entire being to give birth to who he was now.

But this did not mean that the dual headed salamander had completely vanished.

Chapter 362: Success 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen withdrew his hand and glanced at the totem panel. The Dual Headed Salamander’s icon remained there. It did not turn grey nor disappear.

He thoughtfully withdrew his hand and immersed his body in the nutrient pool, which had turned to clear water. The blood stains on his body were quickly washed off with the slightly vibration, revealing his white fleshed body beneath.

Suddenly, he noticed that although the Dual Headed Salamander's icon remained, some strange changes had quietly taken place.

He carefully looked at the totem’s introduction symbol. Suddenly, his pupils shrunk.

"What is this!!??"

The explanation on the front of Dual Headed Salamander’s totem icon suddenly evolved into a core totem!

"Core totem - Dual Headed Salamander: Third evolution of Deep Swamp Croc. Third Form Creature, Ultimate Totem, Cannot be evolved.

Abilities: Maze Mining, Life Tear, Dragon’s Roar, Dragon Skin, Parasitism."

Suddenly his heart skipped a beat, Garen gradually gathered his martial arts aura.

As the Myriad Water Jasper Technique continued to operate, a faint red aura slowly formed. It was a blood-like, thickened fluid, spreading all over the ground.

Garen could clearly feel a huge blood red pattern forming on his back. It was the pattern of the Dual Headed Salamander's body outline.

Garen extended his arm to look at his fair but abnormally tough skin. His five incredibly sharp fingernails on his left hand turned into devil-like red. Garen naturally realized that his left fingernails were the parts that could use Life Tear. Once the five red fingernails pierced any living being, it would replicate the effect of the Dual Headed Salamander’s Life Tear and draining the being’s life force to restore his own.

"This is the real way to use totems?" Garen felt enlightened in his heart.

His heart skipped a beat as the red Dual Headed Salamander behind him suddenly let out a fierce howl.

Sshhhh!!!

A circle of clear sound waves originated from him and spread throughout the perimeter.

"This is Dragon’s Roar." Garen, without any change in expression, jerked his left arm forward. Chii!! His five fingernails naturally extended, leaving a red shadow,. It was like a lunging, ferocious bite towards prey.

"This is Life Tear."

He abruptly leapt out from the pool in a blur. He landed in front of a clothing rack on the right side of the cave. He grabbed a grey robe and wrapped it around his body.

In a flash, Garen’s whole body was wrapped in the grey robe. His dripping wet golden hair was draped over his shoulder. His eyes were faintly glowing in red, but the most noticeable was the three red dots on his eyebrows which were still faintly emitting red fluorescence.

With a beat of his heart, the gigantic Dual Headed Salamander totem slowly dissipated. The three red dots on Garen’s eyebrows also stopped glowing, reverting to a normal three dot birthmark, like a cinnabar.

"Looking at it, once I stop using the totems, there won’t be any strange signs on my body." Garen had an epiphany.

The bizarre existence of the Dual Headed Salamander was similar to the primitive totems of Luminarists.

The only difference was while Luminarists used silver as the material for totem creation, Garen relied on blood; large amounts of the Dual Headed Salamander’s blood.

The similarity was both had an activated and deactivated form.

"Luminarists use a storage device to keep their core and secondary totems. While it seems that my current method is to combine the totem with my body as one?" Garen cautiously sensed the changes of his body. The Dual Headed Salamander totem seemed to be in the three red dots on his forehead.

He had a vague feeling that he was on the path of the legendary warlocks.

"If the way of the Luminarists retains the totem’s life as an independent being, my way of integrating the totem into the body to obtain the abilities of a core totem causes the totem to lose its independence. It will be totally dependent on the host body for nutrients.

He looked at the half-opened door in the distance. Komodo left it opened as he was fleeing. It was still lightly swaying from the air flow in the cave.

"Next, let’s see whether I have really surpassed my limits."

Garen focused and concentrated on the most important point.

The sign of surpassing his limits was tied to the increment of his attributes with potential points. This was the thing that he cared for the most. As for the core totem’s inability to evolve, there would be solutions in the future.

Even a Luminarist’s core totem could be changed once in five years. Maybe this form of core totems would be able to as well.

After focusing, Garen shifted his attention towards the attribute pane.

"Let me try it on vitality first." He glanced at "vitality" on the pane.

His vitality had already raised to 2.97 after the heart transplant.

He focused his gaze for three seconds.

One potential point vanished from the pane.

The vitality bar jumped from 2.97 to 3.07 in a moment.

Garen’s eyelid twitched. He remembered clearly that one potential point could increase 0.3 on the attribute pane previously. But now, it only increased it by 0.1.

Although he expected a increase in the depletion rate of potential points during attribute increment due to the increase in his strength, he didn’t think it would be so much.

"Luckily I’ve accumulated more than 400 potential points. Let’s see how much will be used." Garen was determined. His fixated his gaze on "Vitality".

His vitality shot up like a rocket. From 3.07 to 3.27, then 3.57...3.96...4.26...

His potential points also dropped like a stone.

As the vitality hit 5.00, the increment speed slowed down.

Through Garen’s careful observation, he realized that the depletion rate had changed once again. One potential point could now only increase 0.05 in attributes, which means 20 potential points were needed to increase 1 attribute point.

"Since I still have a lot, and only a few potential points were used, continue!" Garen’s expression remained and continued increasing his attributes. He was looking forward to see the attribute limits of his new body. Every being has a limit. The difference was whether the limit can be reached.

His vitality points continue to raise at an insane rate. As it hit 5.00, it required 20 potential points to increase 1 attribute point. In one go, Garen’s vitality rushed past 6.00, then 7.00, 8.00.

As it hit 8.00, the depletion rate chanced once again. From requiring 20 potential points to increase one attribute point, it became above 60 potential points.

As his vitality hit 10.00, it was stuck at this number and could no longer be increased.

His potential points had already been depleted by almost 200 points. Garen felt the heartache as he looked at the remaining 200 potential points which had been accumulated over a long period of time. Recently, the results haven’t been good for the Petrifying White Dragon and the rest. There was only an increase of around 10 points each day. It was evident that there wasn’t much to hunt.

As Garen stood in the tunnel, he felt the changes caused by the huge increase in attributes.

Before the increase, he could already rely on his 6 points of strength to draw in a fight with the Dual Headed Salamander. The Dual Headed Salamander was a giant beast known for its strength. As his vitality reached 10.00, Garen was unsure what changes it would bring. He only felt a stronger musculoskeletal system,tougher skin and more alert senses.

His sense of smell could detect different kinds of odors. It could detect the Dual Headed Salamander’s blood, his own blood, the smell of stones, the smell of nutrient fluids and even the fragrance of a bush in the far corner.

His eyes could see the minute patterns on the wall opposite the cave’s hall. There was a black beetle crouching there. Garen could clearly see that the little finger-sized beetle was mildly chewing on some moss on the wall. He could even clearly see the villi on its mouth.

The sound of the beetle chewing on the moss seemed to be just beside his ear. He could hear it completely once he focused his attention.

Garen felt the toughening of his skin all over his body, but other than that, there didn’t seem to have much changes visually. It was still fair like white jade of the finest grade. However, Garen could feel that his whole body was layered with a layer of invisible stratum corneum. This layer of stratum corneum was incredibly tough, like the scales of a dragon.

"The increase of vitality was effective indeed. Looks like 10 points is this body’s new limit." Garen focused his gaze on the two key attributes, strength and agility.

"Strength seems better. My martial arts has always been on the path of strength. All my styles revolved around immense strength." Garen thought for a moment and chose to increase his strength. Whatever remained would then be used on agility.

Since his martial arts did not focus on agility, this was the best way. For those martial artists that focused on speed, agility would naturally be the choice.

His fixated his gaze on the strength attribute.

The same scenario happened. The strength attributed climbed upwards from 6.66. In a brief moment, it exceeded 8.00 and was still swiftly increasing.

Garen was delighted and was eager to test the effects of the change in strength.

Suddenly, a bored, low growl came from the back of his mind.

His blood red core totem - the Dual Headed Salamander emerged from his back. The 7-8 metre tall blood totem twisted and roared towards the sky.

There was ball of flesh emerging from the Dual Headed Salamander’s body, from its back part near its neck.

The ball of flesh grew and expanded. Finally, with a tearing sound, the ball of flesh tore apart and another dragon head appeared.

It was then Garen noticed that balls of fleshes were growing on the salamander’s back as his strength attribute increased.

The balls of flesh grew more and more, bigger and bigger, like a fast-forwarded movie. The balls of flesh grew a rate visible to the naked eye. They would then tear part, forming wet, new dragon heads.

One by one the new heads emerged. Until after the eighth head, things came to a halt.

The eight headed salamander’s size had evidently increased. From a height of 7-8 metres to 10 metres and eventually twelve metres. Its twenty-metre long body looked exactly like a red mountain.

At this point, the strength attribute had increased to 14.00. The limit of the body was 10.00, but the increase of the gigantic creature wasn’t included in the limit. Garen was delighted.

Whether it was the salamander’s change or him surpassing the limits of the attributes, there seemed to be an unknown connection.

While Garen was delighted, he also faintly realized. This method of totem combination seemed to be far stronger than the way of the Luminarists.

The improvement of the host’s body could even affect the core totem. This was mind boggling.

Chapter 363: Arrangement and Moving Forward 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Its strength kept increasing until 14 before coming to a pause, and the Dragon’s heads stopped increasing once it reached eight. However, there was a new bag of meat on its back, suggesting a possibility of having a ninth head.

Garen observed that the existing nature of this Dragon was rather elusive as it didn’t have an actual body. The eight headed dragon indeed did not have an actual body, as it didn’t interact with everything else. However, the strength he could use from the Dragon would increase greatly when it appeared. The strength he could put out was twice the strength before he released the totem.

Garen named this new creature as the Eight Headed Dragon. Although he named it as such, anyone would have assumed that the ninth head would come out sooner or later, due to the bag of meat on its back.

The second head of the Dual Headed Salamander had the Life Tear ability but the remaining new heads didn’t seem to have any unique ability. Perhaps it’s due to it not having an actual body or some other reason that these new heads didn’t have other ability, and all of them had the Life Tear ability!

As these heads were born, Garen could feel that Life Tear had been enhanced to an incredible level. Although he didn’t know the extent of this effect, he believed that it should be at least 6 times stronger than the original Life Tear, and it shouldn’t be weak no matter how he looked at it.

What the evolved Eight Headed Dragon brought to Garen wasn’t just an enhanced strength, he had also a new ability -- Gravitational Vortex.

With his grey robe on, Garen reached out his right hand and flicked his finger.

Pew!

An invisible vortex was shot up and floated in front of him no more than one meter away.

This vortex was about one meter in diameter and rotated the air surrounding it, attracting everything from its surrounding. There was an unknown hole in the center of the vortex which lead to an unknown space.

Garen counted that he could released eight of these vortices at the same time, which was the same number as the heads of the Eight Headed Dragon.

These eight vortices rotated at a high angular velocity, resulting in the formation of a strong whirlwind causing huge amounts of items flying towards the vortices. It was like a powerful tornado.

In a blink of an eye, large amount of shirts, wooden racks, scientific equipment and nutritional wastewater were absorbed into the vortices. What was left in the hole was those items that were hard and solid.

As Garen dissipated the vortices, he rubbed his stomach with a weird expression, as he felt that something had entered his guts.

He felt that those items that were absorbed into the vortices were transported into his stomach.

It seemed that those items had been refined and turned into nutrients and entered his body.

"Could it be that these eight vortices are the Eight Headed Dragon’s mouth?!" Garen guessed.

He then started to analyse these eight vortices in detail.

After some time of experimenting, Garen finally understood the theory behind these eight vortices.

It was the same as he imagined. These were all the mouths of the Eight headed Dragon, and they could swallow everything from the outside world, including rocks, debris and some dangerous sharp weapons. Furthermore, the debris that it swallowed could turn into pure energy and replenish the totem power.

One had to realize that one would spend their totem power whenever they activated their totem, be it a core totem or a support totem. The more totems one activated, the more totem power was spent. A typical form one totem user could engage in a high level battle without breaking a sweat.

However, a form two user could only engage in a high level battle for about half a day and a form three totem user would have spent even more totem power. The typical form three totem users wouldn’t activate their totem casually and would only use them when necessary. Furthermore, a lot of totem users would rely on their low grade support totem as an energy source to reduce their expenditure of totem power. This was also the reason why the totem markets kept existing.

As for the strong spiritualized totem similar to that of Beckstone’s spiritualized totem Sunflower, he would feel exhausted if he were to release a small amount of power even with the support of the Heirlooms. Regardless of whether if it’s related to his physical strength, this also proved that a spiritualized totem required a lot of energy.

Garen wanted to find a solution towards the Crystal Derivator’s flaws, as he cherished this item a lot. This was because the empowered totems which were controlled by the Crystal Derivator did not require an ounce of totem power. The totem itself would eat and rest to recover, which was one of its major advantage.

Naturally, it had its own disadvantages as well. While the empowered totem did not require any totem power, it required a huge amount of food which was rather troublesome. He would need to spend a huge amount of meat daily to feed the large amount of Deep Swarm Crocs and Parasitic Beetles. If their food source were to be interrupted, they would be weak and might even die. On the other hand, the Primitive Totem was very convenient as it didn’t require rest nor food and it could be carried with him anywhere.

Garen didn’t know which class he was in anymore, but what he was sure was that he was much stronger than before.

He felt that his core totem’s state was similar to that of the legendary form four, which was purely elementalization. In this era, where spiritualized totems were considered rare, the fourth form totem, elementalization, was completely in the realm of the mythical. In addition, he had yet to account for his physical attributes, where his strength had increased to 14 points and had 10 points of constitution. Under these extreme limits, he could be considered more fearsome than the totem itself.

Garen walked towards the side of the nutritional pool as and looked at himself in the reflection. He looked weak, gentle, slim and handsome, which gave off a delicate and beautiful juvenile vibe. He was very satisfied with his current look as his demeanour would definitely confuse his enemies. While his biceps did not look physically strong, it possessed an incredible strength that surpassed any living being.

"Reylan had mentioned before that the Elemental Generals of the Obscuro Society were all spiritualized. Each of them had at least two spiritualized totems, this without considering their ability to control their General-level subordinates. Based on this, an Elemental General would have the strength of an army of Spiritualized Totems, with most of them being form three creatures. Since there creatures able to kill Elemental Generals, this obviously means that form four creatures exist, and the reason I hadn’t encountered one at all was because they are very rare. To think that the Marshall of the Obscuro Society is able to take back his territory by letting the creatures escape as they smelled his scent, this means that there is something stronger than elementalization, which places him at form four or form five. If this is true, then the Obscuro Society’s overall strength is clear as day."

Garen sorted out his chain of thoughts.

"We can ignore the Marshalls for now; those are the people who manage the overall situation of multiple countries and are under the direct command of the Hellgate of the Obscuro Society. They basically wouldn’t appear because of any one situation, as I have never heard of a form four of form five Marshall class appearing before. The strongest person in charge is definitely the Elemental General per country, who is at the Spiritualization level. Judging from the looks of it, my totem strength has reached a certain peak."

Now that he had a clear understanding of where he stood in terms of strength, his totem was at its peak before the mysterious creatures appeared. He would have to fight with this mysterious creature to find out that who was the stronger one.

As he looked at the holes caused by his messy experiment, his sight landed on the corpse of the Dual Headed Salamander. This old Salamander was so thin that it practically didn’t have any muscle at all.

"Komodo." He turned around as he walked towards the door. "Clean this place up."

A tall figure peeked his head in from the entrance and Komodo relaxed as he saw Garen.

"Alright Sir." He was glad when he saw Garen was safe. This meant that his future was insured.

As Garen walked out of the cave, he could faintly hear Komodo’s cries echoing from within.

"Oh… The cave that I cleaned up just a moment ago…"

Garen laughed as he walked up the stairs in the laboratory. He was so swift that his figure faded as he went out.

A few seconds later, he stood at the exit of the underground laboratory and gently opened the door.

Wow.

Garen was blinded by the golden ray from the outside.

He squinted his eyes and walked out of the experimental room, the door behind him closing shut by itself.

It was noon. The scorching wind blew in from the balcony, rustling the pots’ leaves by the wall.

Garen turned right, and went into his bedroom and wore an undergarment which he took out from his wardrobe. He then took out the Secret Agent Armor given by His Majesty himself.

It was an all-black hardened armor and looked like it was connected by many small squares. He had a black hood on and two pauldrons protruding out from his shoulder.

A pair of band collars surrounded his neck and the left band collar had the national flower, the Golden Iris Flower of the Kovitan Empire sewn onto it.

It was the first time Garen saw the iris flower, even when he was on Earth and the world of Secret Techniques. This Iris Flower that was sewn was golden in color, the overall shape was a perfect equilateral triangle as if two three leaf clover superimposed each other and formed the petal. Two three leaf clovers overlapped each other, and formed a perfect triangle. The stamens at the center of the triangle formed another perfect triangle, which gave off an exquisite vibe.

He touched the cloth, which seemed to be made out of golden thread.

As he wore the full body armor, the upper body was hardened armor whereas the lower body was a black skirt. He even paired it with black trousers and a shiny long boots.

Garen stood in front of the mirror and admired himself. After refining his body, he had gotten slimmer, and his body was well portioned. He wore a pair of gloves and his hood, which totally covered his face. Only his pale chin and red lips could be seen.

The armor didn’t require any body support, and everyone seemed to be able to fit into the armor. If he were to slightly lower his head, no one would be able to recognize who was wearing it.

Surprisingly, Garen didn’t feel overheated as he wore his hood and gloves. The sun blazed overhead outside, as waves of heated drafts gushed in from the balcony.

He analysed the the armor and realized that there was something on both of the pauldrons. Both pauldrons were engraved with a simple Solidifying Tactic. This armor was very similar to the War Chain that could release the Solidifying Tactic and its effect.

Garen analysed the workings of the armor, and it seemed that it could absorb the totem user’s naturally leaking totem power and use it for the armor’s tactic. Hence, this airtight design’s purposes were to remain hidden and collect as much totem energy as much as possible.

Whether it be illuminarists, totem users or Forgers, as long as he possessed totem energy, he or she would naturally lose a minimal amount wearing this. It was similar to a human body losing body heat to the surrounding.

This armor made full use of the these, and recycled the energy to the best of its extent.

Chapter 364: Arrangement and Moving Forward 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stroked this set of armor as he daydreamed one that was even more advanced.

The technology of the Secret Service was so advanced that it already had such an armor set. If that was the case, then they should have even better armor which had an even stronger Solidifying Tactics engraved onto it. It would collect the emission of totem power and release it when it was needed.

Garen was stunned. Totem users who possessed this armor would be much stronger than the typical totem users. If one were to have very powerful armor…

He stopped his train of thought.

He reached out his hand and pulled the thread beside his bed.

Ring ring.

A clear and crisp bell was rung, and footsteps could clearly be heard coming from outside.

The restless Lala soon appeared outside the room. Her face was filled with joy as she saw Garen.

"You finally came out! There are a few letters for you recently, all of them want you to be there as soon as possible. Even the messenger kept reminding me multiple times."

She felt relief as he saw Garen came out as her main support had returned.

Garen adjusted his collar and walked out of the room to the wooden sofa in the living room, sitting down.

"Where’re the letters? Bring them to me. Didn’t they say that I should be there 2 months later? Why are they rushing now?"

Lala walked towards a vase which was placed at a corner of the living room and poured out all the letters contained inside it. All of these letters were yellow and square in shape.

"The messenger said that there was an emergency and they needed a helping hand." Lala arranged the stack of letters by the date and placed them in front of Garen before she stood at one side waiting for more orders.

Occasionally, she would give Garen a strange look as she compared Garen’s thick armor and her sleeveless white dress.

Garen picked up the first envelope and took out the letter.

There was merely a line written on the white piece of paper.

‘The reporting date has been brought forward due to an emergency. Vice Captain Garen Trejons, kindly report into the Wells Castle as soon as possible.’

The date written was: Sun Calendar 3568 11th of May.

There was also a red circular stamp where the word Confidential was faintly inked. It was the word confidential made out of three alphabets.

Garen opened the remaining letters and all of them were basically urging his earliest arrival. The most recent one was three days ago, which was on the 14th.

"I wonder what does this Vice Captain position His Majesty has assigned me does. It doesn’t sound too bad but it doesn’t look good either." Garen placed down the letter. "Are there any more?’

He looked at Lala.

"Yes, and they are invitations to the ball from the Noble households." Lala answered immediately as she ran out of the room and returned in a short while with a box of invitations. These invitations were crafted delicately.

Garen glanced at the names on the letter and they were all relative households of the Trejons Household. He picked out the invitations from Earl Baxy and Viscount Lavel and was about to throw the remaining to the side.

Suddenly he saw a familiar name, Prynne.

Prynne Acivis.

His name was printed black on a golden surface, with an image of two blades crossing each other.

Garen picked up the envelope and opened the letter.

‘My best friend, Dear Acacia:

Oh wait, I should be calling you Garen. Alright. How are you Garen? I heard the incident of the Trejons Household and your current situation seems dire. Just let me know if you need a helping hand. You should know very well of my grandfather’s networking.

Furthermore, your cousin has sent Andel to my place and I will arrange everything nicely, so don’t worry about it. Malin is here as well. She doesn’t seem to be in a good mood as Baron Delt has passed away, and mistress Callaway is missing. I have sent a few people to track her down but to no avail.

The kingdom’s situation is rather complicated. I have told my grandfather about your situation and he also know that you have given an item called the Green Vine Sphere to His Majesty and that you also join the Secret Service. He suggest you to enroll in it so that you can avoid the complicated situation in the Kingdom. It’s best for you to stay low profile. Although you’re very strong, the Kingdom has many strong people as wel,l so please be careful.’

Garen reread the last part of the message where he told him to be careful. It was obvious that Prynne knew much more than him due to his Household’s connections.

He placed down the envelope, placed both of his hands together and crumpled the letter into white dust as he threw them into the dustbin nearby.

He had already memorised the address written in it.

Prynne’s grandfather was one of the two people with the most authority in the kingdom, excluding His Majesty.

These two were originally the high class nobles in their respective area and both of them hold the title of Grand Duke. However, as the area deteriorated, both of them moved to the kingdom and became the new dividends in power. The Grand Duke of the Iron Tank City was not comparable to these ones as these stood on the top of the country. They were the upper class nobles who had been around for thousands of years with deep backgrounds and incredible strength. They had at least form three totem users, or else they wouldn’t be able to migrate a huge amount of people to the Kingdom. They definitely had Spritualized totem users, maybe even more than one too.

These superior nobles hold a great portion of the whole kingdom’s power, and the remaining portions were held by the remaining nobles, which formed the entire strength of the Kovitan Empire.

As Prynne’s grandfather, his intel would most likely be accurate as no one had no reason to lie to him.

"Looks like the strength I have revealed back in the manor has travelled to the Kingdom." Garen noted on this as he had reveal the strength of a form three spiritualized back in the manor to oppress Beckstone and the people from Obscuro Society.

This news was most likely got there through the word of mouth from Andel, Hathaway and the people who had escaped to the Kingdom. There were also those two old instructors, Barr and Baphje, who were also likely to the ones who spread the news.

"I’ll head out for a while so you guys can go and make yourselves some dinner without me." Garen pondered for a while before he stood up and told her.

"I’ll prepare a carriage for you." Lala immediately ran out.

Garen placed the verification document and verification ID given by His Majesty into a black file and brought it along with him.

As he walked out of the manor’s entrance inside the cliff, a black wheeled horse carriage was already waiting for him. The carriage’s wheels were massive, and the driver was a middle aged man with a small moustache in a black suit. He took off his hat and greeted Garen.

"I am Josephine, your newly hired driver."

Garen nodded as he got up the carriage.

"Towards Wells Castle, please"

"Alright, please sit tight." The driver Josephine responded as he took out a whip and made a noise in the air.

Two strong aberrated horses started moving. These two horses were brought by Garen to the manor. Their strength and endurance was commendable, and were considered the good ones among the aberrated horses.

"Your horses are very powerful." The driver praised. "There are little aberrated horses that can run like that."

"Oh?" Garen laughed. "Aren’t all aberrated horses excellent?"

"Of course not. There are a lot of aberrated animals that are bad. Some aberrated horses are weaker than before." The driver laughed as he replied. "It’s very easy to be your driver. These horses are very docile, and they will be full for a few days if you feed them meat. I get paid with such a high salary and I don’t even needed to go out for half a month."

Garen smiled and didn’t say a word afterwards.

The talkative Josephine wanted to talk more but he suddenly recalled the rumors of the owner. After some hesitation, he decided to keep his mouth shut and didn’t utter another word.

As they went up the hills, other carriages would occasionally passed by them and as they intersected, he could faintly hear the girl’s mourn.

Garen suddenly realized that these scenarios were fairly common, as most nobles had sought refuge in the kingdom. Along the way, they had most likely lost a lot of their relatives, parents, siblings or offsprings. Almost all families had lost some of their members, many of them were like Vanderman, where not even bones were left for them to perform a proper burial.

As the carriages moved forward, small buildings started to appear beside the white lanes. These were all black double storey or triple storey buildings, busy with people going going in and out of the houses.

Garen looked out of the window and saw a young lady in a white head scarf placing a pot of fresh purple flower by the window on the second floor of a double storey building opposite the street.

There were a few men quarreling and shoving each other, on the ground floor, incessantly shouting at each other.

After the carriaged passed through the buildings, they arrived at a black cemetery.

The cemetery was densely packed with white tombs and there were rituals being performed right in front of two new tombs. A Priest in white robes stood together with the family members in black attires as they mourned.

After passing by the cemetery, they arrived at the place with buildings of three storeys. It looked like a shopping district as the buildings were densely packed together.

The majority of the shops were closed. There was a long queue among the shops still open, lining eagerly in old and ragged clothes. Among the queue, some of them were women with a child in their arms, very thin youngsters and even pale old men.

As Garen’s carriages passed by, some of them looked towards his direction and immediately lowered their heads in fear.

Thud!!

There were a flew clangs.

The carriage was immediately put to a halt.

The driver Josephine’s voice could be heard in the front as the carriage shook before coming to a stop.

"Damn it! Which household’s driver are you from? Didn’t you see us passing through from the right?!" A high and mighty tone came from the front.

"It was obviously you who didn’t notice us!" Josephine shouted in disatisfaction.

"You dare to talk back to me! How dare a broken piece of carriage crash into Viscount Duncan’s carriage! I will…"

"Bob! Shut up!"

A man’s cold voice came within the opponent’s carriage.

The driver was silent as he turned around and smiled. As he turned his head back, he stared fiercely at Josephine.

Garen pulled up the curtain and saw the man in the white carriage doing the same as well. The other party looked gentle but had a rather sharp gaze.

The other party’s blue eyes were filled with fear and alertness as he saw Garen’s black armor.

Both of them smiled towards each other politely, wind down the curtain and both of the driver continued driving in their respective directions.

"Looks like this Secret Agent armor provides a good deterrence…" He started to feel excited towards the legendary Three Departments. Perhaps he could be able to get more in touch with this world’s secrets when he joined this strong organization.

Chapter 365: Exposed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Hehe, these people don’t know you’re the leader of a noble household." Josephine smiled. ""You’re much more valuable than these old nobles by the streets."

"Don’t say that." Garen scolded mildly. "There should be a lot of leaders of the noble households who lost their territory, causing them to be unable to support their household’s power, right?"

"That’s true." Josephine’s smile disappeared. "I have once worked for an old noble who was in the same situation. He didn’t buy much into the industry in the kingdom and the wealth he brought along the way was lost. A few days later, we were separated as he could no longer support us. To see a household of a few hundred years collapsing just like that, sigh…"

Garen didn’t utter a single word as he listened to Josephine.

From the mouth of a driver who was hired by many nobles, he was able to obtained a lot of small intel that nobody knew. The drivers often gathered together and talked to each other and he found out that nobles with authority in the kingdom amounted to less than four hundred. Compared to the thousands of noble families in the past, this was just a drop of water in the ocean.

Josephine was originally unhappy due to his unemployment, but he didn’t expect to be hired by Lala, and became the main topic among the drivers. Although Lord Garen’s reputation was subpar, he was indeed an actual upper class noble, and rumor had it that he had a close relationships with the nobles with high authority.

The carriage finally got out of the kingdom and passed through the district and took half a turn in the kingdom. After passing through the custom, what awaited them at the front was a huge yellow-green grass field.

The grasses were green and yellow with some bushes of red fruit dotted here and there.

This field was located at the very end of the black building district, surrounded by a circular black wall, forming a huge oval shaped zone.

The giant pond in the center slowly came into view after travelling on the field for a while.

"That is the Wells Lake, the main source of water to the entire Kingdom. Other than the Wells Castle where you’re heading, the Kingdom’s Water Supply Department is located here." The driver Josephine seemed to know this place very well.

There were a few single convertible carriages heading towards the Wells Castle on the straight road as well. Occasionally, a few horses overtook Garen’s carriage, there seemed to be no one walking at all.

The carriages on the lane gradually increased, making the speed of the carriage gradually decrease as well.

After 10 minutes or so, a grey-white stone castle finally appeared.

The small castle was built on the lake, and the only connection to the castle from the land was a stone bridge.

The wall of the small castle seemed to be made out of pieces of cobblestone, which looked like goose eggs. They were uneven and densely packed together. There were four peaks at the top which formed a square point. A black chimney could be seen at the center of the of the castle.

Garen looked from afar and the castle didn’t seem to be very big, as it was about the size of a double storey residential building. There was a black traffic light set up at the entrance by the stone bridge. There were two people wearing the same black armor as Garen whispering among each other.

Garen’s carriage stopped at the empty space beside the stone bridge.

"We’re here, m’lord."

"Alright. You can head back first and not wait for me." Garen got down of the carriage and walked towards the stone bridge.

He walked past a couple of people in conversation and entered the entrance of the small castle through the stone bridge.

After passing through the pitch dark entrance, he arrived in a guest room linked together on both sides. The wall was hung with all kinds of weird accessories, most of them were weirdly shaped accessories made out of white bones. There were white deer horns, thick thighs and a skull the size of basketball.

There was a pale lady in spectacles and grey custom made armor, sitting at the reception at the right side of the guest room. She smiled as she saw Garen come in.

"Good day, you must be Viscount Garen who came reporting in right? We have already received your notice and we have a picture of you here. Please verify your identity."

Garen took out a document, which was a golden certificate given by His Majesty.

The pale lady returned Garen the document after examining it closely as she note down the relevant information onto a small notebook.

"Please wear this and head towards the second room on the right. Someone will meet you there."

She passed him a golden-black badge with a golden Z alphabet on it.

Garen followed her instructions and entered the room on the right, heading towards the small room at the far end.

The decoration of this small room was similar to the living hall as accessories made of white bones were propped up everywhere. There were two males and one female arguing over something and all of them quiet down as they heard footsteps.

As Garen entered, a guy and a girl, both in black armor, looked at him, the other guy with brown hair placed his finger into his hair with his head down. It was clear that he had yet to calm down as he kept expanding his chest.

Garen ignored them and walked directly towards the room on the left.

Whoosh…

After a series of noises, the wall split and opened a path that lead to a slanted passage.

The ceiling of the passage was made out of glass and guided the sunlight in from the outside just like the skylight.

Garen walked into it.

"Welcome welcome! Welcome Viscount Garen Trejons." A fatty walked towards him with joy and hold Garen’s hand tightly.

"I am Baidel and I’m the deputy city governor from the distant Shield Hill. I am currently seeking refuge in the Kingdom. Your arrival is a blessing to us all!"

The fatty was ecstatic as he pulled Garen enthusiastically forward and informed him of the situation as they moved forward.

"You may not know of the current situation since you have just arrived. Our overall structure in the Secret Service consists of the Headquarters, administration branch district Office and the special service group. These five layers fully cover the entire Kovitan, and this is the headquarter of the Kovitan. We manage five branches, and each branch managed their own district and we have many more groups further down. And you’re currently our most wanted Vice Captain."

"The current situation is dire and we have lost a lot of Captain level personnel. Although you’re currently just a Vice Captain, you can officially become a Captain through some training. Here, no matter if it’s the Headquarter, Branch or the District Office, our core strength comes by forming a team. The headquarter’s team is the best, followed by the team from Branch office and so on." The fatty explained swiftly.

"If the team from the District Office cannot accomplish the mission, they will report it to the Branch. After the assessment from the Branch, they will dispatch a team from the Branch to perform the mission. If the mission is still yet to be completed, they would report it to the Administration and so on until it reaches Headquarters. You are currently under the Kovitan’s Administration team. The current situation is complicated as there are a lot of situations that can't be resolved. We have sent out most of our team, 8 out of the 10 that we have. We are left with one team in the Headquartera in case of emergencies, and the other one is currently performing their duties in the Kingdom. His Majesty heard that you’ll be here so he had made preparations beforehand…"

"Wait a minute. Did you just say that you’re the Director of the District Office in the Kingdom? If this is the Headquarter of the Kovitan, then where is the branch director and the headquater director of this place?" Garen cut off his explanation.

"Uhh… They have all gone out on their respective missions…" The fatty took out a white handkerchief to wipe off his sweat. He wasn’t sure why Sir Garen’s image was totally different from the intel he received. The intel said that he was a gentle and polite person who loved beautiful women (He was once head over heels over Aquarius), and also a person who loved poetry.

However, this person who stood before him felt like a beast. Although his skin was pale and his face was indeed gentle and occasionally had a smile on his face, he also somehow gave off a feeling that sent shivers down his spine.

It was indeed weird, how could he be so fearful with his gentle smile?

The fatty felt very anxious.

"We are seriously lacking a lot of manpower, and there is also the fact that the Secret Service is being threatened as well. Raged, the general director, decided to bring out the strongest Silver Team out for this mission. It is estimated that they would return in a week’s time. Hence they've put me temporarily in charge here."

"What benefits would it bring to me if I were to join the Secret Service?" Garen asked the most important question straightaway.

"You’ll have access to the Royal Alliance’s highest level of intelligence, and you would receive a good sum of money and resources every month. You will also have the authority to kill anyone who doesn’t bear the title of Viscount and above. You will also have full authority to forcefully detain anyone who isn’t a Viscount during emergencies. If the opposing party refuses your order, they will be treated as breaking the law and become a wanted battle criminal." The fatty seemed to be very familiar with this as he explained everything in one swoop.

"Another important thing to note is that you can, based on your grade, visit any Master-level to create or service your totem from the Royal Alliance. Naturally, the expenses will be borne by you."

"Hehe… This is very beneficial." Garen couldn’t help but to feel excited as he listened.

Although he had killed so many people out there, he would immediately be hunted down by the strong people all over the country if he were to kill anyone within the Royal Alliance’s territory. If he were to have this position, he would naturally be relieved of his worry. No wonder His Majesty was constantly concerned over this department as they had such an amount of authority. If His Majesty were to not control them with his own hand, he might be in trouble as well.

"To be frank with you, the reason I joined this department was because I was aiming for the right to select at my own discretion. Hehe." The fatty told Garen what every men knew. "If you were to find any beautiful women, you can simply find a reason to fulfill your right to act, if you know what I mean."

Garen was speechless. He recalled the destruction of the Kovitan Empire in the original history. The first reason was that His Majesty had been assassinated and the second reason was that the citizens were outraged because of the abundance of power the Secret Service department held. It’s most likely because of these types of people similar to this fatty.

"Then, what do we have to sacrifice?" Garen asked again.

"Follow the orders from the upper echelon. Your superior will be Marquis Yawei, who is the Deputy Director of headquarters. He is also the person who manages the Nine Color Team. Naturally with your level which is at the Administration, you’ll be performing the same duty similar to the Deputy Director of the Administration. Hence you can freely mobilize the people below you. As the Secret Service, our main responsibility is to take care of the issues within our territory. Anything related to assassination, rebellions, riot, spying etc falls under us. The National Department will be fighting openly and the hardworking kids in the Geometry Service will be doing researching. Simply put, we are responsible for handling issues in the dark. Everyone will be doing their own stuff if nothing is going on and will risk their lives if we are tasked to do something."

"I understood." Garen understood.

Two of them walked forward and took countless turns. Soon, the lights from above dimmed and the supports of the glass became transparent. They could see the crystal clear water flowing above their heads.

Finally, they entered a small passage with two rooms placed opposite of each other, and two bronze nameplates hung above each of them.

Garen looked at the names of the plates and realized that one was orange and the other red.

He was then pulled by the fatty into an underground room to the left.

There was a long meeting table placed inside the room, and there were already four or five people sitting inside. All of them were wearing a slightly shallow grey armor and all of them seemed to be rather depressed with their hoods on.

These people didn’t react much as they saw Garen entering the room. They were minding their own business. Two women were having a conversation together and one youngster seemed to be discussing something with an old man. There was even one who directly placed his legs on the table and covered his face with his hood as he snored all the way.

"This is your red team. From today onwards, they will be your group members. I have to go as I still have other things to attend to. You’re on your own now." The damned fatty left immediately after a brief explanation.

"What do you mean I’m on my own." Garen didn’t manage to understand the whole situation and the fatty ran away. He couldn’t shake the feeling that something was off.

He stood at the entrance and looked at everyone in the room who were ignoring him. These people had used up all the chairs and didn’t even leave him one.

"Whoever knows the overall situation, can you tell me what’s going on?" Garen revealed a harmless smile.

The youngster and the old man paused their discussion. The white haired old man raised his head and squinted his eyes as he looked at him.

"Young man, are you the new team leader?"

"Based on the fatty’s statement, I believe I am." Garen showed his emblem.

"You should go back from where you came from." The old man shook his head. "This is not a place where a small kid can enter freely."

Garen smiled and didn’t say much.

"Am I not the person in charge of this team?"

Chapter 366: Exposed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"This is the red team, but it is not a place you can handle." The woman who was having a conversation raised her head and smirked at Garen. "Everyone here is a form three totem user. We have finished up to hundreds of missions before we got here. Do you understand what it means to complete hundreds of missions?"

The girl smiled.

"It means that everyone here has killed hundreds of totem users and all of them were in the same class."

She continued. "We of the Secret Service had a statistical death of one person per group per month. There are a lot of back ups waiting to fill our role. These people are professionals who live on the edge every single day. Do you understand what I’m trying to say here?"

"That’s true. If it’s me, I wouldn’t believe a leader who came down from the sky either. If that’s the case, then I will give up on my rights in command and we will all be on equal footing and perform the mission together. Do you agree?" Garen said nicely.

"That’s the right choice." The old man seemed very satisfied.

"My name is…" As Garen was about to introduce himself, he was cut off by the old man as he raised his hand.

"Young man, It’s best not to reveal your real name in this sort of place. Using a nickname will do. This is an advice from an old man. Alright alright, everyone drop your act and properly introduce yourselves." The old man smiled. "My call sign is oldman. These two sisters are called Kitten and Fox respectively. This youngster beside me is called Hunter and the person who is asleep is our vice captain, Red Umbrella."

Garen nodded.

"The nicknames were created by yourselves?"

"Of course, you can call yourself whatever you want as long as it’s easy to pronounce." The old man nodded.

"Then you can call me Nineheads." Garen replied gently.

"Nineheads? The old man shook his head as he gestured the kid Hunter to give a space for him to sit. "Have a seat. We were discussing a mission we were about to execute before you arrived."

With this, the whole atmosphere had warmed up.

"Everyone will have their own standard parcel for this mission and I would need you to retrieve it for us later. We will discuss about the difficulties of this mission for now." The old man commanded sternly.

Garen glanced at everyone else and the man who was sound asleep had placed down his legs and was no longer snoring. It was obvious that he was listening to the discussion. Everyone looked focused and was completely different from a moment ago.

Garen didn’t mind as he was entered the Secret Service to do what he had to do in a low profile. The incident regarding the Trejons Household was very heated and it required some time for it to die off.

He didn’t want to be targeted by the Obscuro Society and Terraflor Society just yet.

The Black Prince would soon arrive in the Kingdom to meet His Majesty. Security detail fell under the Secret Service, but it was the mission given to the Black Team, which was the strongest team among the Nine Color teams so it was none of his business. What they needed to do was to eliminate the group of monsters in the surrounding area.

The location of the mission had been implemented into the map and was packed with at least ten red dots. They only had one month to clear the mission to prevent any delay in the Black Prince’s schedule.

Garen was rather stunned at the Old Man’s arrangement as there was no strategy involved. Positional tasking was given as to who would be in charge at which area. Some were given two or three places, indicating their difference in strength.

One had to realize that these red dots might have form three creatures gathered and they were all distributed among the five of them. Hunter and Red Umbrella had more red dots, three and four red dots respectively. Furthermore, these red dots were the stronger ones as well. As each of them obtained one or two, they soon finished distributing the red dots.

The Old Man suddenly realized that they had an additional person, Garen. He looked at Garen as he hesitated. "Do you want one?" He asked.

"Sure. I will take it as a beginner’s training. One red dot shouldn’t be any issue." Garen smiled.

"Be vigilant. Although it’s just one red dot, there will be at least two form three creatures. If you can’t handle it you should immediately send the rescue signal." The Old Man expressed his goodwill.

"You should leave this group if you can’t even handle one red dot." Kitten smirked.

"I will go to bed if there’s nothing else." Red Umbrella yawned as he stood up, preparing to leave the room. "Send the things to my room later."

"You can send the items to our rooms later. It’s indicated in the map and it’s easy to find." The Old Man stood up and patted Garen on the shoulder.

"It’s time for you to shine." Kitten walked passed Garen’s side and did the same. The other girl, Fox, didn’t say a word and left the room.

The Kid Hunter smiled at Garen and was the last one to leave.

Garen stood in the room speechless as he looked at the empty chairs and tables.

"So I’m the bellboy now?" He shook his head. He could see that these people had their hands filled with blood and its stench, much stronger and concentrated than his were.

He had killed many normal secret technique users in his previous world. Technically speaking they were just commoners and he was slightly stronger than them. These people said that they had killed totem users on par with them. They didn’t even mention about killing people not of their level or the commoners.

It was obvious that the amount would be a lot.

"I have got to give credit to the headquarters. They only have ten groups, yet the weakest one is already this strong." Garen felt emotional and he didn’t understand the intention of His Majesty placing him here. However, since the Secret Service had access to highly classified intelligence, he should be able to obtain some special intel regarding this world.

He memorized the map and left the room. As he was on his way out, he encountered a grey shirted lady pushing a cart, claiming to be the courier.

Garen gave her some tips and told her to help send the items to the rooms indicated on the map. The woman seemed to be very familiar with the place as she often sent packages around here. She happily accepted the request as she usually did this without getting pay.

Garen inquired about the setup of this place and found out that the place was built underneath a lake.

After finding out where the Archives and the Database were located, he decided to find out if they had any intel that he would find useful.

Although he was not satisfied with the attitude of the Red Team’s members, he didn’t take it to heart as he knew that it was normal for people to behave like so.

What he currently needed was the intel on removing the Crystal Derivator’s hidden problem. Although this item was no longer item he most relied on, it was still very useful so he didn’t want to simply give it up.

Furthermore, his ultimate objective was to try and find any information regarding the relationship between this world and the previous world.

There was still one year or two before the Kovitan Empire collapsed. Garen planned to settle everything for Hathaway, Goth and Prynne within this time frame. He wanted to compensate Acacia for lending his body to him by preparing a path for his relatives and close friends.

He would then focus all his energy into finding the secret between connecting this world and the previous one.

*******

In a distant land far away, there laid a tall black minaret that pierced through the clouds and beyond, shrouding the topmost parts of the building. .

Black smoke could be seen at the bottom of the tall minaret. The smoke morphed into the shape of a tall humanoid with black armor.

The humanoid looked at the minaret in front of it as the black smoke rotated around its body, forming a huge cloud vortex. Loud whistles of wind constantly travelled down to the ground.

"Is something wrong, Heiji?" A man's deep voice suddenly came from the minaret, as if the whole building was reverberating this sound.

The armored humanoid stood still with its head down as it paid respect towards the tower.

"There’s a new movement from the Terraflor Society. They seem to be nurturing a man called Beckstone."

"I know. We can just ignore him. Our current opponent is the Royal Alliance of Luminarists. The Three Departments are troublesome in their own way and the President is still asleep. We need to be more cautious as the time he awakens draws near. These three old men are no simple characters. We will have hope of overpowering them when the President successfully awakens and we no longer need to rely on creatures to contain them."

The man in the minaret explained.

"What about Marshall God Cloud? We have noticed that a General-class Crystal Derivator is acting strangely."

"Send a message to tell him to deal with it himself. We of the Black Sky are only in charge of monitoring them and are in no position to oversee the whole operation."

"What worries me is that we can’t get in touch with the General who is in charge of Kovitan. It may affect the whole plan." Heiji responded.

"It is the plan of Marshall God Cloud, not ours. Alright, we'll stop here today." The tower quietened down and no sound came from it afterward.

The black armored humanoid, too, dissolved into a pile of smoke and disappeared.

***********

Somewhere in the ruins of Daniela, a black unihorned creature was slowly moving among the ruins. The Unihorn Creature was carrying a purple haired woman who had an eyepatch on her. She had a red crystal ball floating in her palm, the surface was faintly glowing in red.

"Demetrius, are you able to get hold of Jess?" The Elemental General, Andora’s voice came from the ball.

"What’s wrong? Is there an emergency?" Demetrius gently comb her hair with her hand.

"The Black Sky said that Jess’s Derivator is broken. The general meant that it may be too late to change a new one as Kovitan is entirely in charge by Jess. Since you’re the only person who had seen Jess’s face and identity, the General wants you to go there by yourself. Since you still have another General there, you don’t need to worry about something happening at your place. That fellow hasn’t been contacting the other Generals in the area. Anyone would believe that he’s lost." Andora explained coldly.

"Alright. Intel says that he’s currently in the Kovitan’s Kingdom. Isn’t there already a General there? Furthermore the General from the Elite Squad is there as well. Please let them know of the situation since I’m not familiar with them."

"Alright, let me try and contact them."

Chapter 367: Exposed 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The information at the Archives had been moved to the Royal Secret Department. Garen, who just came out from the Wells Castle, was slightly disappointed to find out that the Secret Department’s wasn’t here, but on the other side of the Kingdom, which required a journey of half an hour.

He called a carriage and went back to his residence.

After ten minutes or so, he arrived the Blue Bay Manor.

As Garen was about to get down from the carriage, he saw two tall men with red shawls standing in front of his manor, and seemed to be inquiring Lala about something.

He squinted his eyes.

"Keep moving forward." He ordered the driver.

The driver looked at Garen skeptically and moved forward without asking further.

Garen acted as if he were passing by as he looked at the two of them through the window. As they left with the carriages and disappeared on the lane, he then ordered the driver to turn around and go back to his manor.

After getting down of the carriage and paying the driver, Garen walked towards Lala, who was standing in front of the entrance.

"Who are those two?"

"They claimed to be the guards of the princess and came to find you for something." Lala whispered. Her face was filled with suspicion. "They said that they want you to contact them immediately once you have returned."

Garen’s heart sank.

"I understand. You go do your stuff."

"Yes." Although Lala didn’t understand, she could see that Garen was unhappy and immediately turned away.

Garen walked into his own manor and passed through the guest room down to the open air garden in the middle and straight into the main living hall.

Without any hesitation, he walked into his own bedroom and pulled out a black box at a corner of a wall and opened the box with the key on his body.

Flopped, the black metal lock and box was opened, revealing the items inside.

Among the black ribbons laid a faintly glowing red Crystal Derivator.

A sentence was shown on its surface: You have five communication request, do you want to answer?

Garen took out the Crystal Derivator and let it floated on his hand.

He opened the communication request and they were the request of two upper class Generals and three middle class General. What a luxurious line up.

He clicked on an unknown name of an upper class General and answered the communication request.

The inner structure of the Crystal Derivator glew red and formed a vortex.

"Jess? Since when did you change your name? Garen? Isn’t this name…" A charming female voice came out from the Crystal Derivator. "Whatever, let’s not talk about this. Demetrius didn’t manage to get in touch with you. Is your Derivator broken? DIdn’t we just visit the Black Sky to fix it last time? You have been saying you have issues with your Derivator since last time."

Garen hesitated for a moment before purposefully simmering his voice coarsely.

"Are you Ann-Rue?" It was the name stated for the upper class General.

The opposing party was silent for a moment.

"That’s not it! You’re not Jess! Jess would never talk to me like that! Damn it! Who are you?!!" Ann-Rue went full rage as her voice were cold and rapid.

"I am jess, it’s just that my throat…"

"Don’t bother. Who are you? How dare you disguise yourself as upper class General Jess and infiltrate the Obscuro Society’s military. How did you find out about the secret code?" Ann-Rue’s tone was no longer charming and lazy, but cold and cruel instead.

"Whatever. There’s no point in asking this. Let me look at your empowered totem… Hmm… One humanoid and three spiritualized…. Three spiritualized Totems?!! Not bad eh kid." Ann-Rue’s tone became gentle all of the sudden.

"To be able to nurture three Spiritualized totems. This should be your main strength eh. Hehe, Garen… This name Garen, don’t tell me you’re the young Viscount from the Trejons Household?"

Garen was shocked at how sharp and quick witted the opponent was.

"Since you already know, what do you plan to do?"

Ann-Rue started laughing.

"Do you know that, the moment I report this to the higher ups, all your totems will be confiscated? Three of your spirtualized totem creatures that you nurtured so hard will become the property of others? And you yourself would be killed by them."

"What are you scheming?" Garen didn’t change his expression and reverted back to his original voice.

The opponent was quiet for a moment before she started to laugh again. "Since the Derivator is in your hands, it’s safe to assume that Jess is no longer alive. I really have no idea how you nurtured them, even I have only two spiritualized totem. Hmm… It’s rare to stumble upon a great thug. What should I do with you?"

"How about this, since I have an important task to do, I want you to be at the Vivian Garden located at the northern side of the Kingdom within 10 minutes. I will be waiting for you on a long chair by the roadside."

Garen put away the crystal ball and went out of the door without saying another word. He then rode his Aberrated horse, reserved for emergencies, and rushed towards the Kingdom.

It took Garen 9 minutes to reached Vivian Garden located in the northern side of town.

The garden was in complete silence, and so were his surroundings. Most of the trees inside had wilted, and there were only a few white jade sculptures in the middle. The circular garden wasn’t huge, and there was circular road with a row of long chairs beside them.

Garen took a turn and didn’t see anyone there.

"I have arrived, where are you?" He walked towards a corner where no one was present and took out the crystal as he asked.

"There’s a change of plans, you need to be at the Bernoulli Stone Bridge of the west in three minutes. Someone will naturally tell you what to do there." Ann-Rue answered lazily.

Garen squinted his eyes. "Are you messing with me? Bernoulli Stone Bridge is five kilometers away from here. The Kingdom doesn’t allow the use of a totem how do you expect me to reach there in time?!"

"It’s up to you if you want to go or not. Remember, you only have three minutes. If you’re late I will report you. If that happens, your empowered totem, including the girl you empowered would be gone. It’s your choice." Ann-Rue laughed coldly.

Without any hesitation, garen jumped onto his horse and rushed towards the west. Luckily, there weren’t many carriages on the street.

As he arrived at the Bernoulli Stone Bridge, he could only see a few homeless men sleeping by the bridge, no suspicious looking person was present.

Garen went to both ends of the bridge and didn’t see anyone.

"Alright, consider yourself passed. Next up.. Hmm… Let me think. Do you see that beggar who is sleeping underneath the sculpture on your left? Go hug her and tell her that you’re her long lost relative and you want to bring her home. Make sure you’re expressive okay~~" Ann-Rue yawned as she said so.

"Are you fucking around with me?!" Garen’s expression worsen as he looked at the beggar. Ignoring the ulcers covering her body, she reeked with foul odor, her hair was messy and saliva was dripping out from her mouth. Anyone would know that she was a mentally retarded idiot.

"I’m fucking around, did you only realize that?" Ann-Rue started laughing. "It should be time now, where the little girl in your manor had been captured by my men. Imagine your little empowered female servant was discovered by the Royal Alliance. Hehe, I wonder what will happen… The Royal Alliance will definitely see you as a traitor. What should you do~~ Oh so troublesome~~~"

"However, as long as you listen to me, I will not reveal your secret~~ As long as you’re obedient. Alright now follow what I just…"

"I found you." Garen suddenly smirked as he licked his lips.

"You?"

The Crystal Derivator instantly broke and became a pile of red dusts and Ann-Rue’s voice stopped coming out.

Garen put away his right hand as he rode his horse with his sight set at a certain direction on the left of the stone bridge.

Pew!

He immediately disappeared.

**************

Far away from the Bernoulli Stone Bridge, there was a tower in construction just beside the river which protected the city.

A woman in black skirt placed down the crystal ball in fear. She sensed that a horrifying threat was approaching her. This sensation was unique only to the Royal Household.

Her delicate face was filled with anxiety.

"Wade!"

"Yes Princess, do you have any orders?" A humongous yellow-copper colored man in armor kneel down and asked respectfully.

"We will change our holding area immediately. It’s no longer safe here. I keep having this sense of foreboding." The woman in black skirt held her chest as her face went pale.

It was as if the man’s voice in the crystal derivator was still ringing by her ears.

"Find me? What can you do if you find me? I have the Royal Knights protecting me. What can you, a totem user who had placed all your empowered totem outside of this area, do to me?!"

The black skirted woman started to feel calm as she comforted herself.

"Let’s go! Let’s leave this place." She stood up, took her purse and rushed down the spiral staircase. Without realizing it, she looked down from the tower.

She was instantly horrified.

A tall man in black shirt was grinning at him at the bottom of the tower. His white teeth gave off a sinister vibe. It was the ‘Jess’ that she saw at the Bernoulli Stone Bridge.

"Move! Quick!!" The black skirted girl started to panic and shouted loudly. She started to feel fear that she hadn’t known existed.

As the Royal member of the Kovitan Empire, they had a unique ability that was envied by everyone. It was the ability that to alert them to impending dangers.

This was the Kovitan Royal household’s predictive ability, or a gifted talent which was a special ability.

Every Royal member had different degrees to which they knew danger was coming, and this woman had lost her cool due to this.

***************

"This is Royal territory, no entry allowed!" Two heavily armored guards crossed their spears to block Garen’s path.

The two of them stood at the entrance of the tower and stared fiercely at Garen.

"Didn’t your princess invite me here?" Garen could hear their conversation clearly at the bottom of the tower.

"What uninteresting subordinates, what do you need them for?" He smiled gently.

Cha!!

The upper body of the guards instantly disappeared. It was as if they were bitten off by something invisible. The lower body stood still. Blood hadn’t even had the chance to move. The fresh blood from the remaining corpses slowly flowed down to the ground.

With a smile on his face, Garen walked into the white tower.

The corpses behind him fell onto the ground.

The passers by started shouting one after another as they saw the scene.

"Protect Her Highness!!!" A group of heavily armored guards started to gather.

A series of powerful totem powers appeared behind Garen. It was the totem powers of many form two totem users rushing into the tower. Their bodies were filled with many colors of totem light.

The narrow staircase in the tower couldn’t fit totem creatures with huge bodies, so the ones who entered were small totems with special abilities.

As Garen stepped onto the first layer of the staircase, he could feel that his speed had been slowed down. It was as if an invisible force field was affecting him and slowing his speed as a result.

"Delayed Superimposition!"

An old man with a grey beard walked down from above and stared coldly at Garen.

"How dare you kill the Royal Knight’s guard and disrupt the third princess’s rest. You should be punished with death!"

Chapter 368: Exposed 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This old man had a red crow perched in his shoulder, its eyes like black jewels staring at Garen darkly.

Garen felt this power curiously, raised his head and smiled at the old man.

Chack!!

Another set of invisible jaws snapped towards him.

The grey-bearded old man jumped back nimbly, a hint of sardonicism on his face. "Traceless and soundless, this ability is indeed impressive, but you shouldn’t have revealed him beforehand." He glanced at the surge of Royal Knights behind Garen, and waved.

"Step down, all of you, don’t disturb my deceleration force field. I’ll settle things here…"

Chack!!

Before he finished speaking, another pair of huge jaws bit down on him.

The old man’s expression changed, and he shook out a Tactic Chain, activating a red light on it but couldn’t wait for the red light to take effect.

There was a snapping at his waist, and he broke into two. His top half disappeared in an instant, together with the red crow, bitten off and swallowed by the invisible jaws.

Poof.

His lower half fell to the ground, blood and guts spilling onto the floor.

Garen moved his body.

"Deceleration force field, how useful. Even a body as powerful as mine can be affected by it."

He continued to walk upwards. He looked slow, but his speed was unnaturally fast.

"Protect Her Highness the Princess!!"

"Protect Her Highness with your life!"

The Royal Knights behind him pounced one by one, activating all sorts of abilities. Some used the same deceleration, some lit fires on their bodies, others increased their speed, or enlarged certain parts of their body and so on, but all their totem power was not enough to affect Garen’s steps.

The Totem Light around him forcefully kept all the ability attacks outside. Several shapeless jaws bit the Royal Knights chasing after him straight into two.

He didn’t like to eat the whole thing. Although the Salamander had this ability, once it ate the whole person, that meant it was eating humans as food, and not just killing. That wasn’t the feeling he wanted.

And people tended to have a lot of filth in their lower bodies, so Garen purposely avoided this part.

Wooo~~~~!!

Suddenly, there was a piercing siren in the air above the capital outside.

It was the piercing siren that only rang when there was an urgent attack from outside.

Garen dashed to the top of the tower in a few steps. There was nobody at all at the exit to the top of the tower, nothing at all.

Garen stood at the entrance to the stairs, took one look around him, and suddenly smiled slightly.

Huge unseen jaws instantly chomped forward.

Chack!!

The scenery around him rippled like water.

**********

The Third Princess, Ann-Rue, hurriedly walked onto the back of the huge green bird.

Behind her, the top of the tower was being wrapped up in a blood-colored ball of flesh. The flesh ball wriggled constantly, a wrinkled old woman floating beside it

Chack!!

A strange biting and chewing sound came from inside the flesh ball.

With the flinch of each bite, the old woman’s face grew paler, her originally rosy face growing whiter and whiter.

"Go!! Your Highness!" she yelled loudly and sternly. "I can’t hold on much longer!"

"Grandma Lina!" Ann-Rue turned around to look at the old woman, the struggle evident on her face.

"Go!!"

Ann-Rue clenched her teeth, and stepped on the large green bird under her feet.

The giant bird immediately spread its wings and flew off into the distance.

She turned around to look deeply at the flesh ball, as though looking through the flesh ball and seeing Garen inside.

"I’ll get you back for this!! Garen Trejons!" She clenched and gritted her teeth, her eyes filled with hatred. "Just you wait, you’ll be hunted down from both sides!! Everyone related to you, I’ll make sure to properly pass on your good deeds to them…"

"Unfortunately, you won’t have the chance to anymore." Suddenly, there was a casual voice by her ear.

Ann-Rue’s expression changed, and she jumped off the green bird without thinking.

Just as she leaped off the bird’s back.

The giant flesh ball on the top of the tower exploded instantly, and an invisible mouth flew out, biting down on the green bird in midair mercilessly.

The green bird emitted green electricity, fighting against the large jaws. It threw its head back and screeched sharply.

A large amount of green electricity covered the surface of the mouth, and finally revealed its features.

The large mouth was a huge, salamander-like head, but it was only a part of the top.

The giant salamander head had a long snake-like neck, stretching backwards into an unknown space, as though it was a powerful creature from another space, poking out from goodness knows where.

Just from the proportions of this salamander head alone, the length of this creature’s body would be a terrifying twenty meters or more. Otherwise, there was no way it could reach out to bite the green bird that had already flown out more than ten meters.

Hurr!!!

Suddenly there was a bolt of purple lightning from below, piercing right at the eye-catching huge salamander head.

The purple lightning was like a long spear, shooting out mercilessly, piercing accurately through the salamander head’s chin, and then emerging from the top of its skull.

Roarrr!!!

The Salamander screamed, and let go.

But by then, the back half of the green bird had already become a mess of blood and flesh, and it fell down from the sky heavily with a wail. With a whoosh, it became a stroke of silver light, flying back into Ann-Rue’s ring.

The long spear of purple lightning was shot with all the strength of Wade, Ann-Rue’s personal bodyguard. There was a pair of whisker-like purple wings sprouting out of his back, twisting rhythmically towards both sides, like two spreads of dense tree roots.

"Let’s see how you attack now!!" Wade looked up at the top of the tower, his expression cold and determined. This lightning spear was the result of his gathering all the power in his body, the strongest power he could muster.

As soon as the spear was shot out, even a Spiritualized Totem wouldn’t be able to take it. Once it hit the totem’s vital spots, the only end result would be utter disintegration.

This was the main reason he could become the Third Princess’ personal bodyguard, a defensive knight.

That was his Thunder God Spear, that had killed more battle-loving elite warriors than he could count on the battlefields of the past.

The Salamander did indeed grow quiet, and did not appear anymore.

"Is he dead?" Wade glanced around the top of the tower warily, but did not see anything suspicious.

"Leave that place!!" The Third Princess, Ann-Rue’s voice came from far behind him.

Wade was slightly confused, but still obeyed and retreated rapidly.

Chack!!

A huge pulling force appeared in the air in front of him, as though he was being swallowed by something in one gulp.

Wade’s expression changed.

"Wade!!"

He heard the Third Princess’ desperate yell, and then, there was no longer an ‘and then’. His vision went black, and he instantly sank into the endless darkness.

Garen’s body slowly landed where Wade was standing, and another large mouth swallowed Wade utterly.

"Tsk-tsk, what power, that one hit took out one of my heads, you know." Garen’s expression was appreciative. Unfortunately, the Eight Headed Dragon had extraordinary regenerative powers, and the destroyed dragon head quickly regrew. Those guards it had swallowed just now made the best nutrients.

Unless you destroyed all of the Eight Headed Dragons’ heads at once, there was no way to destroy the Eight Headed Dragon.

The ability to swallow unseen, terrifyingly formidable power, impressive elemental resistance, and Life Tear, the ridiculous ability that will boost its own life force.

This beast, evolved to the max, was practically the strongest war machine!

He looked at Ann-Rue, her face deathly pale in the distance. This Third Princess was currently backing up non-stop, looking panicked and terrified. She had immense power, but right now she was basically a little girl. She had a powerful totem but didn’t know how to use it, neither did she have the courage to fight. This was the condition of the current royal family, they had the power to fight, but didn’t have the corresponding guts and valor.

"How pathetic." Garen shook his head slightly. "Aren’t you an Elemental General? Where’s your totem? These subordinates dying to protect you are actually all a lot weaker than you. But they all have the courage to face a powerful opponent without backing down, what about you?"

Ann-Rue bit her lip. It was true, she barely ever left the capital, and the few times she had fought, she had always been protected by everyone else. Her battle experience was unbelievably bad.

She looked at the mess around her. Her power had more or less died out, her subordinates’ broken limbs were strewn everywhere, and it had taken barely a minute to create such a tragedy. The other person’s strength and cruelty were unbelievable.

"How boring." Garen was suddenly disinterested. "I thought it would be a fun battle." Looking at the terrified Princess Ann-Rue. He waved one hand.

A large mouth bit Ann-Rue mercilessly, picking her up.

Ahh!!

Ann-Rue screamed, and her eyes rolled back into her head. She had actually fainted from fright.

Garen glanced at the many shadows flying towards him rapidly in the distant sky. It was the capital’s reserve team of elite fighters, rapidly gathering.

"Less than a minute’s time, their reflexes are not bad."

With a whoosh of wind, he and Ann-Rue disappeared from the spot at the same time. All that could be seen was a shadow faintly ducking into a small street, and vanishing from sight. It was as fast as a phantom.

An Elemental General had high value in terms of intelligence. There was always that Lala to be found, so it was too early to kill her now.

Garen acted quickly this time, wearing his hood the whole time. Those who had seen him were all permanently silenced. The whole mission had taken less than two minutes. Even Garen himself was especially satisfied with how fast and how absolute it had been.

This mission had also, in a way, tested his current abilities.

During the mission, he had encountered Form Three totem users. There was that first grey-bearded old man, who was eaten instantly. And then there was that old lady, she seemed to be connected to her core totem somehow. When the illusory flesh ball was punctured, that old hag was also torn to pieces.

As for that last one, Wade, his electric spear was indeed impressive, to think it could take down one of the Eight Headed Dragon’s heads. Just as a Spiritualized totem user, it was something for him to be proud of.

This had also exceeded Garen’s expectations. He didn’t think that one Third Princess would have such powerful protective knights. Although the royal family was corrupt, looks like it still had decent power.

Moving quickly through the streets, Garen moved at high speed, quietly and unseen, even the smell of his body gathered completely.

This time, he didn’t want to be prematurely exposed, he hadn’t wanted to solve this matter so impulsively either, but since he’d done it, he needed to consider all the possible results.

Chapter 369: Mastermind 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Dragging the Third Princess behind him, Garen didn't stop for anything, quickly returning to the bridge, and riding his own horse casually as he rushed back to his estate. Besides, the Third Princess was being held in the Salamander’s mouth, still unconscious.

He wasn't panicked either.

Riding his horse from afar, he saw the area around the tower surrounded by many troops. Several characters with impressive auras appeared one after the other, observing the situation.

Garen even pretended to be a passerby, walking past the scene.

One of the leaders was a red-haired man wearing a white cape, crouching on the ground where Wade had disappeared and checking the traces.

Two guards were beside him reporting the situation, and there was a circle of guards in half body suits of white armor, sealing away the scene.

There was even a group of spectators surrounding them, speculating away and sounding like a swarm of flies on a pile of rotten meat, buzzing.

Garen rode his horse and passed the scene slowly.

"Tsk-tsk… How terrible, not even one survivor." He acted like an ignorant passerby, tut-tutting at the scene.

"What do you mean, dear sir, you don't know. I came here as soon as I heard the sounds, but once I got here, I saw that the killing was already over. I didn't see the killer, but all this blood on the floor… Tsk-tsk…" A fat merchant was also passing by on a single-seater carriage, looking at the scene just like Garen.

"Aren't you afraid of getting involved?" Garen glanced at this man.

"Of course! Why wouldn't I be afraid? But my biggest hobby is to stick my nose into other people's business, as long as I find a safe space, I won't have to be worried about anything." The fatty waved his hand.

Garen shook his head, and rode his horse casually past. Looking at the White Cape’s expression of confusion, his heart lightened up.

Without making any stops along the way, Garen returned to his own estate.

As expected, Lala was gone.

He carefully avoided everyone's gazes, calmly walking into the estate and closing the room door behind him. He then pulled that person out of the Dragon's mouth, carrying the Third Princess in one hand and closing the windows with the other.

After checking all the doors and windows carefully, he was satisfied that they were all tightly sealed shut.

Garen carried the Third Princess and walked down into the secret basement. The first thing he saw was Komodo, panting in the entrance to the tunnel, his expression panicked and his body plastered to the wall as though he was hiding from something.

He held an iron shovel in his hand, and was shocked when he heard footsteps, so he raised the shovel and smashed it down at Garen’s direction.

"Look before you smash!" Garen pinched the shovel with a smack, glaring at him coldly.

Komodo instantly widened his eyes.

"Aw mah gawd! Aw mah gawd!! Master, you’ve finally come home! Miss Lala was taken away!" Komodo’s expression was that of intense relief. He looked strong on the outside, and was rather large-sized, but in truth he was extremely cowardly and afraid of dying.

"Move aside!" Garen pushed him away, carrying the unconscious Third Princess with one hand and striding down the corridor.

When he reached the corner of the second corridor, he slapped the wall on his right with his palm, and just happened to hit a palm-shaped dent.

Clack-clack-clack…

There were crisp sounds behind him, and the two black-purple metal walls came down over the entrances, sealing the corridor away.

"Master, what are you doing?" Komodo followed behind Garen, confused. He had also noticed the woman Garen was carrying in his hand.

"Before I finish my business here, no one is allowed to enter. That includes you," Garen replied mildly.

Komodo immediately gave a shudder of fright, and didn’t say anything more.

The two of them descended rapidly, one after the other, and soon reached a lab that wasn’t very big.

Throwing Princess Ann-Rue inside, Garen adjusted the passcodes in the room. In the whole underground, there was one extra-secure room like this one, secured with five chain wheels. Therefore, it could be arranged into five digits, so after setting up five different numbers, he could properly secure the room.

Garen turned to the correct passcode, and walked inside.

"Komodo, you go take care of those survivors from the experiment, don’t interrupt me unless there’s something important."

Komodo blinked, and put on a suggestive expression.

"Alright, Master. I’ll make sure no one disturbs you!" he guaranteed loudly.

Garen was too lazy to bother with what he was thinking, and slammed the door shut.

The secret room was a bit like a huge tent, the top was rounded to a tip, and the area in the center was cylindrical.

There was pale yellow light in the room, and a large fire basin hanging above, illuminating the room in place of a lamp. The red flames in the fire basin leapt non-stop, coloring the ceiling a total black-red.

Garen reached out to turn some switches on the wall next to the door, adjusting the flames in the fire basin lamp.

There were two lonely black sofas in the secret room, and a red-brown compound shelf in the corner. There were nine shelves in total, and two of those shelves were even open.

Garen walked to the sofa and sat down, quietly waiting for Princess Ann-Rue to wake up. At the same time, he organized his situation now.

"I got rid of the witnesses properly, that area is under the Royal Family’s patrol, and passersby might have seen the color of my clothes, but even then they surely only caught a glimpse from afar, and couldn’t see the patterns clearly. Judging from the reaction from the Royal Family just now, they shouldn’t have found any effective clues."

Garen caressed his stubble lightly, his long blonde hair reflecting a mysterious golden-red under the firelight.

"I have no choice but to give up on the Crystal Derivator, since it could be taken over and controlled by Obscuro, I might as well release the three Spiritualized Petrifying White Dragons, rather than just hand them over." He lifted the Crystal Derivator, and suddenly remember that this Third Princess should have one with her too.

He stood up directly, and walked up to Ann-Rue, who was lying on the ground. He crouched down next to her and started pressing around her body, quickly discovering her Crystal Derivator in a small pouch behind her waist.

Garen didn’t even look at it, pinching it into pieces with a snap.

The broken crystal shards scattered everywhere.

He directly took all the little pouches Ann-Rue carried with her off, and poured all the bulging contents onto the sofa. He then stripped the totem storage tool off of her.

There was a red scroll, tied neatly with silver string, but he didn’t know what it was for.

Two black crystal storage rings, a small makeup mirror. And some tiny shards of red and blue gems.

Lastly there was a glass flesh-colored tube that looked like lipstick, he could see sticky flesh-colored liquid shaking slightly inside.

Garen looked at the label on the glass tube, slightly curious.

‘Aer Chest Enhancement Oil, Specifically for Royalty’

He glanced at Ann-Rue’s chest somewhat at a loss for words. It was flat as a pancake, with only the slightest suspicion of a bump…

He didn’t waste any time keeping the ring and rubies, as well as the scroll, all into his own bag. Garen sat back onto the sofa, and waited quietly.

He had just killed so many totem user guards and three Form Three totem users, one of them was even Spiritualized.

Garen couldn’t count the total number closely either, so he settled his heart to check how many potential points he had earned.

‘Power 14. Agility 3.11. Vitality 10. Intelligence 2.53. Potential 5528%. Has Luminarist quality.’

"Only 55 potential points?" Garen frowned, this might even include the few potential points he had left before.

The Petrifying White Dragons kept hunting for him, amassing many potential points, to the point where Garen nearly forgot how hard it was to earn potential points.

He killed many powerful entities this time, and still only earned fifty-five potential points. The Petrifying White Dragons had collected so many before, more than four hundred, who knows how many monsters they had to massacre to get so many.

"I had so many potential points before, so although fifty-five points is already a lot, it just feels rather underwhelming." Garen was slightly self-deprecating, over four hundred potential points had spoiled his sense of judgment.

Looking at his attributes, his agility was still only at 3.11.

It was just nice that these attribute points could be all added to his attributes.

Garen immediately moved his gaze to stare at Agility, and his potential points dropped like a stone.

At first, one potential point could increase his agility attribute by 0.1.

Soon enough, after using almost twenty potential points on his agility, he increased it to five attribute points. In an instant, he required 20 potential points to increase his attribute by one.

After increasing his agility to 6 points, Garen stopped immediately. Looking at the dozen or so potential points he had left, he shook his head rather helplessly.

He used his potential points up too quickly. He hadn’t even considered adding more secret techniques.

Garen thought about it, and the three red dots on his forehead immediately lit up with a red light, a small, shrunken version of the Eight Headed Dragon totem materializing behind him.

The meat lump that formed the ninth head on the totem’s back had clearly grown a lot bigger.

Evidently, the change in attributes had a certain effect on its growth, it was just that he still didn’t know when it could grow its ninth head.

Garen really anticipated this. Be it in the legends of Earth, or those of the Secret Technique World, there were stories about the Nine Headed Hydra. They were each different, so he was really excited to see what heights the totem that began as a Dual Headed Salamander would morph into at the final stage.

With six in agility, he felt his body grow a lot lighter, the lines of his body also evened out. Whenever he lifted his arms or legs, it felt as though the air automatically gave way.

It was a very strange feeling, and somewhat intoxicating.

Garen felt the changes in his body carefully, and lost track of time.

"Mm…"

After staying unconscious for no one knows how long, Princess Ann-Rue finally frowned, and slowly woke up on the floor.

"Where is this? My head hurts so bad… Wei Xi! Wei Xi!! Bring me a cup of Active Water." She didn’t seem to have a grasp of the situation yet, and after calling what seemed to be the name of a maid a few times, this spoiled princess finally woke up, and glanced at Garen on the sofa. She quickly covered her chest, and shrank into the corner of the wall.

"You!! It’s you! What are you planning!? I’m warning you! I’m the Third Princess of the Kovistan Royal Family! Once he realizes I’m missing, my father the King will definitely send out the strongest Royal Knights out searching everywhere, you’d better release me now! I can pretend nothing happened. Otherwise, you’ll definitely be dismembered! You’ll be staked! Fed to the dogs alive!"

This poor thing was so scared her face was white, her expression that of terror. Even then, she was threatening Garen loudly.

"Poor thing. You still don’t know what situation you’re in now?" Garen stood up, playing with the unknown scroll in his hand. "Now tell me, what is the scroll in my hand here for?"

Chapter 370: Mastermind 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ann-Rue swallowed, and was already shrunk into the corner.

"Why should I tell you!?"

As though thinking she was acting too weak. She instantly puffed out her chest.

"I advise you to let me go as soon as possible, or else once they realize you did it, even I wouldn’t be able to keep it under wraps! Be it the Royal Family or Obscuro, they’re not people you can afford to piss off!"

Garen was at a loss for words, shaking his head and laughing.

"Are you really so stupid or just pretending? I killed so many people of yours, and you’re still hoping I will let you go?"

Bam!!

He kicked Ann-Rue’s waist mercilessly.

The golden Totem Light fought against the black Totem Light on his foot, spraying out small flecks of black and gold light. The many flecks scattered onto the ground, and rapidly disappeared.

"Ahh!!!" Ann-Rue screamed loudly, her whole body kicked to the wall, the golden Totem Light on her body dimming significantly.

"Speak, what is this thing?"

"It’s… it’s, it’s a sealed scroll!! It’s sealed with three shots of Wade’s Thunder God Spear!!!" Ann-Rue was utterly terrified, and immediately spilled everything.

"Tsk-tsk, such a powerful item, and you kept it with you without daring to use it, just watching as I killed off your beloved subordinates. I finally understand how stupid you are." Garen was in awe.

Three shots of the Thunder God Spear, if used well, would be completely enough to wound him slightly and put his guard up.

Looking at the piece of crap in front of him, a hint of ruthlessness flashed past Garen’s eyes. She was useless alive anyway, so he might as well get rid of her.

"No!! Don’t kill me! Don’t kill me! I don’t want to die! I know a huge secret! You’ll definitely be interested in it, don’t kill me!!" Ann-Rue immediately sensed the possible danger, and instantly closed her eyes, screaming.

"Secret?" Garen kept pulled back his hint of killing instant, rather surprised at how sensitive Ann-Rue was to danger. "Tell me, if it’s not worth any money, you know the consequences."

"It’s a secret to do with the Endor precious heirlooms!!" Ann-Rue immediately said it without hesitation. "You’ll definitely be interested in it, it’s the Endor heirlooms! Legend has it each heirloom has the power to reach the skies and split the earth!! As long as you don’t kill me, I’ll immediately tell you everything I know!"

Endor!

Garen’s heart gave a jolt. Although he didn’t show a thing on the surface, his heart was already extremely shocked.

In his previous life, he had entered and left the Endor ruins multiple times, so he heard a lot about this old and mysterious civilization. To think that even in this world, he could still hear rumors of this civilization.

"Are you sure it's the Endor heirlooms?" He raised his voice and asked, this secret room was completely soundproof anyway, so he didn't have to worry about his voice getting out.

"Of course, I'm a hundred percent sure!" Ann-Rue hurriedly answered like a chick pecking at rice, "It's just that… just that…"

"Just what?"

"It's just that this precious heirloom was made when Father called strong fighters from all over to mimic it, but it's definitely a masterpiece that's the closest to the Endor heirlooms! Believe me! I've seen what it can do!" Ann-Rue hastened to add.

Garen faintly sensed that Ann-Rue’s words contained a territory he had never experienced before -- precious heirlooms.

"Tell me properly what these heirlooms are. How are they divided?"

Ann-Rue nodded quickly.

"Most people don't really know about precious heirlooms, only the people at the very top know about these secrets." She paused, and seeing that Garen didn't look at all impatient, she grew slightly braver, getting up and crawling to the wall.

"Precious heirlooms were originally found by a totem user scholar, in a certain set of ruins. They're mysterious tools with special abilities. These are the Original Heirlooms, four in total, one here in our Kovistan, one in Daniela, and two others currently missing. Father thinks they might have been lost to the West Continent or towards the Archipelago.

"Get to the point." Garen hastened her with a frown.

Ann-Rue was so scared her whole body shook, and she quickly spoke faster.

"Precious heirlooms can be divided into three levels, the Original Heirlooms, the Ultimate Heirlooms that mimic the Original Heirlooms, and the Regular Heirlooms that mimic the Ultimate Heirlooms. Most powers have the Regular Heirlooms, some just have more than others, even the totem storage tool is an Heirloom technique.

And Ultimate Heirlooms were passed down from the golden age of Heirlooms five hundred years ago, so there are exceedingly few of them. Now, only a few main powers have the ability to create them. Their strength is obviously more powerful, for example the two Grand Duke families in the Kingdom both have one Ultimate Heirloom each. And then there are the Original Heirlooms, also known as the Endor heirlooms, the strongest tools in legend, there are only two in the East Continent."

"How strong are they?" Garen said evenly.

"Original, Ultimate, Regular, the three levels are only general ratings, since their abilities are different, it's hard to decide how their powers stack up against each other, they're all grades according to how rare they are, how widely they can be used and their uses. The order of precious heirlooms also depends a lot of the influence of the wielder. If someone can make full use of a precious heirloom, this heirloom would naturally be placed higher and graded better." Ann-Rue hastily revealed everything she knew.

"But the Original are definitely the strongest, without a doubt," she added on.

"Then where is the Original Heirloom in Kovistan now? What's it called, what can it do?" Garen asked the key of the matter.

Ann-Rue hesitated for a moment.

"Kovistan’s Original Heirloom is called Caesarton, its ability is Absolute Protection. Since Father took the throne, he's always been wearing it on his finger. As for its power… Once, three Spiritualized totem users used their strongest attacks on him at once, and Father was still unharmed."

Garen's heart gave a little jolt.

His Majesty Avic was just a normal person, to think he could use this precious heirloom to fight against three Spiritualized totem users.

"Wait! His Majesty Avic isn't a totem user, is he?" he suddenly noticed the key to the question.

Ann-Rue’s gaze was complicated as she nodded.

"Yes, Father is just a normal person. The strongest point of the Endor heirlooms, is that even normal people can use them."

Garen instantly fell silent.

The secret room sank into a long silence, neither of them spoke.

After a long time, Garen completely accepted this unbelievable fact, and finally looked at Ann-Rue, her expression full of fear and respect, again.

"Then do you know exactly how many elite fighters there are in the Kovistan palace?"

Ann-Rue shook her head.

"I don't know, everyone hidden very, very well. In the palace or even in the whole Kingdom, the stupidest thing to do is to completely reveal your own power, that'll bring death upon your head. So I don't know how many powerful people there are either. Father’s thoughts run deep, I have no idea how many secrets he's hiding."

Garen arranged the information he just got.

"What about Obscuro? Aren't you one of Obscuro’s Elemental Generals? Why do you want to assassinate Avic? Doesn't he have Absolute Protection?"

"It's precisely to get Absolute Protection. Firstly, this Endor heirloom has no attack power whatsoever. Secondly, it can choose some trusted person and lower the defenses against that person. This requires a Ritual of Trust信任仪式, and the trusted person will also be protected by the Heirloom’s power. And of all the concubines in the harem, only the First Concubine Delouse will soon receive Father's total trust, with the Ritual of Trust in the works. Delouse gave Father three sons and a daughter. Twice she saved Father from a serious loss.The moment Delouse’s Ritual of Trust succeeds, that will be the moment of Avic’s death!" Ann-Rue's voice deepened without her knowing.

It was hard to imagine, the internal conflict among the Royal Family had already reached such a cruel state. His own daughter wanted her father to die as soon as possible.

"What about you? As a royal princess, why are you willing to join the Obscuro Society?" Garen looked at this woman of paradoxes, both cowardly and cruel, and couldn't help but ask.

"Me?" Ann-Rue gave a chilling smile. "Can you.imagine how a daughter feels when her father has taken her to bed since she was ten years old? Out of the twelve princesses and royal daughters, the first eight took turns entertaining Father in bed every night. As for the other four, perhaps they were too far away, or maybe there was some other reason, maybe because they were too young, only then did that beast reluctantly let them go. He liked to play like that."

She looked at Garen without shame, the sorrow of throwing it all to the sails in her eyes.

"To outsiders, it looks like we the twelve royal daughters are much beloved by the king, but in truth this love had a reason."

Garen fell silent, he found it hard to believe that King Avic was secretly such a perverted and shameless person.

"Before having us, that beast first chose wives of different looks and auras, his real aim wasn't these concubines, but us, born to those concubines. He is such a pervert! My mother was starved to death in the palace thanks to him, the only reason being she broke a crystal glass."

Now that Ann-Rue had said it all, she felt relief instead, as though she had put down a heavy burden and was all the lighter for it.

"Anything else you want to ask?"

Garen glanced at this pitiful woman,

"That's alright, I know everything I want to now."

"Oh, yeah, I kept that maid of yours in the Nongarde Villa, you go look for her yourself." Ann-Rue has also guessed that there was no way Garen would let her go, so she closed her eyes. "Make it quick."

Garen released a long breath, and his right hand shot out like lightning.

Psst!

The moment her Totem Light blocked it, it was immediately pierced through, and his finger accurately pierced into Ann-Rue’s forehead.

A fountain of blood and brain fluid sprayed out of the back of Ann-Rue's head, splattering onto the walls behind.

With a whump, Ann-Rue slid to the ground softly.

"Pitiful woman, pitiful royalty." Garen shook his head, the perverse inner nature the Royal Family had earned his eye as well. Such a Royal Family was beautiful on the outside but rotten on the inside, although Avic was particularly kind to his ministers and acted like a breath of fresh air, towards his own family he was unusually cruel. And his largest weak point just happened to be with his family.

In the original history, the Kovistan empire was headed towards becoming one of the strongest countries in the East Continent after he ascended the throne, but then it abruptly collapsed. This was probably the main reason.

Chapter 371: Setting Off 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Looking at Ann-Rue’s corpse, Garen raised and waved his hand. With a whoosh, an invisible pair of jaws immediately swallowed up the entire corpse.

"This is the perfect way to dispose of bodies, huh." Satisfied, he turned around and left the secret room.

After that, it was time to consider Obscuro’s reaction.

Killing an Elemental General-level spy would evidently be dealing a huge blow to Obscuro’s plans. But they probably didn’t know for sure who killed her, and Jess’s and Ann-Rue’s crystal balls were shattered on the same day at the same time, so they would probably think both Generals were killed at the same time.

He had no way of gauging their general reaction, but Garen wasn’t too worried about their revenge. While the Kingdom was still the Royal Alliance’s territory, Obscuro wouldn’t dare to make a careless move.

Putting aside the Secret Service’s strong teams in charge of the Kingdom’s safety, these were just the forces lurking in the dark, there were still the national departments on the surface, and the strongest of them, the branch of Silver Knights, was also based in the Kovistan Kingdom. There weren’t many members in this powerful and mysterious squad, but each member was definitely the cream of the crop. Together with the Secret Service, one in the dark and the other in the light, they were top-grade guards in charge of the entire Kingdom.

Garen wasn’t very familiar with the last one, the Geometry Service, but it was an even more mysterious department. What techniques they had in there, what power, nothing at all was known.

The three departments had their own duties, like three countries within a larger country, and each had a territory of their own. They represented the alliance of power between the high nobles in each country. They were the most basic of the Royal Alliance’s roots.

But even he could get rid of Princess Ann-Rue in the blink of an eye, so it was still better to be careful with these things.

"In the Kingdom now, the three departments, Obscuro, and members of the royal are all mixed together, so the situation is rather complicated... Right now I’m in the Secret Service, so Obscuro probably wouldn’t dare to make an obvious move. Besides, they don’t know my identity either, so there shouldn’t be a problem. Now I should first go on quests to increase and fill up my attribute points, so first I’ll have to reach the level of the Nine Headed Hydra."

He settled his heart, with his hidden ability.

Putting aside the Eight Headed Dragon on the surface, which was a Form Four Totem and had unique, powerful abilities, there was also the true form he hid away deep, that was an even stronger existence. There was no need at all for him to worry like he used to.

On the other hand, there were the two precious heirlooms Ann-Rue was talking about, one was Absolute Protection, resting on the king’s finger, the Endor Heirloom. The other was a forged heirloom, it was definitely a lot weaker in power, but it should still be pretty decent. After all the Ultimate Heirlooms were the second level items, if they were worth so many people forging them so whole-heartedly, their power naturally wouldn’t be weak.

He was indeed somewhat tempted. But once he remembered the mixed up powers in the Kingdom now, he decided that it was best not to get involved before the situation cleared up.

"Forget it, I’ll just mess around in the Secret Service for a while for now, I better not join in the assassination matter, I’ll just focus on getting my potential points." Garen made his decision, and didn’t think any more of it.

After that, he quickly went to the Villa Ann-Rue mentioned, and saved Lala, who was kept there.

He didn’t try to explain anything to her, and Lala seemed very calm as well, this girl seemed to have gotten calmer over her journey with Garen.

Returning to the estate quietly, Garen returned to his consistent lifestyle from before. Waiting for his time to go on a quest to arrive.

********************

Deep in the Kingdom’s Palace, in an extravagant white bedroom.

The number one concubine was a cold woman with a slender figure and golden curly hair. Right now, she was wearing a tight white dress, revealing her perfect curves as she stood in front a huge dressing mirror.

The two maids behind her were arranging her golden hair into cylindrical curls, layering these curls and weaving them into beautiful cylinders that looked like gold jewelry.

The large amount of long golden hair was woven into curls, bouncing occasionally as Concubine Delouse moved.

"Your Excellency, Lady Red Chrysanth’s Derivator was destroyed." A maid moved her lips, but her voice went straight into the First Concubine’s ear. She lowered her head and combed the golden hair, as though she was completely focused and had no other thoughts.

Delouse narrowed her eyes.

"What happened? What about Theta? Wasn’t he guarding Red Chrysanth?"

"Theta is dead. Everyone around Red Chrysanth was attacked at the White Bird Tower at about ten in the morning today. Red Chrysanth’s whereabouts are unknown, the rest all perished in the line of duty." The maid picked up a black forehead crown and put it on for the concubine.

Delouse mused slightly. "Red Chrysanth’s Derivator was destroyed, and I just received the news that Jess’s Derivator is broken as well. It can’t be a coincidence. Inform Black Sky, find out what actually happened."

"Yes."

"From now on, don’t tell me about the Military matters, just send it directly to God Cloud’s side. Be careful, make sure that old man Veska doesn’t notice."

"Understood. The Defense Minister went patrolling at the front lines today." The maid winked, and smiled.

******************

Several tens of thousands of kilometers away from the Kingdom, in a pitch-black underground cave.

Suddenly, the silver color on the walls of the cave wriggled, dripping down like sticky liquid, and landed with a few splatters.

These silver liquids wriggled slowly, quickly becoming a complete humanoid shape, looking like a clear human figure made of mercury.

It had no features, its face was flat, but its figure and all that were properly shaped, so it looked just like a silver statue.

This was a woman’s figure with large breasts and long, long hair. She walked slowly to the center of the cave.

"Respected His Excellency God Cloud, Delouse sends news, two of the Elemental Generals had their Crystal Derivators destroyed at the same time, so she needed to ask people from Black Sky to investigate this matter.

She was the only person in the cave, there was absolutely no one else, but then a sound came from the cave ceiling.

The silver cave walls actually started wriggling and bulged into a huge silver face. It was a man’s clear face, only its eyes were two dark and empty holes.

"I already know about this. The people from Black Sky have made a conclusion, Kovistan will temporarily be under the Elite Department and Delouse to handle, those two are both dead. Someone actually dares to publicly attack my people. Anya, which generals are closest to the Kingdom these days?"

"There’s Sindre in charge of Kevita Area, and there’s Ariel, who’s fighting with the national department of Silver Knights now. Add Delouse, and that’s all the existing power we have in Kovistan." The silver woman replied respectfully. "In order to raid the Geometry Service’s Blood Tower, we incurred heavy losses this time, three generals were weakened and died."

"But the situation in Ender has been completely stabilized, hmph! That Blood Tower fellow, if it weren’t that I’m at a critical moment now and can’t get away… The situation now is very complicated, Ann-Rue had no ability to resist whatsoever, and Jess had disappeared since Iron Tank City, her Derivator was always being used by an outsider. To the Black Sky, we the God Cloud Military Department have become a laughing stock! Our own General’s Derivator was being used by an outsider for so long and we had no idea."

The silver face grew darker.

"But to be able to kill Ann-Rue without getting even a scratch, this person must have more than Spiritualized power, they probably have the Fourth Form. you send Demetrius over, Sindre and Ariel will be the captain, that thing doesn’t have to be returned for you, just go over there and destroy the fellow impersonating Jess. I allow her to mobilize all the power there as long as they’re outside the plan. Also, Black Sky will send you some information and characteristics of the killer."

"I will convey your wishes immediately." The silver woman bowed lightly, and dissolved into a puddle of silver liquid with a patter.

*******************

Several days later, Kovistan Kingdom

Behind the Kingdom, leaning closely beside the tallest building, the clock tower, there was a grey-black stone cliff.

The cliff was covered with a dense green forest. When seen from afar, it was like swathes of green moss covering the cliff.

Amidst these dense trees, beside a clear lake, there were several figures in black.

Amongst them were an elderly, a child, two young girls, and two young men. There were six people in total.

The golden noon sunlight shone down from above the forest, reflecting truly golden sunlight on the surface of the lake, so much that it was slightly blinding.

The six of them wore uniform black dresses of armor, wearing hoods so their faces weren’t clear, only revealing their different figures and a little bit of skin.

"Have everything with you?" Old Man asked softly. "The place we want to go to this time is somewhere the Black Prince will certainly cross. At the same time, other than this quest, we have another newly-arrived quest, we need to settle then on the way. Nineheads, you say it."

A young man with balanced proportions nodded his head, it was a gently smiling Garen. His long blonde hair leaked slightly out of the hood, while his face was completely hidden in the shadow of the hood. Like the others, everyone’s faces seemed slightly blurry and distorted, it seemed to be an automatic effect of the armor.

Garen cleared his throat.

"Yesterday there was more news from upstairs, it came from the Deputy Director.

In the area where our quest is, an upper noble sent out an SOS, they hope we can go lend them a hand, we just need to kill the monsters surrounding him."

"More upper nobles again, how troublesome." One of the two girls, Kitten, pursed her lips disinterestedly. "Every time we go for a quest, we need to help someone on the way, they really do take us for free labor!"

"It’s on the way anyway, we go straight to our destination, and then come straight back, it won’t take any time. The other party only has two people."

Garen smiled.

"I’m fine with it." Red Umbrella crossed his arms over his chest, and was even yawning.

"I’m the same as Big Bro Red Umbrella." The Kid always followed Red Umbrella.

As for Fox, she usually didn’t speak.

"Then it’s decided." Old Man took out the map, and spread it open. He pointed at a newly added red dot with his finger. "Remember this place, when we’re there we just need to clean up the monsters there as we go. Let’s give this to Kid. Anybody have any objections?"

"Whatever, Kid needs more quest points now anyway, I’m fine with giving it to him." Kitten’s tone was decent for once.

Nobody else had any other opinions.

"Then thank you, big brothers and big sisters." Kid smiled as he thanked them.

Garen glanced at Kid curiously. This little fella who was only half his height couldn’t have been older than thirteen or fourteen, yet he had such good connections within the team.

Chapter 372: Setting Off 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After staying in the estate for a few days, Garen hadn’t received any news.

But now, it was finally time to go on a quest.

Everyone in the Secret Service’s Crimson Team, under Old Man’s arrangements, had gathered at a fixed place, that was the large clock tower, the tallest building just behind the Kingdom.

This was the stone wall of a cliff, with some green forests on top, and a small lake.

"Alright, let’s go down." Old Man nodded, and led the way to the outskirts of the jungle.

The others followed suit.

Garen followed at the very back of the team, not too fast or too slow, carefully scoping his surroundings.

All the trees in the forest were rather short, and a glance over them showed they were sparse as well, sunlight falling onto the green blanket of plants, shining with a jade green glow.

The six of them entered the little forest one by one, and walked straight to the edge of the cliff.

Old Man led the way, and actually turned his step, walking down the edge of the cliff as though he’d just jumped off. It gave Garen quite a scare.

And others followed suit, Garen the last, all the way until he reached the edge of the cliff, where he looked down.

There were many intricate black boxes built on the cliff under him, each smaller than a palm. That was when he noticed that there was actually a downward sliding staircase on the cliff beside his feet. Ahead of them, Old Man had already gone quite a distance ahead.

The stone steps stuck tightly to the cliff, like trenches dug out of the black cliff, going all the way down.

Garen glanced at Fox, who was beside him. She didn't look surprised in the slightest, and as evidently used to seeing this kind of thing.

He hurriedly followed them down, following the stone steps one by one as they advanced towards the bottom right.

Holding the black stone handle on the left with his hands, he felt a cold touch coming from his palm, and Garen continued down the steep stone steps.

On the left side of the stone stairs tunnel, a lot of cold wind due to the high altitude was blowing in, billowing up their hoods and making them flutter.

The six of them didn't say a thing, walking down quietly.

On the black cliff walls, the stone steps were like a split, stretching from the top of the cliff to the center.

The six of them walked on the inside, like black ants crawling in the crack, soundlessly, inconspicuous.

After about two minutes.

The path ahead them opened up, into a wide circular hall. On the ground in the center was a huge bird's nest, more than ten meters in radius.

The bird's nest was woven out of dried, earth-yellow tree trunks, oval in shape, and had a giant black bird crouched in the middle. The bird looked like an enlarged version of a crow, completely pitch black, with only scarily pearly yellow eyes, glimmering in the dim cave with a yellow glow.

The giant bird was more than seven meters long, crouching quietly in the nest, and it actually had a natural dent in its back.

Old Man walked over first, the black light patterns under his feet disappearing after a flash. With a ding, his whole person leaped up lightly, as though he had springs on his feet. While in mid-air, the black light formation at his feet lit up again, propelling him directly into the dent on the bird's back.

"Everyone gets a Black Crow each, the ones at the back, make sure you don't get left behind." He yelled loudly from that height.

In an instant, everyone walked towards the edges of the cave and walls, and saw that there were tunnels leading to other caves.

Garen chose one and walked over too, after following the tunnel for a bit, he found another huge Black Crow crouched in their nest. The Black Crow glanced at him, a hint of viciousness in its yellow eyes, but it immediately sensed the special aura on Garen and instantly calmed down.

Garen touched the diamond shard ring on his hand, the ring was made from a black metal, and had four diamond shards embedded in it to form a diamond shape.

"As expected of the three departments, they sure have many good things."

Garen touched his ring, and the same black light formation flashed past his feet as well, like a trampoline, exploding with a light and gentle bounce.

Borrowing this power to jump into the sky, Garen took another step in mid-air, the black light formation circle flashed again, and he landed lightly in the dent on the crow’s back.

The dent was warm, and the area under his feet was soft, the swathes of feathers in front of him functioning as grips.

"Nineheads, you ready?"

Old Man’s voice came from his waist-pouch.

Garen opened the pockets on his waist, and took out a small round black box, the voice was coming from here.

"Ready," he replied softly.

"It’s your first time riding a Black Crow, watch your safety, and always keep in contact," Old Man advised him.

"Why are you bothering with him, if he doesn’t even know that much, he should just scram!" For some reason Kitten just didn’t seem to like Garen very much, and kept geting annoyed at him.

"Then let’s go," Old Man agreed.

Garen patted the yellow diamond ring on his hand, and the Black Crow under his feet gave a slight jolt.

The Black Crow stood up in the nest, and started running urgently forward.

Tap-tap-tap!

After taking a few steps, the way forward lit up with a white light.

Whoosh!

That was the sound of the Black Crow opening its wings, its huge wings spanning more than ten meters as it pounced out of the cave.

On the black cliffs, six Black Crows rushed out of the cave one after the other, and flapped their wings, shooting into the sky. They created six round flight paths in the sky.

Woooo~~~~! Haha!!

Kitten’s whoops came from the left.

Garen’s eyes got used to the sudden burst of blinding sunlight, facing the strong winds as he narrowed his eyes to look around him.

He felt as though he was going diagonally up, the intense cold wind beating against his face, flowing into his nostrils and down his neck.

Everything around him was slanting, and shook non-stop.

He gripped the black feathers tightly, ordering the Black Crow to follow the Black Crow in front of it, and then just let it go on auto-pilot.

With a whoosh, Fox’s Black Crow brushed past on his right, and rushed to the very front with extreme speed. After that, Kitten caught up as well, the two of them chasing each other, and soon they became two tiny black dots in the distance.

"The two of you, don’t break away from the team!" Old Man’s voice came from the black box.

Garen glanced downwards.

The whole Kingdom was now just the size of his palm.

The whole Kingdom was sunk in the middle of a mountain range, all alone with nothing around it, as though it was a city built on mountaintops. It seemed ancient and mysterious.

The Kingdom became smaller and smaller, further and further. Garen’s hood couldn’t stay on, and was pulled down by the strong winds, his long golden hair flying in the wind.

"Careful, we’re going above the cloud layer." Old Man’s voice came from the Black Box.

Garen clipped the Black Box onto his collar, and it happened to fit perfectly on the golden iris, hanging there securely.

Before the voices faded.

Garen had no time to reply when he felt the large swathes of white cloud mist assault his face. It was cold and moist, as though someone sprayed mist into his face.

Everything around him became a sea of white.

Caw!!

The Black Crow in front of him made a sound.

Caw! Caw!!

The Black Crow he was riding also cried out.

The Black Crows seemed to be using that to determine each other’s locations.

The cries rang out and echoed by Garen’s ear, lasting an entire half minute.

Finally, with a whoosh, they went through the cloud layer in an instant.

The golden sun hung quietly in the distant deep blue sky, and below them were the sea of white clouds.

Some clouds sunk in, so they could see the earth and mountains down there, as small as grains of sand.

Some clouds protruded, like strangely-shaped pillars. Some clouds were just bunches of cotton.

Above the endless layers of clouds, six giant Black Crows were like six sesame seeds, flapping their wings and soaring almost indistinguishably.

"We need to keep flying for two hours, it’s a bit far away. Be aware of your own waist-pouch, don’t let it get blown away," Old Man reminded tirelessly.

Garen turned around and looked in the direction they came. He instantly felt a slight jolt.

In the sky above the Kingdom, seen from a distance, there was a grey-black light all over the sky above the Kingdom.

That light was like a fog, floating and twining all above the Kingdom, there were even many black tentacles poking out here and there, waving in the sky.

"Do you see that? Ninetales." Old Man’s voice came again. "That’s the Kingdom’s strongest tactical defense formation, without permission, no flying creature can go past the sky above the Kingdom."

"It’s quite the sight." Garen sighed.

The Black Crows flew forth in parallel with each other, in a V-formation.

The time passed, and soon half an hour had passed.

"Careful, everyone, we’re coming up on the West Farm defense lines, there might be high-flying monsters attacking." This time it was actually Red Umbrella’s voice, how rare for him not to be yawning.

Garen focused a little more as well, raising his guard.

It wasn’t long after the reminder that two strange birds immediately rushed up from beneath the sea of clouds.

Waa! Waa!!

Cries that sounded like children weeping came from in front of them.

The strange birds were completely purple-black, like bald eagles, with a snake-like neck, and four red eyes on the top of their heads.

The two strange birds were about seven or eight meters in size, but as soon as they rushed up and saw the six giant Black Crows, each more than ten meters long, the two birds panicked immediately, turned around and dove into the clouds again, disappearing without a trace.

"They’re Four-eyed Birds, one of the rare few bird-type monsters that can fly at altitudes above seven or eight thousand meters. They’re powerful, equal to a Form Two totem. But unfortunately, we’re riding on Giant Black Crows, which are even stronger. One Death Glare can kill those two in an instant," Old Man laughed, in a light mood, but mostly he seemed to be explaining for Garen’s sake.

"I wanted to taste what Four-eyed Bird meat was like, but they run so fast every time!" Kitten’s voice sounded disinterested.

"We need to go low in the area ahead, it’s that crazy monster’s territory, so everyone watch out and go lower with me," Old Man said loudly.

"Got it.""As usual, Red Umbrella takes the rear."

Everyone replied one by one.

Garen was slightly curious as to what kind of monster could let the Form Three totem users from the Secret Service all decide to avoid it. But they were high in the sky, so he didn’t ask.

The Black Crow kept close behind the ones in front, and suddenly sunk, reducing their altitude and dashing down.

Whoosh!

They dove into the fluffy white sea of clouds in an instant.

After more than ten seconds, the cloud sea burst open, and below was a large sweep of white mountain ranges, dotted with dark green forests and lakes.

The Black Crows rushed down, flying towards that mirror-like lake, the lake-water reflected the layers of clouds, clear and clean.

A few giant black turtles were basking in the sun, like so many black stones, heavy and clumsy.

A herd of light yellow deer was drinking water next to a dried up and collapsed tree trunk, taking tiny sips, their ears occasionally twitching nimbly.

Whoosh!!

The six giant Black Birds suddenly rushed down, dipping past the mirror-like surface of the blue lake, the gusts of wind causing the water to shake, creating large ripples.

The deer yelped in shock, and left the lake in a hurry. The black turtles immediately pulled their heads back into their shells, and didn’t move at all, playing dead.

Garen stood on the Black Crow’s back, watching the lakewater retreat rapidly backwards, to be replaced by forest. Many birds were spooked and took flight, escaping towards the left and right in flocks.

There were even three female campers surrounding a fire and barbequing something. Two of them heard the commotion and immediately stood up, looking towards the sky, their mouth wide open and their expressions spooked.

"Wooo~~~!" Kitten was crying out again.

The six Giant Black Crows swept past the forest, causing the leaves to rustle.

Chapter 373: Gathering 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Black crows glided in the sky above the vast sea of trees, occasionally flapping its wings.

Garen tightly grabbed onto the protruding feathers that looked like black iron. His entire body rested within the recessed region, his entire body felt warm.

The black crows dissipated warm heat, filling the recessed area with its warmth.

Without knowledge of how much time had passed, they finally flew past the vast expanse of forest beneath, and it faded behind them behind them.

At the end of the stretch of woods was a huge circular basin. The depressed region looked like a hollow basin made of red-colored stone, and at its center was a deep black canyon.

Six black crows flew out from the edge of the forest, across the edge of the basin, and dove straight into the canyon.

Garen was riding one of the black crows diving straight into the dark canyon. On his flanks were steep uneven walls of red rock, with the abyss below pitch black. It was impossible to see anything. Up above was a strip faint white clouds adrift.

Whoosh!

The crow’s wings fluttered to the sides canyon, blowing a gust which detached some loose rocks from the wall. A few pieces of red stones fell into the bottom of the unending trench.

Garen bent down, looking at the corners and curves ahead of him, rapidly moving within the canyon cracks.

With such rapid flight and tortuous canyon curves, Garen had the unshakable feeling feeling that he might hit the rock wall at any time.

"I've reached my objective. Commencing operation." The voice of the red umbrella was heard from the black box.

"Be careful," the old man answered.

"I know."

One of the black crows separated from the team, and flew towards the left canyon crossing, rushing forward into a huge ancient structure ahead.

The structure was a large red tauren stone statue about half a man’s height, it held up its fists, and seemed to be making a roaring action. Its lower body was embedded directly into the cliff face, and the entire red cliff seemed to have been emptied, leaving an ancient relic site behind.

Garen only took a cursory glimpse as he flew by and he did not have a clear look.

He then moved forward for a bit more.

Soon, foxes and kittens also split off from the team.

It was finally Garen’s turn, and he remembered the location’s features on the map.

"My mission point is here, I’ll make my move first," he said directly to the box.

"Be aware of the surroundings, reserve some power in case of possible accidents." The old man said, evident of a kind, aged, personality.

"Good luck, nine-headed brother." The child flew to Garen’s side, standing on the back of black crow as he raised his fist. "Let me know if you encounter any difficulties, my mission is near yours."

"Thank you," said Garen. Although he did not know the strength of the rest of the Red team, it was estimated that he would be the least likely to encounter any problems.

The overall strength of Red Team was very strong, any one of them could independently take on multiple form 3 monsters quite easily. That was to say, they had at least a pinnacle form 3 totem, and even the power to spiritualise.

The fact that Garen had the power to spiritualise should have spread to the capital,al and it surely would have have reached the king, but he was still not taken seriously by the red team. He really do not understand why.

However there was no point in thinking about these things. More importantly, this task could be a juicy opportunity to rack up some potential points. Garen planned to first evolve the ninth head of eight-headed dragon, and then focus on upgrading the Secret Techniques to see what would happen.

Banking right into a corner guiding the black crow, Garen suddenly flew into a black-red crossroad.

At the end in the distance, a large triangle-shaped red stone wall was clearly visible. It resembled a huge red beehive, full of holes of all sizes.

From the void came some whistles whimsically blowing constantly. Besides that the surroundings were eerily silent.

Garen rode the black crow and rushed straight towards it. The red beehive came nearer and nearer.

Each hole was more than half a meter in diameter arranged neatly together, forming a huge triangle of hundreds of meters in length and width.

The black crow round the triangular honeycomb stone wall, but did not see any creatures. Not even a single piece of greenery could be seen.

He controlled the black crow as it slowly on a flat stone on the rock bumps.

boom!

With a wingspan more than ten meters , the black crow flapped twice, its wings creating bursts of wind as it gently landed on the ground.

Garen jumped down from its back, twisting his body slightly in mid-air. A black light glowed from under his feet to buffett the landing and he gently landed on the ground.

"White Dragon, go ... ..." Garen remembered that the derivator have been destroyed by himself, because of the fear of Obscuro tracking technology. There was no way to relieve the hidden dangers, after all, hence he chose to destroy it.

He shook his head slightly, tidied up his messy black armor, and wore the hood on his head so he would be hidden in full armor.

The surroundings were spacious, ahead of him was the triangular beehive, and on his left a stone wall, while under his feet on the right was a bottomless abyss.

Garen stomped on the ground.

Bang bang

A very dull sound came forth.

"Very sturdy." Garen looked up at the huge red triangle in front of him and ordered the black crow to hold position.

He took two steps forward and one step mid-air.

Ding!

Black light array fleeted.

Garen jumped lightly and flew in midair, shooting his foot out once again in mid-air, turning on the black light array. His entire person stepped on the black light array like ladders and jumped straight toward the triangular stone wall.

After each step, he felt that that his current jumping strength was enough. Garen jumped four times consecutively and he reached the top of the triangular stone wall.

Suddenly diagonally on his right side, a huge red stone ball flew towards Garen.

Bam!

A stone ball as wide as a man was smashed into smithereens.

The air around Garen twisted for a moment, then returned to normal.

"err?"

He turned his head and looked down to the right, his body was on the top of a triangular stone wall.

"What is that, to actually dare to attack me?"

He looked down

On the lower right side of the red stone wall, a cave about 7 to 8-meter-high appeared unknowingly. It was so dark one cannot see the bottom.

Standing by the cave entrance was a silver-colored hairy monster.

The monster looked like a gruesome human with both feet standing, long arms with long red claws, much like a human arm holding a huge stone ball.

Its head actually had only a huge red eye, his mouth full of fine rows of white teeth.

"It seems like this is my objective." Garen did not panic, "One Eyed Beamon."

He recalled the information he had.

This creature was named the One Eyed Beamon, it had extremely sharp claws, incredible strength, and agile movements. It could excavate a tunnel of dozens of meters in half a minute.

Its abilities were unknown, as no one actually had contact with it before. With the secret service cleaning up the area, it was a requirement to collect first-hand information in order to reduce possible future damage.

Awoo!

One-eyed Beamon roared, the stone ball is its hand was sent flying toward Garen once again.

Garen made no action, instead quietly standing still. He stared at the stone ball hurling towards him.

Bam!

Once again, the stone ball exploded, at the same time, a trace of twisting in the air that felt like teeth snapping thin air.

"Good strength." Garen felt that this time the strength of the stone ball had actually doubled, the dragon was numb from the hurled ball.

Fragments exploded, but also left a little debris that did not spread. within Garen’s vision, three more stone balls were hurled, all tumbling in the same direction.

He snickered, jumped, and easily escaped the stone ball attack. A flash of light flashed at his feet, pushing him toward the lower right of the cave.

His black clothes made some rustling sound in the air. Garen drew a black line, then rushed straight toward one-eyed Beamon.

fuuuuuuu!

Suddenly another three stone balls from his rear appeared, crashing onto Garen’s back. It rained down like shells of bullets.

Gallon was unable to react midair, hence he got hit severely by the first ball.

Bam!

A large hold appeared on the stone wall behind Garen again. By the entrance came another One-eyed Beamon.

Heart was now fighting two One-eyed Beamons!

The One-eyed Beamon opened its hand. Its palm gathered a large number of stones around it, as if there were an invisible force gathering the debris, condensing them into a rock.

As it hurled one, he immediately formed another. Its action speed is very high.

In just three seconds, it threw six boulders.

Huge boulders instantly formed with a bang, and then were hurled out.

Two one-eyed Beamon hurled a bunch of boulders midair in quick succession, then only they stop to take a look.

As the boulders was crushed to smithereens, the debris fell down almost hit a wasp’s nest on the right side of the stone wall. Its destructive power was staggering.

Red ash filled the air.

"Hurled a bunch of boulders after I got up, so ruthless." Garen’s figure was revealed from the red debris.

His entire body was covered with dim black totem’s light. He was completely unharmed, instead he only fluttered towards the stone wall to the right side.

The One-eyed Beamon on the left roared, and it once again hurled boulders with force. The right Beamon remained silent, turn around into the cave and disappeared.

Its proficiency in action was surprisingly quick.

Garon jumped and landed in front of the cave entrance on the right with a thump, a twirling transparent vortex behind him kept blocking the boulders hurled from behind. Each throw produces da strong impact, shaking the mountain wall with each impact.

"Crafty little guy." Garen looked back and met its eye, and the opponent was merrily hurling away.. Stone balls was hurled one after another, as if it is endless.

"One-eyed Beamon, ability one: boulder hurling, the power exceeds form 3 totems, close to spiritualization, deals large area of effect damage." Garen took out a small book and carefully recorded ability.

After the boulders rained on him for a while, it seemed to realise that this did not pose a threat to Garen, and it finally stopped its throws.

The One-eyed Beamon looked up and roared, and its eye suddenly turn red. Its body expanded, and seemingly much stronger now, and a faint pale red aura covered its silver fur.

It stomped its legs fiercely, and with a bang, leapt forward like a monkey jumping towards Garen. A pair of sharp red claws shimmering faintly, fiercely clawing for its target.

In a single jump, it actually covered more than 20 meters across the canyon. Fluttering across the cliff, its tall body with revealed the location of the silhouette’s bombardment towards Garen.

Chapter 374: Collection 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Five sharp claws that looked like five red blood crystals. A beautiful crystalline translucence can be seen among them, as they swiped towards Garen’s waist and abdomen.

At the same time, the cave that Garen was in, the same one-eyed Beamon, who had reddish fur, also fluttered.

With the same action and the same attack stances, the two Beamons, one in front and the other behind Garen flanked him in the middle. Four red claws swiped towards Garen simultaneously.

Garen raised his eyebrows, three red lights flashing.

He raised his hand, and a giant red silhouette lit up behind him, a dragon more than ten meters high with 8 heads showed its upper body, the rear half seemed to be still somewhere outside.

Garen’s eyes had a flash of red light.

"Dragon roar!"

Roar! ! ! !

A burst of sound waves burst forth like ripples on water. Both sides of canyon walls shook violently, knocking loose rubble and gravel.

The raging sound waves momentarily scattered in all directions, the rock Garen stood on shattered, forming a circular pit full of dense cracks.

All eight heads of the dragon roared at the same time, releasing a sound that is almost four times the original power! The horrifying sonic boom swept two Beamons off their feet.

Both One-eyed Beamons had blood oozing out of their eye, nose, ears, and mouth. The monsters were overturned, and were unable to move as they sat on the ground.

They struggled to get up, but all their muscles were numb from the roar and failed to move. Their single huge eyes were unable to see anything, only darkness.

The Beamons whined pitifully, its tone filled with panic and fear.

Two of the Eight-headed dragon’s heads reached out, each leaning down toward one of the One-eyed Beamons. Its jaws clamped on the Beaons and launched them straight into the air.

A crisp tearing noise came from the Beamons.

The two Beamons were violently torn apart by the eight heads midair. The eight mouths constantly let out terrifying chewing sounds. Bones were crushed by snapping jaws, followed by gulping noises indicating the sound of swallowing.

In just a moment, the two huge one-eyed Beamons were torn apart by the eight-headed dragons as a meal.

Garen touched his belly, his teeth felt sore.

One-eyed Beamon's flesh was so tough that when eight dragons chewed on their bones, he felt a bit of soreness on his own teeth. The Beamon’s bones were harder than other bones.

After the two monsters were swallowed, what’s left was leftover flesh dripping, splashing down like a short burst of bloody rain, splattering heavily on the ground of the cave.

The silhouette of eight-headed dragon slowly disappeared.

The three dots between his eyebrows faded, no longer shining. Just that the color of red was bright, as if was smeared with blood.

Garen walked to the rest of the flesh, these are the parts that the eight-headed dragon refused to eat; either because they doesn’t taste good or was too hard to digest.

To his surprise, Garen found four blood red claws.

Each claw had four fingers, and were actually its finger nails.

Most of the red crystalline nails have been crushed, and only two was fairly intact. Garen bent over to pick it up, slightly shaking off the blood. They looked like two decent crystal machetes at a glance.

Garen tested the Beamon claws by slashing a handkerchief, and then by tapping the black crow ring.

"The main dish is finished, now is time for the other pack monsters, those are some Form 2 monsters, it should be a breeze." Garen’s tied the claws to his waist. He was in a good mood; he had earned 16 potential points and even got some souvenirs. Naturally, his mood would be in high spirits.

Soon, a huge black crow appeared and landed directly in front of Garen.

He somersaulted and landed on the back of the black crow. Its wings flapped loudly, and the black crow launched off the canyon floor, spread its wings and flew away. It soon became a small dot in the sky; gradually fading away.

A few minutes later.

From within the triangular honeycomb stone wall, a petite ugly man walked out of the crevices; his face was pale, he donned a black robe which didn’t stand out.

The man laid down at he cave entrance as he observed Garen from afar, his face looked solemn.

He took out a pale red crystal ball and tapped on it a few times.

"Demetrius, I met the target ahead of time."

The crystal ball was silent for a while, then faint breaths were heard over the crystal ball. "How was it?" A woman’s voice was heard from the derivator.

"Extremely difficult." The petite man answered solemnly, " I originally thought that I could easily settle the opponent with my artifacts, but just as I arrived, I bumped into the target battling two One-Eyed Beamons. So I hid myself to spectate the battle.

"Were you humbled?"

The man forced a laugh. "That was less of a battle but more of a one-sided massacre. We are both very well aware of the strength of the One-Eyed Beamon, yet he killed two of them while sustaining zero damage. The Royal Alliance has not met these creatures, they wouldn’t know their strengths, but we, who are from Obscuro Society have made contact with the Beamons would know how tough they are. Two One-eyed Beamon that berserk were equivalent to a single Spiritualized Totem User."

"And what are you trying to imply?"

"Gather all the Colonels, surround and ambush him!" A hint of ferocity can be seen from his eyes. "I suspect that this is the same man who disguised as Jess and killed Ann-Rue.

************************************************

On the red canyon, red plains can be seen afar from the edge of the cliff.

On it was some sparsely spread dead black trees, the leafless trees were twisted and bent beyond recognition, and some oddly shaped growth can be seen on its barks.

There were red boulders of various sizes scattered around the plains; from a man’s height, to over ten meters in height. Most of the boulders had a hole in the middle which was indicative of weathering. As the air current passed through the holes; it let out an odd ring.

A giant crow flew past the plain, on top of it was a man donned with black armor, wearing a hood. Few strands of golden blonde hair can be seen from the side of the high collar.

That man was indeed Garen, who just killed two One-Eyed Beamons. He was scouting the vicinity of his mission waypoint, but unfortunately, there were no signs of life around the entire vicinity after that dragon roar

He was circling the plains for half a day; but not a single shadow passed, only messy footprints on the ground, and some skeletal remains that were not finished remained, indicative of some creature hordes nearby.

There was some foul smell emitting from the ground, which smelled like faeces.

Garen deduced that this should be the horde’s excrement, which released the foul smell after being exposed to sunlight.

Bzzzt bzzzt… the black box on his collar let out a crackling noise,

"I’m Old Man, send in your mission reports." The box on Garen’s collar emitted Old Man’s hoarse voice.

"Fox here, I am all cleaned up." A clear female voice was heard from the box.

‘Tch! Kitten was done long ago." Another girl’s voice was heard.

"Kid is not done yet, but I’ll be done soon, there was a sudden horde of creatures, who knows where they came from." Kid’s voice had a hint of breathlessness.

Garen was secretly guilty.

His mission point was really near Kid’s mission point, the horde on Kid’s side was definitely the monsters who got scared by his roar.

"Nineheads all settled." He replied.

"What about Red Umbrella?" Old man asked in confusion.

" Big Bro Red Umbrella?" it was Kitten’s voice.

"... Ughh, apologies, I had a nightmare, that was scary!" Red Umbrella’s voice was heard from the box.

The band of people were speechless; this fellow got the hardest mission, he actually completed it so early, he could take a nap…

"Alright everyone, please gather at the next mission waypoint, no issues right?" Old Man ordered, "those who forgot the route please voice out."

"I forgot!" Kitten said righteously. " Big Bro Red Umbrella, why don’t, I go to the waypoint with you. Going together would allow us to take care of each other…." Her voice got weaker towards the end.

The rest laughed out.

"Okay now, the waypoint is Pumpkin Farm. everybody knows this historical ruinright?" Old Man repeated, "The location is Pumpkin Farm, rendezvous time is in half an hour, everybody be punctual."

"Roger." Kid was the most well-mannered, and answered earnestly.

The rest of them didn’t bother replying, as they directly turned off the box.

Garen ordered the crow to turn around and head towards the direction as he remembered in the map.

The crow increased its elevation, and flew out of the red canyon.

Ahead of him was a sea of forests that seemed boundless.

Green trees, red trees, and some tall black statues that he passed towering in the woods.

All the statues are of the same figure; the torso of a man, the lower body of a lion, with one arm lifted to point forward, its head turned back, as if it was talking to those behind him.

The statues seemed aged, some of it was covered in dense cracks, some of it had more than half its statue was covered with moss and vines.

Garen stood on top of the crow as he gazed below, soon, a large patch of black colored land was seen ahead, much like a patch of shaved hair in the midst of the sea of forests.

On the entire patch of ground, there were large yellowish green pumpkins, spread well away from each other.

Each pumpkin was the size of a basketball field, tens of meters in diameter, it’s yellowish-green shell was covered with many pitch black holes.

Garen rode on the crow, and flew one round a piece of pumpkin, he then realized that the insides of the pumpkin was all hollow; there was nothing inside.

Garen looked closely, he then realized that these aren’t real pumpkins at all, but instead giant boulders which were weathered to this stage. On the surface of the pumpkin was covered in yellowish green moss.

"Hey!!" Garen looked down where a man in black was waving at him.

"Big Bro Nineheads, look over here!" It was Kid’s voice.

Garen looked towards him closely, he only saw Kid holding a giant strawberry. The strawberry was radiantly red, it looked extremely fresh, the part which was grazed by Kid’s clothes was oozing its fresh strawberry juice, flowing down along Kid’s clothes, coloring his clothes red.

This monstrously huge strawberry actually needed both hands to hold onto.

Chapter 375: Gank 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen descended with the crow, slowly landing on the clearing next to Kid.

He jumped off the crow’s back, and stood firmly on the black soil.

"Where’re the others?"

Kid shook his head. "I just got here too. Haven’t seen anyone else. I guess they’re en route." He pointed the giant strawberry "you want some? This tastes good."

Garen shook his head. He then immediately saw that Kid’s hand had skillfully dug the strawberry open, reaching all the way inside, pulling a red fruit out with a whoosh.

This piece of fruit looked oddly similar to a heart, it is still beating, and were emitting heat off it.

" This is the strawberry’s heart; you can get a mild immunity to poison from this." Kid bit down and spoke with a muffled voice.

"A strawberry that grows hearts?" Garen can’t help but to be curious," where did this Strawberry come from?"

"My mission waypoint was Strawberry Field, there’s plenty of this where I came from, and there’re many more produced every year." Kid briefly explained, "I grew up here.

"You grew up here?" Garen did not expect Kid to have these experiences.

"Yeah, I ate these growing up." Kid answered earnestly, "Strawberry Farm’s strawberries are very sweet."

Kid had his mouth smeared with strawberry juice as red as blood.

Garen didn’t mind him, as he continued looking around.

Surrounding him were all those gigantic pumpkins, as the wind blew through the holes of the pumpkin, it made some eerie whistling tunes.

"Hey hey, Nineheads, where are you?" Old Man’s voice can be heard from the black box.

"I’m already here, at Pumpkin Farm, i’m with Kid now."

"You, and Kid?" He suddenly stunned, which felt weird. "You, alone? With him?"

"Yeah? What’s wrong?" Garen was confused by Old Man’s intonation, something felt off.

"You stay where you are, I’ll be right there!" Old Man got anxious out of the sudden. "Please don’t talk to Kid too much!"

Garen was confused, so he turned back to look at Kid.

As if without awareness, Kid was gulping the strawberry in his hand. He kept taking things out from within the odd strawberry, there was a part that looked like liver, a piece of fruit which looked like a lung, there was even a tube that looked like a bronchus. It was all eaten by Kid with huge bites. His stomach was like a bottomless pit, as he stuffed everything inside.

Garen suddenly felt that something was off.

There was a faint scent of blood was let off from the strawberry in Kid’s hands.

He paid closer attention to the strawberry. Although it didn’t look different from a regular strawberry from the outside, but for reasons unknown to him, he could sense fear and despair from the strawberry; as if it was a living thing.

He also suddenly realized that Kid’s black box and crow was not there.

"Kid, where’s your crow?" He can’t help but to ask.

"Crow? You mean that big guy? I don’t know, he was gone once I looked away." Kid answered honestly.

"Them, what about your black box?"

"It’s here." Kid took out the black box like it were magic.

Garen relaxed for a while, if the black box is there, then he is not an impersonator.

He tried contacting Kid with his black box, everything was normal.

Soon, a huge crow spread its wings and dived towards them.

Old Man jumped off from the crow, black light lit up from under his feet, which helped him land.

As he hit the ground, he looked at Garen weirdly. Then he looked over to Kid who was merrily eating.

"Kid, it’s rare to see you being so honest this time around."

Kid wiped his mouth. " But wasn’t I always honest?"

Garen was confused as he was, judging from the way Old Man spoke, maybe being alone with Kid would be dangerous. Just that there was nothing weird about Kid.

As he saw the the old and young together, like a usual gathering, he did not want to ask further.

Soon, Kitten and Fox arrived. The last one was Red Umbrella, who flew from behind, looking sleepy with droopy eyes as he touched down.

With all six of them here, Old Man began leading the team towards Pumpkin Farm. The rest of them followed him.

The entire farm was engulfed in a thin mist, which looked like it came from the forest. Visibility was poor.

As they walked deeper for a moment, faint music could be heard from their surroundings.

The music was faintly discernible, as though if came from a faraway place. It sounded like a girl was singing in a language not comprehensible to them.

Garen’s heart shivered, that was Endorian, he only understood a sentence or two, since he did some self-learning, he wasn’t sure if it was correct.

The music continued to linger, giving them a clear sense of language acuity.

He began to try to analyze the lyrics, but he had trouble listening to the song clearly enough to make up its contents.

The song suddenly stopped, the piano piece also started getting slightly messy. It felt like a girl who just started playing piano, restarting the verse due to a single mistake.

The music started playing again, on repeat.

Garen looked at others, he realized that there was no reaction, except Kid, who was humming to the girl’s music.

"Kid, can you stop humming? What song was that? Why haven’t we heard about it?" Kitten said impatiently.

"I was humming along to little sister though?" Kid answered earnestly. "Didn’t you hear? Little sister played wrongly again." he looked like he was listening in again.

"Here he goes." Kitten pressed her forehead disappointedly.

"Pay no heed, Kid’s acting up again." Old Man said quietly.

Garen had a thought. Does that mean they all couldn’t hear it? As he observed each person, he realized that the rest was indeed unable to hear the voice except Kid and him.

He now paid more attention to Kid.

The single file continued moving deeper into the farm, soon, they found the nobilities hiding within one of the giant pumpkin.

The two of them were hunkering down in the pumpkin from the panic, only to relax as they saw the group, and climbed out of the pumpkin.

These two people were messy; who knew when was the last time they had a shower. A huge whiff of unbearable stench hit them as the two people approached.

"I am Duke Pratoe from White Mist Town, This is my wife, Aliya, Thank you for your rescue, we will be sure to reward you handsomely once we get back!"

The man could barely hold up his pride and calmness, as his body could not suppress his shakiness that exposed his current emotions.

"Right, shall we get back soon?" The Duke rushed.

"Nineheads, you’re responsible for them, let’s go back together." Old man ordered.

"Right, gentlemen, we still have some things that needed to be moved back, I wonder if…" The duke smiled as he spoke.

"Nineheads, take all of it back, I can’t wait to leave, I don’t know why but this place is giving me the creeps." Kitten said impatiently.

Garen shrugged, these people seemed to have made him the dispatch boy.

The Duke smiled at Garen and said. "I would have to trouble you then."

Garen didn’t know if he should laugh or cry.

"By the looks of it, we’d better do it the usual way; the slowest one should do it." Red Umbrella said.

"On what account?!" Kitten lashed out.

" Alright, stop fooling around, your time is the slowest, you should help pack up. It’s not like we needed you to do it; you just need to put your totem." Old Man advised.

"The monsters on my side were much stronger than Nineheads’! Two Type 3s!! They were almost spiritualized too!" Kitten looked at Garen with an unconvinced eye.

Garen gave Kitten a smile. That made Kitten even angrier.

"Go." Red Umbrella said coldly, looking nonchalant.

Kitten was pouting as she stood there, but she listened to the instruction at the end.

She would only listen to Red Umbrella.

Garen finally had the chance to see Kitten’s totem.

A ray of red light dashed through, it was a giant red tiger the size of an elephant appearing on top of the pumpkin, long fur covered the tiger, its limbs were all weird looking white hooves. It doesn’t seem to resemble anything.

Kitten was mumbling and scolding as she loaded the items onto the tiger. She glared at Garen from time to time, too.

"This wasn’t my fault." Garen smiled helplessly. Putting up an innocent face, Garen proactively went ahead to try to help.

"Stand aside! Who needs your help!" Kitten lashed out again.

Garen backed off as he looked at Kitten loading the boxes of items onto the tiger alone. He didn’t know why, but he felt that teasing Kitten was an amusing thing to do; seeing her lash out was always interesting.

"There’s someone here? There’re actually people who still come here?" Red Umbrella suddenly said. His face showed a rare look of suspicion, as he looked towards the mist at the left side of the group.

"How can there be anyone here? Surrounding Pumpkin Farm are dense hordes of creatures, we were also just getting by to clear them." Old Man was confused too.

A few people stopped their movements, while simultaneously looking at the swiftly approaching silhouette

Soon, as the opponent approached, the silhouette showed itself entirely.

It was actually a tall man wearing black robes, he was covered in black scarves, the upper half of his face covered under a silver mask, all you could see were a pair of silverish-grey eyes. Even his hair was covered by the hood.

This person walked towards them, until he stopped about ten-odd meters away from them. He took a look at the tall Crimson Fur Tiger. His gaze then fell straight towards Garen who was standing among the crowd.

"Garen Trejons. If you are willing to accept our sincerity, join us, then the next two wrongs that you commit will be given lenient treatments by us."

"Who are you?" Old Man stood out and asked loudly.

The other party didn’t answer, only staring straight at Garen.

"What lenient treatment?" Garen laughed.

Unknowingly, The nice guy vibe on him changed slightly, as though his entire person had more of an odd vibe.

Old Man stood the nearest to him; hence he realized this clear change.

He then had an uncertain suspicion look as he stared at Garen.

"What if i did not accept your sincerity today?" Garen spoke again, a smirk was shown on his face with a hint of coldness.

"Killing two Elemental Generals back-to-back, if you refuse, then you shall die here." the opponent smirked coldly.

" What arrogance!" Kitten who had the worst temper couldn’t hold it in, the giant Crimson GIant pounced onto him, it's four limb actually ignited with clouds of black flames, slamming onto the opponent like a small hill.

Her fingers ignited with crimson flames, as it carried an afterimage, she quickly drew out a diamond-shaped tactic.

Bam!

The Crimson Tiger exploded suddenly, turning into countless flames as it swept towards the opponent.

"Be careful!" Red Umbrella’s expression changed, he then instantaneously rushed in front of Kitten and blocked with his right arm.

Dang!!

A black light crashed into his arm; it was actually a black bird.

The black bird pierced straight into Red Umbrella’s arm, and came out from the other side, but its direction was also changed by the block, disappearing in a black line into the mist.

"The opponent’s a Spiritualized Totem User!! Everybody be careful!" Red Umbrella did not pay attention to the injury on his arm, the wound had automatically closed and recovered.

Kitten was scared pale at this moment, even Red Umbrella’s Totem’s Light could not block the opponent’s attack; obviously this was not something an ordinary totem user could achieve. If it wasn’t blocked, she would have been severely injured.

"Spiritualized Totem User? Haha." The opponent laughed, the silhouette that was covered in flames stood unharmed; taking almost no damage.

His sight was fixed onto Garen again, ignoring the rest.

"Looks like a decision has to be made today." Garen took a long sigh.

At the same time, from the group’s left, right and rear, each came a man wearing a silver mask, they all had the same appearance, each had the same unfathomably strong vibe.

"Any last words?" The silver masked man leader asked coldly.

The Crimson Team got nervous.

There are not those oddballs from Obscuro which possess the crystal Derivator. These people

rely on the single strongest core totem, even though most of the team of the level of spiritualization, the weakest being Kitten with a form 3 totem. However looking at the opponent's strength, they were also at least in the realm of spiritualization. Kitten’s attacks didn't faze the opponent’s totem’s light; the situation seemed grave.

Chapter 376: Gank 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen understood well that no matter how strong the headquarters’ Red Team was, they were not the Black Sky’s Elemental Generals, and didn’t possess as much powerful empowered totems as they did.

A typical totem user’s strongest totem was his core totem, and there were very rare totem users that were able to nurture a second spiritualized totem. The difference between the Generals of the Black Sky and the others was that they possessed a special nurturing technique where the aberrated creatures would be devolved and cause a major loss. However, they themselves did have the strength that far surpassed a typical spiritualized totem user.

Each of them had the strength of at least two spiritualized totems. One was their own core totem, and the other was the empowered totem they possessed.

Each of them were of the same level as Beckstone, whom Garen faced in the manor. Since they had four of them, it meant that they had the strength of four Beckstones.

This was the true strength of the Black Sky, unlike Ann-Rue who was actually just a flower in the living room!

Garen squinted his eyes as he noticed the leader had an additional exquisite, black pocket watch with him.

"You people are from the Black Sky!" The Old Man seemed to recognize their identity.

"Hehe." The Silver Masked Man laughed coldly. "Communication Imprisonment!"

A large amount of air suddenly appeared behind the four of them and they were surprisingly spiritualized air. The four of them had ten spiritualized totems!

All of the Spiritualized Air merged together and formed into one body.

Garen looked at his surrounding and found out that none of the Red Team members planned to leave at all. They stood still as they stared at the four formidable foes.

"You guys go ahead. I’m the one they’re after." He knew that these people had yet to reveal their trump card for escape purposes.

It was at this moment that Red Umbrella recognized this new team leader.

"Since we have recognized you, you are now one of us. We, the read team are never the type who would leave their team members behind."

The remaining four of them didn’t utter a word as they silently prepared for battle. They even brought out weird and strange looking battle equipment.

"Kitten, stand behind me." Red Umbrella ordered.

Kitten glanced at Garen with a complicated looked and obediently stood behind Red Umbrella. She knew that the situation was dire and it was not the time to be wilful.

The four silver masked men had finished setting up their strange formation and a faintly glowing white membrane cylindrical in shape had engulfed everyone.

The two nobles had been scared to the point where they couldn’t stand and didn’t even dare to hyperventilate.

"Accept your punishment!"

Four of their totem powers merged into one.

In an instant, countless of black smoke gathered above everyone and formed into the black Crow that they encountered earlier.

These small Crows gathered together, forming a black stream as they kept revolving in the sky. As it chirped, a waterfall was formed as the water gushed towards the crowd.

Countless of small Crows cornered Garen and the team from all directions.

Each of these small Crows were half transparent and half intangible. They could even overlap against each other.

The scream of these Crows covered the whole surrounding, causing annoyance to everyone hearing it.

"I can’t move my totem!!!" The Old Man shouted in surprise.

"Me too!" Kitten shouted along.

Red Umbrella felt that his totem was being locked by some shackle and it wouldn’t budge at all. Panicked, he looked up at the herd of crows that were fast approaching them. He had just experienced the prowess of these Crows recently and he knew that it could penetrate his totem light. Hence they were definitely Spiritualized class totems, and there were so many of them!

Suddenly, Fox pulled his shirts from behind as she shook her head.

"Look over there."

Red Umbrella looked where she pointed.

What he saw was the four silver masked men behaving in such a way as if they never had the chance to win at all. In fact, they looked like they were facing a formidable foe and were looking anxiously at them.

"This is…?" He was stunned as he looked at where the enemies were looking.

It was where Nine Head was standing.

Nine Head’s birthmarks was brightly lighted in blood red and he looked demonic as it shone.

Countless of Black Crows ignored the rest and flew directly towards Garen.

Garen raised his right hand and his five fingers were lit up in red.

A strange and terrifying aura emerged from his body.

"Dragon’s Roar!!"

Roar!!!

A solid, continuous roar instantly spread throughout the area.

The upper body of the Eight Headed Dragon appeared behind Garen’s back and eight of its heads were continuously roaring towards the sky.

With Garen as the epicenter, a deep crater was formed around him in a ten meters radius. Countless dust and pebbles flew everywhere as it spreaded in all directions.

Large amount of Black Crows turned back into black smoke and disappeared before they even reached Garen. Cracks were constantly forming and healing simultaneously on the light membrane trapping them. The cracks and their recovery clashed into each other, and they barely found a balance in between.

The four Silver Masked Men were trembling, as fresh blood could be seen dripping out of their mouths as they tried to maintain the Imprisonment Tactical Formation.

This Tactical Formation was made by combining all ten spiritualized totem’s totem powers and totem light together to form a Formation on par with a form four totem.

However, everyone had underestimated the enemies as they were not a typical Upper Class Elemental General. They had the strength of a Commander-level!

The leader of the Silver Masked Men was stunned as the Dragon Roar’s reverberated. He had brought four Generals with him and even a heirloom to produce a formation. He was so sure that he could eliminate the opponent, but unfortunately it was still not enough.

"He’s not even 23!" He was stunned as he had such a strength at that age. Imagine when he fully matured…

"No! Since we had started a feud with him, we must deal with him now! If we wait for him to fully mature…" The leader of the Silver Mask shivered as the though reached his mind and took out an exquisite white pyramidal shaped item.

The pyramid gave off a white light and the intense white light flowed into the Silver Masked Man’s palm.

The recovery rate of the Tactical Formation instantly increased.

The Dragon Roar had finally stopped.

The Eight Headed Dragon’s body gradually disappeared.

Garen frowned as he stared at the solid cylindrical imprisonment. The massive black fog once again condensed into Black Crows and charged towards him.

He was the only one who could freely use his totem in this formation. Red Umbrella and the others were shackled, showing that this Tactical Formation was extraordinarily powerful.

"Today’s the day you die!" The leader of the Silver Masked Man laughed as the white light from the pyramid in his hand grew more intense.

"That depends." Garen smirked.

The shadow of the Eight Headed Dragon appeared behind Garen once again and all eight heads came down and took a deep breath.

Large amount of Black Crows were sucked into the mouth, forming 8 black vortices in the air.

Every Black Crow in the Formation were completely sucked into the Eight Headed Dragon’s stomach within ten seconds.

Roar…

As it roared, the cylindrical light membrane cracked once again.

All four Silver Masked Men were shocked.

"Damn it! It’s a form four! Retreat!!" The leader of the Silver Masked Man put down his hand and ran away.

However, two of the Silver Masked Men slowly disappeared. They had obviously ran away a long time ago, leaving two illusions in the formation.

The last Silver Masked Man attempted to run away but was blocked by one of the dragon’s heads.

"Don’t kill me! I am!!" Crack!!

The dragon’s mouth took a bite and chomped this person into half. It took a few bites before swallowing him.

The gigantic dragon head returned to behind Garen. All eight dragon heads looked around as it started searching for something edible.

In the eyes of these dragon heads, it was either edible food or not.

They soon gave their full attention towards the members of the Red Team.

Garen immediately restricted its will.

As the eight dragon head stared at them, they members of the Red Team felt a shiver down their spine. They gave out a sigh of relief and felt slightly worried at the same time.

Since his strength had been exposed, Garen didn’t bother to treat them nicely anymore. His expression gradually calmed down and gave off a cold, emotionless vibe.

"I need to deal with these future troubles. This is my personal matter, I hope you guys have no comment on heading back first?"

Kitten, who was rebellious in nature, wanted to refute but she lowered her head as she felt a shiver down her spine when she looked at Garen.

"Nine Head, since you have some actual strength, why didn’t you reveal it earlier?" Red Umbrella asked calmly.

"Does that mean you acknowledge me as your captain?" Garen looked at Kitten with interest as he asked them.

"Do you think it’s easy to be the captain? Do you think you can become one by just having overwhelming strength?!" Kitten couldn’t resist but to ridicule him.

Garen was surprised that this fellow was still unsatisfied even after revealing his true strength.

"Then what do you think a captain should have other than strength?" He asked as he laughed.

Kitten thought for a while. "A captain must fulfill two criteria. If you do, I will be the first to support you!"

"Which two?"

Kitten said with a serious face: "First, he must be able to push forward, and retreat together with his other team members. Our team has lived together on the edge for many times"

"The incident we had just now is one of them right?"

"I guess so." Kitten then pulled out her second finger. "Secondly, he must be broad-minded and not care about the little things."

Suddenly, she felt something touching her butt from the back.

She turned around and saw that a gigantic dragon head had its mouth pointed at her revealing its set of teeth. The teeth that were as sharp as a sawblades still had some meat and bones hanging in between them.

Kitten was sweating cold sweat and started to tremble. The worst way to die to her was to be eaten by a creature, and there was a gigantic creature currently behind her with its mouth open.

"Do you think I have fulfilled both of these criteria?" Garen asked gentle. "Oh right, I remember our team has a death index every month, right?"

Kitten’s face turned pale as she tried to swallow her saliva.

"Yes… You have.. Fulfilled them!" He nodded aggressively. "I support you as the team leader!! Without a doubt!! I will be the first one to punch whoever rejects this motion!!"

Garen clapped as he smiled.

"See, isn’t that easy?" He touched his chin. "I personally think I am rather broad-minded, right?"

"Broad-minded! Very broad-minded!" Kitten immediately pulled out her thumb. You were literally threatening me in broad daylight!" She tried to weep and had goosebumps all over her body as she felt the gigantic dragon head behind her.

The remaining members knew that Garen meant to harm to Kitten, and decided to watch everything unfold. This incident had revealed Ninehead’s true strength, and this inhuman strength had everyone recognizing him as the team leader.

Afterall, strength is the only thing that could ensure your safety during this chaotic era.

Chapter 377: Veins 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As daylight broke, the off-angled sunlight dyed the clouds in a faint gold color.

In the abandoned city beside the Pumpkin Farm.

Countless black buildings were placed beside each other; the place was dead silent. The surface of the buildings were dull and some of the glass doors were shattered with a few glass shards left behind.

At the center of the square field, a sculpture at the center of the circular fountain was slightly slanted with deep cracks at the right side of the floor. It seemed like someone had attacked the floor with a sword nearby and created this crack, as it propagated to the fountain, causing the sculpture to slant.

The grass on the floor was all dark green and dry,wilted. It formed a guardrail as it attached itself to the chain and a short stone column together.

There was a tall man in black armor standing beside the guard rail.

He placed one of his legs on the stone column and carefully scanned the surrounding.

The man took down his hood, revealing a handsome, white and tender face. He had a silky smooth golden hair at shoulder length and also three red dots on his forehead as a birthmark. He was Garen, who was going after the leader of the silver masked man.

He looked around his surroundings as if he were trying to pick up some sound with his ear.

A faint golden halo came from behind and landed on his feet, lighting up the wilted grassfield.

"I have already spotted you, come out." Garen shouted calmly. His voice traveled far and reverberated constantly in the deserted city.

"You have been trying to escape from me for about a day now, and you’ve exhausted all your options. I believe that you do not have the ability to send a message within a short distance." Garen put away his leg as he started to wander around the fountain.

Suddenly, black mud moved at the bottom of the fountain.

Ahh!!!

As someone gave off a deafening scream, the mud spread about and a bloody red figure rushed towards Garen.

Boom!

The air behind Garen bent, as if there was a rigid transparent force pushing back the bloody figure back into the pool of mud.

The red figure rolled a few times in the mud before it got up dizzily, revealing his physical appearance.

Unexpectedly, it was a man with blood all over him. His lower body was no longer there, save for his upper body. He had nothing with him from the waist down below, as if he was cut waist down.

This half bodied man was muscular, and covered in blood. His head was similar to of a locust, long and had two antennas on his head. His body was covered with a series of hard objects, as if he was wearing a layer of armor.

With only his upper body, he was about as tall as half a man. After rolling on the floor for a few times, he dizzily stood up and floated in the air. There was no visible support from his lower body, he was simply levitating off the ground.

He revealed two of his sharp claws and charged towards Garen once more. However, his upper body was bitten by a shapeless mouth as he was charging in.

Chomp!

With a sounding crisp, the upper body man was torn into millions of red pieces. Soon after landing on the floor, the crystals melted and became a pool of blood and seeped into the ground.

"That’s the fifteenth." Garen frowned.

After leaving the Red Team behind, he had been pursuing the leader of the Silver Masked Man from the pumpkin farm to here since last night.

This seemingly dead city was filled with these bloody half bodied creatures. They were everywhere, hidden in any possible spots and would often attacked people.

These half bodied creatures had incredible speed, and any totem users whose main attribute was not agility would definitely barely be able handle them, and at best, could only defend against them. However, Garen was different. His five senses were extremely sharp, and with his terrifying precision from his Secret Techniques, he would be totally safe with only two dragon heads as his defense. Two mouths with the radius of one meter each were like his shield, protecting him at all times.

These half bodied creatures didn’t possess any power strength, and their strength was at the level of a form one totem user at best. It would be an useful option if it was used to fight against a commoner, but if it were to be used against Garen…

Even if he were to stand still and let them attack him, no one would know how many hours they would take to break his defense.

Suddenly, the familiar footsteps could be faintly heard deep in the city. It was fast paced yet tiring. The sound was very weak, and he wasn’t sure how far it is.

Garen obviously heard it and he started grinning as he went towards that direction. Although he seemed to be very slow, every step he took was at least a few meters apart and it was as fast as a commoner sprinting.

The opponent clearly didn’t have any more energy to spare, as the he had deactivated his Acceleration Tactic. Without the support of the totem, he could only use his legs to run.

Garen guessed that even if he were to stop pursuing him here, he would most likely not survive in this city for long, as this city had more than just the form one creature.

The footsteps became clearer in front of him.

The library, which was shaped like a mountain, had three tips at the top, and there were two grey gargoyles standing by the entrance of the library.

As Garen sprinted towards it, his footsteps kept reverberating within the city as if there were many people running at the same time.

Masi!!

A raging roar came from the library. It was so loud that even the ground started to tremble and even the small pebbles started to move up and down.

It sounded like a language and yet it also sounded like a meaningless roar.

Boom!!

As the sound of a glass breaking could be heard, and a person was sent flying out of the library and landed heavily onto a sculpture in front of the library. After a thud, the human figure dropped down from the sculpture and laid down on the ground.

It was the black shirted silver masked man who ran in the library a moment ago.

He gasped heavily as he tried to get himself up from the ground but to no avail. He seemed to have sprained his waist.

Boom! Boom Boom!!

Heavy footsteps could be heard inside the library, as if there was a gigantic monster walking about inside it.

Soon, the footsteps diminished and everything was silent once again.

Garen looked inside the library from afar as he wondered what kind of creature lurked inside it and it seemed to be very strong.

However, his first objective was to capture the silver masked man.

With a stomp from his feet, his motion became blur and leaped a few hundred meters and directly stood behind him

The opponent saw the sudden appearance of a human figure, whose shadows completely covered him from behind.

He was stunned.

"You caught up in the end." His voice sounded very bitter under his mask. "According to the regulations of the nobles, I have the right to pay for actions in exchange for my freedom and life. I hope you, as a noble, would allow me to repay my debt."

"What’s inside there?" Garen didn’t reply him as he looked into the library with interest.

The opponent was stunned by his behavior but immediately reacted. "I don’t know." He laughed wryly.

"When I was here last week, there was no such creature. Now it suddenly appears here. It seems to have come out from the cracks between the stones. We had observed the surrounding before and did not see such huge creatures within the diameter of hundred kilometers.

"You don’t know?" Garen was slightly surprised. "Didn’t you guys create these creatures?"

"That is indeed true. The Silver Masked Man shook his head. "However, everything seems to be out of hand the moment the people from the Black Sky had discovered the Black Copper Mine. I swear that during my time performing experiments in the Black Sky, I have never seen such a creature. Never!"

Garen suddenly recalled the existence of a giant creature in this city. If the giant creature in the city was an experiment created by the Black Sky, no one would have believed it, since if the Black Sky could get hold of such a strong creature, they would have taken over the world already.

"Did you mention Black Copper Mine just now? What’s that?" He questioned again as it was something he had never heard of.

The Silver Masked Man secretly gave out a sigh of relief.

"If you promise not to kill me, I will tell you everything I know."

"Sure." Garen nodded. "I still need you to send a message to the remaining members of the Black Sky. Why would I want to kill you?"

The Silver Masked Man was stunned and couldn’t utter a single word as he looked at Garen’s expression as if it was the natural thing to do.

"I am very regretful at the moment. If only I knew this incident was so troublesome, I wouldn’t have made a move on my own."

"Let’s hear it, what’s a Black Copper Mine?" Garen asked coldly.

The Silver Masked Man tried his best to get up from the ground as he leaned against the sculpture.

"The Black Copper Mine, in a way, is the source of all the aberrated creatures. I once worked at a Senior Workshop in the Black Sky’s experimenting group, so I know this secret very well."

He took out a red liquid from within his pocket.

"You don’t mind if I eat some medicine, right?"

"Go ahead." Garen nodded. "Your body isn’t in good condition. I can catch you even if you run anyway."

The Silver Masked Man smiled wryly.

"It started when we discovered an abandoned altar at the bottom of a ruin. This altar was made entirely out of a metal that was neither silver or gold. It was completely black, and it was a metal that none of were familiar with. As the first surveyor of the Black Sky discovered this altar and this new metal, the whole of the Black Sky community was interested in it. We sent out a large amount of researchers into the altar to study this unique metal."

"The altar itself hadn’t much of a purpose as it was abandoned a long time ago. However, the researchers found something shocking once they cut open this metal that was used to make this altar.

"What did they find?" Garen was caught in the curiosity.

"They discovered that this metal’s properties are very similar to that of copper, so they named it Black Copper. They also discovered that there was a huge amount of Black Copper stored underneath the altar thereafter." The Silver Masked Man smiled wryly once more. "This Black Copper possessed a shocking property."

"Property?"

Chapter 378: Veins 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Yes, you just need a little bit of this type of metal in order to corrode any part or organ of any creature’s body. It will produce a special type of secreted substance that, once filled inside the creature’s body, will give it a terrifying nature that allows it to counter the Totem Light. It would be similar to making water into a type of ice that could be compared to steel. With the emergence of this strange and powerful transformation ability, you could only imagine the excitement on the faces of the expert researchers. This is truly a discovery that will transcend time and eras!" said the silver-faced man, shaking his head. "As for how the crystal derivator came into being, we used the resonance technique that we had perfected much earlier, and coordinated it with this type of creature-corroding black copper, to forge the current crystal derivator known by everyone. However, during the last stage of the experiment, an accident occurred."

Garen looked at him silently, waiting for his next sentence.

"The accident was uncovered by an unknown, ordinary researcher. He realised a terrifying truth about the black copper. This strange metal was apparently allowing monsters that it had corroded to naturally evolve themselves! Once he had observed the incident and confirmed his suspicions, the black copper seemed to have a sense of awareness, and once it had noticed that it had been found out, proceeded to suddenly hurry up the evolution process. When the researcher raised the alarm, the other Totem users on stand-by rushed over, but it was too late by then. The monsters that had been successfully evolved has grasped a strength that surpassed the base’s control, and they ended up massacring twenty-five Obscuro base strongholds. A large number of the monsters fled the base, because we were unable to control them at all."

"Does this mean that, the release of the Aberration monsters this time, was not let out intentionally as part of the idea that you announced to return the world back to its right state? Instead, this incident, from beginning to the end, was just an accident?" Garen asked in a serious tone.

"It’s exactly as you said," answered the silver-faced man feebly. "Thus, the current situation is completely out of our control by now. A lot of areas have suddenly experienced sightings of unknown powerful monsters and strange phenomena that they’ve never seen before. We are unsure of the current occurrences, and all the surviving researchers are working hard in their research. In the end, they came up with a terrifying conclusion that the black copper contained an activated life force, and seemed to be rapidly changing the natural circulation system of the world. They brought up a frightening proportional formula, the Buffett formula. Every time it forged a black copper-polluted creature, it would simultaneously release enough influence to aberrate five other creatures of the same form. Once everyone had calculated the model, they came up with this growth formula, and although there was a complicated process in the middle, the conclusion was as such."

"Even though we already knew this, we could help but constantly attempt to create a power of our own. Once the black copper’s polluted corrosion became even stronger, to the point where even advanced Totem evolutions were beginning to appear, natural Aberration creatures of the same advanced level began appearing on Earth, and once we noticed this, the natural Aberration creatures had already evolved at a faster speed than our own, and we lost all control of the situation. Some of the monsters had even evolved to a stage that even we were unable to derive."

"Then were there any appearances of monsters that did not seem abnormal but were actually unusually strong?" Garen asked again.

"There definitely were, but these phenomena would only occur a short while after the situation was out of our control. The Obscuro researchers realised that the new natural circulation systems built by the black copper in a short span of time were difficult to differentiate in many places, and resulted in many incomprehensible natural phenomena occurring in many places, such as the music in the pumpkin farm." The silver-faced man was well-versed in professional knowledge, and the clarity of his explanations were far superior to than Reylan previously.

"So where can this type of black copper be found?" Garen suddenly gained an interest in the source of this metal.

"The crystal derivators have a small amount of black copper dissolved inside them, but if you’re thinking of obtaining the exact type of metal from its source, you need to go to Obscuro. This type of metal is highly controlled by them, because every time a monster is forged, there is a chance that it will cause five more to be naturally aberrated. It is similar to the Poisonous Dove Flower, it only needs to happen once, before it will happen the second time, and the third, before it becomes deep-rooted inside, and inextricable. In order to counter the unimaginably powerful Royal Alliance of Luminarists, we had no other choice. The Elder Parliament of the Royal Alliance of Luminarists commanded the three departments, and was a long-time established organization that had not been changed in the last thousand years. If the deviated monsters had not pinned the Elder Parliament down, the three departments would have focused most of their concentration on the monsters, and we would not have as much time to layout our plans calmy, or even develop our own strength.

Garen heard a new term once again.

"What kind of organization is the Elder Parliament?" According to his previous history, he had never known about the existence of such an organization before.

"It’s the highest decision-making organization in the Royal Alliance of Luminarists, and also the strongest existing group in the Alliance as well. They were a huge shadow that shrouded over both the East Continent and the West Continent for over a thousand years, and every change that occurred never failed to be part of their behind-the-scenes plan. The three departments of the Royal Alliance of Luminarists were originally loose organizations, and if they were not combined by Elder Parliament, they would not have become an organization like the three departments, as each individual country would have wanted their own way, thus causing mutual conquests," said the silver-faced man as he glanced at Garen with a surprised look. "I assume that the time you’ve spent in the three departments has been too short. The higher level ones, and the ones with more qualifications all have an opportunity to participate in the department’s arbitration assembly which is held every twenty years, to ensure that the attitudes and wrongdoings of each country is dealt with in a balanced and correct manner. This is to prevent the abuse of power in the Royal Alliance of Luminarists."

"Then why have I not come across anyone from the Elder Parliament that you spoke of earlier? Don’t tell me that so many powerful individuals just disappeared without a trace like that?" asked Garen in a surprised tone. "Why hasn’t there been any trace of them even after such large-scale incidents?"

"Everything was underground. The strongest monsters were always lurking underground, and were endlessly evolving. The West Farm defense line that they created was an underground defense line that extended above ground. If that wasn’t the case, do you think that the Totem users and their manpower would have been able to resist the monster’s invasion? Initially, Obscuro was able to defeat even the strongest Elemental Generals. But once the monsters rushed underground into the human cities, the consequences were disastrous. If we Obscuros did not hide ourselves deep inside enough, and well-concealed enough, we would have been killed by the monsters long ago."

Garen felt that he had grasped a better understanding of the situation now. Initially, he was uncertain because even though the Royal Alliance of Luminarists did not seem exceptionally strong, the Obscuro Society was still afraid to face them directly, and only dared to attack them secretly from underground instead. Now he knew that it was because the Elder Parliament had always been watching from afar.

"Come with me, we’ll go in and take a look." Garen pondered for awhile, before turning his head upwards and looking at the large library building in front of him.

The silver-faced man smiled bitterly but remained silent, because he knew that this was an order and not a request. After he drank the recovery drug earlier, he was now slightly better and had managed to stand up. The white coloured Totem Light on his body had lit up once again, and was a sign that the recovery drug had an effect on the Totem Light.

Garen lead the way and walked inside the main door of the library.

From outside, he could see that the rows of thin, straight windows in the library were all broken, and a few broken pieces of glass remained on the window sill. Only a part of the main door was left in the doorway, while the other half had been bitten off by something unknown, exposing the rough black coloured metallic section inside.

As he walked inside through the main door, the morning’s pale gold light beams glittered in from the window on the left side and fell on the floor, causing the floating dust in the air to be seen vaguely.

The ground was littered with broken benches, and the black marble floor was filled was cracked and filled with rubble. There were also a few large pits that were over a meter deep, and the inside resembled magma-like honeycomb that had been melted and condensed again.

In the middle of the hall stood a large silver sphere. The sphere had a diameter of over two meters, and was propped upwards by a thick white pillar below it.

The entire surface of the sphere was covered in multicoloured handwritten words, as if they were messages that people from the past had left behind.

Garen evaded the deep pit carefully, and walked towards the big sphere that was in front of him.

He stroked the various writings on the sphere gingerly and noticed that the words were written in language that he could not understand, which were probably the specialized language of this little country.

Garen looked for a while, but could not find a message he could understand.

After looking for a while, he gave up, and returned his hands to his sides, before suddenly realising that his own fingers were now covered in a thin layer of black dust. The dust seemed to have some corrosive properties, causing Garen’s fingers to hurt slightly.

He had released his Totem Light earlier, but apparently there were still poisonous substances that could come into contact with his skin without his permission?

It was important to note that the Totem Light was connected to one’s consciousness. When the outside world contained substances that could potentially harm one’s body, it would automatically filter out the harmful substance. The same principle was used against its enemies, because once it noticed an enemy that harboured hostility towards itself, the Totem Light would produce defensive measures.

This acted as an exterior skin-like layer that would sense whether the substances from the outside world would harm its main body. It was immediate and connected to one’s consciousness, and possessed an independent judgement system.

During the stages where the Forgers and Luminarists were first forging their Totems, it would first find a way to move the core inside. This was the foundation of building Primitive Totems. Once the Core Totems were formed, it would then enable the core component ability.

Meanwhile, there were currently substances that were able to break through this layer of decision-type defense, and had injured Garen’s skin. This was somewhat incomprehensible to Garen. Although he had not learned a lot of things from Teacher Emin, fortunately he was a legitimate Luminarist by birth, and was very clear about certain basic principles.

He began to ponder deeply.

Bang!!

Suddenly, a dull noise echoed from the right.

Garen glanced towards the side, slightly shaken suddenly.

He could see a strong-looking black horse that was glaring at him with bloodshot eyes.

The black horse had a mane like a male lion that it flipped around constantly. It’s whole body was incomparably black, with no trace of variation. From head to toe, it seemed like he could vaguely see the bright, black gloss reflecting off it.

The strangest part was that the bottom half of the black horse was not made up of flesh and blood, but was a large black paint covered horse carriage instead.

The bottom half of the horse had a black carriage growing out of it directly. It had no hind legs, but in its place were two large black wheels that were attached to the carriage.

Tch!!

The black horse exhaled a large gust of air from its nostrils angrily towards the ground, blowing up a large pile of gravel and dust.

The moment Garen laid eyes on the black horse carriage, he was frozen in place.

"This is… could it really be…??!!" His mind suddenly remembered a name that he had once seen before.

"It’s here again!!" The silver-faced man suddenly shouted behind him, and immediately hid behind Garen’s back, as an unusually scared expression appeared on his face.

"Is he very strong?" Garen asked in a serious tone.

"Incredibly strong, and deviantly so!!" exclaimed the silver-faced man. "I absolutely cannot defeat it! It can only attack me!" Once he thought of the earlier situation, his heart began to thump inside his chest. The speed of this black horse was not exceptionally fast, but it could move in the blink of an eye, and could also any type of substantial object. Also, when it truly wanted to strike its enemies, it would produce truly high-impact damages. It will definitely very strange.

"I never thought that something like this would still exist…" Garen knew that this was not a mere coincidence. "I should have thought of this earlier. To think that there would still be such a thing…"

Chapter 379: Cloud Crow 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen did not seem surprised.

Once the City Troll had appeared, the appearance of other mythical creatures was no longer a surprise. However, the fact that the mythical creatures that once appeared in the Secret Technique world were apparently appearing in the Totem world now, was the thing that he felt was truly strange.

He looked at the black horse carriage in front of him. Suddenly, the name of the creature floated up clearly in Garen’s mind.

"Underworld Carriage."

He squinted both of his eyes.

"According to the Grindor myths, this horse carriage is able to take living people into the land of the dead. It is also extremely fierce, and eats two meat meals and the souls of fifteen sinners every day."

He began to walk circles around the Underworld Carriage slowly.

The black horse turned around in the same direction as him, while it’s large horse eyes became more and more bloodshot.

Tch!

Two gusts of white air shot out of its nostrils again.

Mars!!

A scream that sounded almost like a human’s cry came out of the black horse’s mouth. The loud noise shook up the surroundings and made a whooshing noise as a large amount of dust and rubble fell off the ceiling, as if it was a layer of dusty rain.

The Underworld Carriage charged forward suddenly as both of its hooves dragged the carriage wheels furiously towards Garen. A cloud of thick yellow fog escaped from the body of the horse carriage and appeared at Garen’s side suddenly, as if it was alive, and covered him wholly.

The speed of the black horse increased rapidly until it quickly seemed like a black line that was charging towards Garen furiously.

Garen’s eyes widened. He was completely unable to react in time, and could only feel a powerful force crashing into his body at full force.

He felt as if his arms and legs were completely bound by a strange force, causing his reflexes to become unusually slow. Meanwhile, his opponent’s speed became frighteningly stron in the blink of an eye.

Bang!!!

The black horse carriage crashed against the front of Garen’s body violently.

The black horse and the man crashed into each other and flew outside backwards. They floated in the air for a while, before crashing into the library wall behind them with a ‘bang’.

The wall lit up and a layer of transparent ripples appeared suddenly, blocking the man and the horse completely. It was different from a normal window, as the wall seemed to be covered with a layer of an unknown defensive force field that did not allow any attacks that would harm the main body of the library building.

Garen and the black horse crashed into the wall together, shaking up a large pile of dust and gravel. It seemed as if they had crashed into an ashen sea, as the dust and sand resembled a splash of water that gushed out through the wall and splattered everywhere, as if it was pouring down on them like rain.

At once, loud crashing noises began to echo throughout the library continuously.

Mars!!

The Underworld Carriage screamed again, before it passed through Garen completely, merging into the wall, as if it had changed from a solid object into a virtual object immediately, instantly transforming into an invisible state, before gradually disappearing.

Garen was stuck in the middle of the deep pit in the wall with his arms and legs spread open, shaking his head, before he broke away and released himself, bringing down a pile of rubble with him.

The sound of falling grains of sand could be heard, as well as the noise of Garen spitting out the dirt and sand from his mouth. The ground below his feet was illuminated with a glossy black gleam, before his entire body fell from midair suddenly.

"Sure enough… it’s pretty strange." With a ‘plop’, Garen landed on the floor steadily. Transparent defense ripples were constantly permeating off Garen’s entire body. It came from the Salamander’s giant mouth that was used to resist the attack earlier.

"But its strength was nothing special," he commented indifferently.

At this moment, the silver-faced man was hiding behind the large silver sphere. He saw that Garen had gotten hit, but still managed to nonchalantly comment on how the black horse carriage’s strength was no big deal, causing his heart to feel completely aghast.

When he was hit earlier, he suffered serious injuries immediately. The Totem Light surrounding his body had just healed slightly, before it was completely scrapped. Meanwhile, his Core Totem suffered even worse damages, while his Silver Totems suffered heavy injuries for the second time consecutively.

However, the force inflicted upon Garen during the hit was even stronger than what he suffered, as the black horse had only struck him once, while Garen suffered a hit that caused him to be stuck in the wall, but apparently was not making the slightest fuss about it.

Shh!!

The Underworld Carriage passed through the wall in front of Garen again, as if it was emerging out of water. From its unreal, translucent state, it solidified immediately, and transformed into a physical object. It seemed like it knew that the opponent in front of it was no longer easy to defeat. Thus, it began to cautiously turn circles around Garen.

The wheels of the black horse carriage made noises as they rolled on the ground, which then melded with the crisp horse hoof trotting noises, sounding unusually clear.

Once again, the carriage of the Underworld Carriage begin emitting a large amount of yellow fog again. The yellow fog floated less than a meter’s distance away from the carriage, before appearing at Garen’s side in the blink of an eye.

It seemed to have a life force of its own when it covered the Totem Light on Garen’s body completely.

"It’s here again!!" Garen knew clearly now. "This kind of smoke seems to be extracting my speed and giving it to the Underworld Carriage." He could clearly feel the changes on his body now, and noticed that his four limbs had become heavier, while his reactions had become much slower.

Meanwhile, the movements of the black horse on the opposite side of him were now more agile, and much faster.

"So it’s like this! It extracts its opponents speed and adds it to its own body. No wonder its speed was much faster compared to how it was before. Apparently, all of this was the state of my own speed," Garen pondered seriously.

This was extremely tricky. Garen knew his own speed clearly. At his current 6 point agility, most speed-type Totems could not even match his speed. However, his speed had been extracted by the Underworld Carriage, one increased while the other decreased, causing the speeds of both parties to undergo extreme changes suddenly.

"According to the myths, the Underworld Carriage was smashed alive by the herculean Boerger. As Boerger had received the chaos Warhammer from the Earth Mother, he became immensely powerful, but suffered slow movements in return. This made it impossible for the Underworld Carriage to sap his speed, as he was already slow enough. It made no difference whether his speed was extracted or not," thought Garen as he remembered the story of the myth. "Its unknown whether this story is a myth or not, and the supposed Boerger is historically just a deified human being that loved to boast about his own legendary feats, and whether or not this encounter truly happened, was something that we do not know yet," thought Garen deeply as a train of thought flashed through his mind. However, he still could not think of a way to face the Underworld Carriage.

"The dumbest method would be to wait until the moment before he charges at me, before I fight back harder." Garen became more vigilant, and stared at the Underworld Carriage in front of him. "Who knows, maybe after I’ve understood this thing better, I could even ride it into the mythical underworld and look around. This is the mystical carriage that can take living beings into the underworld after all."

Regarding the underworld in the Grindor myths, Garen had been longing for it for a long time.

Mars!!!

Finally, the Underworld Carriage could not take it anymore, so it bent its head downwards, and charged violently towards Garen. Its body was surrounded by yellow fog, and its speed was frighteningly fast.

Inside the hall, the only thing that could be seen was the horse carriage charging rapidly until it just looked like a yellow line that was crashing into Garen who was still standing in the same spot. The black and yellow creature let out a fearsome crashing noise and a large cloud of yellow fog spread out towards all four corners.

Crash!!!

Hiss!!

Garen sunk both of his feet deep into the ground, drawing two long black scratches on the floor, as his back crashed into the wall once again.

The horse’s head that was extremely close to him was now pressed against his arms, and he could clearly see the black mane behind the horse’s head that seemed like waves that were constantly moving. Its smooth satiny skin was unusually glossy, and its strong muscular profile moved along with its large tendons.

"Now!"

Garen’s forehead was suddenly lit up with three red dots, before a large red Eight Headed Dragon floated out behind him slowly.

Roar!!!!

The eight heads of the Eight Headed Dragon turned towards the sky and roared loudly in unison.

Terrifying sound waves began to quake. After a ‘bang’, the air seemed as if it had exploded, as shrouds of white gas began to spread out in all four directions. The interior of the entire library was filled with the continuous echoes of countless humming noises.

The large silver sphere rolled unto the floor because of the vibrations caused by the loud roars, and was almost smashed by the silver-faced man.

Most of the engraved stone patterns on the wall also loosened, causing broken pieces to fall off.

Initially, the silver-faced man’s Totem Light had already become extremely weak, but now it had been shaken up badly, making it hard for him to draw breaths, as his chest was pressed down and in an extremely uncomfortable manner, making him want to vomit even though he could not.

He dared not waste any more time, so he followed the corners of the wall and limped out of the library hall, before falling in front of the main doorway. Both of his eyes were seeing stars, and he was in a numb, blurry state, unable to see anything.

The strange thing was that the moment he exited the library, the noises behind him became much softer suddenly.

A few seconds later, and with much difficulty, the silver-faced man finally breathed a sigh of relief.

Seeing his own humiliated state, a little while later, he began to cry, before hitting himself in the thigh angrily.

"Did it have to be a deviant…."

Feeling that his tears were about to spill out, he buried his head angrily in his sleeve.

I’m an Elemental General, and I cannot cry! I cannot cry!!

He wiped his tears away angrily.

"To think I would encounter such a deviant! I can’t take it anymore!! Whoever truly loves him can take my place!!" He leapt up immediately and tore the badge off his chest furiously, before turning around to walk away.

Roar!!

Suddenly, the sound of a roar echoed from behind him.

The silver-faced man froze at once, as he remembered his current situation, and realized that he was no longer a free man, because he had become Garen’s prisoner.

"For a civilian to be able to kill another civilian, that was the only thing that allowed me to turn from a criminal to a general!" He mumbled softly to himself, before he placed his backside on the floor of the main doorway, as his hands rummaged inside his pockets and took out a smashed grey cigarette that he struck against the floor. The cigarette lit up immediately, and he took a delicious puff.

"Almost 23 deviants, two left in Obscuro, and three with the Royal Alliance of Luminarists." He arched his head upwards and looked at the bright sunlight in the sky. "The whole world is a deviant, and in this deviant world, normal people like me should always just remain as civilians and call it a day."

After spewing out a string of curses, his mood seemed as if it had lightened significantly. Hence, he just sat here and waited for the outcome of the incident that was happening in the library right now.

It was not as if he had never thought of escaping. On the contrary, he knew that no matter where he ran, his opponent would be able to find him at any moment. This infinite loop of ‘yesterdays’ was already becoming too much for him, and he was tired. After all, he was not a professional combat member.

****************

Both of Garen’s eyes gleamed with a dim red light, as he glared at the Underworld Carriage on the opposite side of him coldly.

The incomparably loud dragon roars apparently had no effect on its opponent, as the Underworld Carriage had merely moved a short distance backwards, while of the surrounding sound waves had been completely blocked off by the yellow fog around its body.

Garen detected the Eight Headed Dragon. Its eight heads were taking turns to fight, and for the Eight Headed Dragon with terrifying regenerative powers, this was no big deal at all.

The man and the horse stood beside the large silver sphere together, as the situation seemed as if it had come to a standstill.

Garen was also out of moves, and did not know how to face his opponent.

His speed had been extracted, and he was a moment away from being sapped completely of it to the point where he would not be able to fight at all. The Eight Headed Dragon’s attacks were also completely ineffective towards it, including using its dragon’s mouth to bite it directly, as it was completely blocked off by the yellow fog.

Meanwhile, the Underworld Carriage struck Garen relentlessly from the wall, the floor, and the ceiling. It charged towards him from various strange angles, hitting it continuously, but ineffectively.

Chapter 380: Cloud Crow 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s hood did not get shaken off his head when he got hit and was sent flying, but fortunately, he did not suffer any injuries.

Both parties were now entangled with each other, and had seemed to sense the toughness of their opponents, causing the situation to end up in stalemate.

Time passed as the minutes and seconds ticked by.

After an unknown duration of time, the sunlight lessened gradually, while the sky began to darken slowly.

The Underworld Carriage finally let out a long cry as it moved backwards slowly and merged directly into a small area of shadows behind it.

Mars!

Its bloodshot eyes glared at Garen, as if it was remembering this bastard that rendered itself helpless for the first time.

Quickly, its body and the carriage entered the shadows together and suddenly, it turned around and galloped even faster in the shadows, before leaping off.

With pin-drop silence, the Underworld Carriage merged into the wall directly, and disappeared completely.

The continuous cries of ‘mars’ could be heard softly from a distance, and it continued echoing throughout the library. However, the further it went, the softer the noises became, until they disappeared completely.

Garen stood in his initial spot quietly, as impatient feelings began bubbling up inside him.

He had tried all of the Secret Techniques inside the pressure box, but the speed that had been extracted from him was too great, and had almost reached 80%, resulting in him being able to keep up in regards to his reactions, but unable to keep up when it came to his body movements. However, this was not a big deal, because as long as he had the ability to predict, it was not an issue.

The most important thing right now was that the speed of the Underworld Carriage had become too fast, almost like a flash of yellow lightning, and in the blink of an eye, it had already struck Garen’s body again.

Moreover, the Underworld Carriage was also completely immune towards Totem attacks. With Garen unable to keep up with the physical attacks while his Totem attacks were completely unusable, there was no way for him to fight!

Garen fought until his head was filled with rage.

Looking at the empty library hall, Garen sighed in relief and turned around to walk outside to see if the silver-faced man was still there.

His footsteps stopped suddenly, and he stood frozen in place.

The entire hall had suddenly undergone a strange transformation.

The gravel on the floor began to float upwards, flying towards the ceiling, and embedding themselves into their initial places that were once cracked grooves.

The large silver sphere that had rolled off was now moving on its own, as it floated gently back to its original position, like rewinding footage in a video, as it orbited and rolled back in the exact same manner in which it rolled down.

A large pile of dust and sand flew everywhere and landed on the statue next to the wall, gathering there again.

Shrouds of dust began to float again, rising up continuously without a single sound. The world seemed as if it had inverted itself, as dust and gravel began to rise up from the ground like a weird kind of rain.

The wooden chairs and tables that were smashed to ruins earlier also began to move on their own, as they rolled back to their original positions, before a large pile of wood shavings flew back unto their surfaces, making them whole again, as clouds of dust covered them once more, becoming thicker and thicker.

The large pits on the ground were instantly filled up again, as the cracks disappeared and were covered by the initial black marble, before a thick layer of dust covered the surface.

The entire library seemed as if it was undergoing a silent time reversal, as all of the damaged areas quickly returned to their initial states.

Finally, everything returned to order.

The library was finally restored to the firs moment when Garen stepped inside. There were no traces of the Underworld Carriage’s movements.

A confused expression appeared on his face as his eyes scanned across the library hall. At this moment, his mind was at a complete loss.

"What’s going on here?"

Garen walked towards the area where he had first been hit, and stood below a large pit in the wall, looking upwards at the place where the large pit had been formed earlier.

It was perfect without any damage, and he could even see a little spider web in the corner of the wall, with a translucent spider shell on the surface.

It was not in a high position, so Garen reached his finger outwards and pressed it against the wall.

It was straight and smooth, and the surface was covered with a layer of white dust, while the black dust from earlier was now gone.

Unconvinced, he pressed down harder this time.

Ka-chak!

Multiple depressions appeared on the wall suddenly. Moments later, they were quickly restored to their initial states. Garen pulled his fingers back and looked at his surroundings, as a thoughtful look appeared on his face.

He turned around and walked out of the main door. Once he had exited the main door, he looked at the silver-faced man who was sitting on the stairs at the doorstep. This guy had apparently fallen asleep, and it seemed as if he had relaxed for a moment, and allowed everything to go downhill from there, to just do what he was supposed to do. He was even snoring.

The black clothes on the man’s body were dirty and full of dust, while some parts of it were even torn.

On the floor beside him, a black badge was discarded there. A peculiar image had been engraved on the badge. It was a silver sun that was releasing countless light rays, and in the middle of the sun was an eye with a black pupil.

Garen kept the badge.

He walked over to kick the silver-faced man.

"Wake up. Hey!"

The silver-faced man toppled over, and woke up instantly. He stood up abruptly.

"It’s done?!" He turned around and looked at Garen frantically.

"What do you mean ‘it’s done’?" Garen was speechless. "We’ll need your strength now. Take me to the Obscuro bases, all of the bases that you know."

He wanted to make a move now. His agility was slightly short of perfection, and his Secret Techniques needed to be increased.

"Bases… I know where the other two fugitives must be headed towards!" answered the silver-faced man immediately. His reaction was completely abrupt, without any hesitation.

Garen glanced at him unconsciously again.

"Remove your mask then."

The silver-faced man smiled bitterly, and removed the mask from his face.

He exposed his unpleasant, middle-aged face. It was a regular, unassuming face with a black beard that contained a few strands of white hair. His eyes were sunken, and he looked severely sleep-deprived.

"What’s your name?" Garen asked immediately.

"Windling. My name is Windling," answered the middle-aged man honestly.

"Windling?!" Garen nearly vomited when he heard that. Looking at that unpleasant face, Garen could not help but think where he should vomit. His name and face did not suit one another at all.

"Alright, Windling," said Garen as he begrudgingly accepted the contrast. "The precious heirlooms that you stole from me during the siege yesterday, bright them all out now."

Windling took an item out honestly, it was an exquisite black pocket watch, and passed it to Garen.

Garen took it and turned it over in his hand.

The pocket watch was extremely small, and only half the size of a regular pocket watch. There were neither numbers nor words on its face, not even a scale. Instead, there was only a needle that was constantly moving around in a circle.

"What is this?"

"It’s the Clouded Crow front," Windling explained. "We call it the Cloud Crow front. It can catalyze more than ten thousand Spiritualized Black Crow Totems to form a cylindrical front to isolate and detain one’s enemies. The cost of its imprisonment ability is extremely great, and after you smashed it to pieces yesterday, a part of this precious heirloom’s structure was also destroyed. All that is left right now is its catalyzed black crow abilities."

"What level does this precious heirloom belong to?"

"It’s a replica of a level two precious heirloom," Windling explained. "You know it as the ultimate precious heirloom replica. Inside Obscuro, we separate our precious heirlooms into categories such as regular, ultimate, and original. We categorize them into levels one to three, to simplify the process of organizing them based on their power, such as the original precious heirloom being equivalent to a level three precious heirloom. The Cloud Crow front is used an Obscuro imitation of a defense front, and is considered as a level two precious heirloom. There are many level two precious heirlooms, and almost every powerful leader possesses one. This was also the reward that we received after our first contribution in Obscuro."

Garen’s eyes flashed.

"So you’re saying, that the Obscuro Society also has a level three original precious heirloom?"

"Yes, this is a precious heirloom that can be reused, and it’s most powerful strength is equivalent to a form four Totem," said Windling as he stared at the pocket watch somewhat painfully. "Now, it belongs to you."

Garen smiled and flipped the pocket watch over to look at the line of silver words that had been engraved in its black-coloured back.

‘If giving up means being wide awake, then I will always choose to persist.’ It was written in Ender words.

"That line of words was engraved by the creator. He was my best friend, and also a top-level forger and researcher in Obscuro, but he has been dead for many years already." Windling had quietened down.

"How do I use this?" Garen flipped the pocket watch over in his hand.

"Imagine the Totem power flowing inside it, and every time you use it you will need a purple crystal. Just a reminder, the Totem power needed for this is extremely great, but of course, you can use your Totem Light to make up for it. The natures of both these things do not differ that much," reminded Windling quickly.

"Oh?"

Garen held the pocket watch in his hand, and tried to make his Totem power and Totem Light flow inside.

"The power of this precious heirloom is determined by how much Totem power and Totem Light you pour inside. The upper limit is form four. The range can be extremely broad," explained Windling as he moved backwards further away. This made it easier for Garen to experiment with the precious heirloom.

"The Cloud Crows that you forged will only have the mindset to attack, and will not be able to do anything else. Thus, you need to be careful when using this."

His voice trailed off.

Garen’s surroundings began to be filled with black mist instantly.

Large clouds of black mist began to diffuse from his surroundings, and the source of the mist apparently came from the pocket watch in his hand.

The mist circled above Garen’s head and finally froze there, before quickly transforming into little black crows. Some of them perched on Garen’s shoulders while other flew above his head. A few others searched around their surroundings with their little eyes for targets that they could attack.

The clouds of black mist continued to freeze, and the number of Cloud Crows increased rapidly and gradually, the entire main doorway of the library was completely covered in black mist.

Windling’s mouth gaped open for a while, but no words came out.

This momentum was similar to the momentum that they had created yesterday. The large cloud of black mist began to flow throughout the air in the library, resembling a long black river that came together and then separated.

Cawing noises filled their ears. It seemed as if the abandoned city had suddenly become lively again.

"How much Totem light does he really have…" murmured Windling, with an unreadable expression on his face.

Moments later, after the scene remained for half a minute, the Cloud Crows turned into black mist again, and flowed back into the pocket watch in Garen’s hand.

The black mist disappeared, and out came Garen’s calm face.

"This thing is not bad, its power is excellent, and its cost is not too high." Garen was extremely pleased with this precious heirloom.

The Eight Headed Dragon was his strongest Totem, as the remaining Totems could not be compared to it at all, because they were far too weak, and he planned to give up his control of them after a certain period of time, so that he could exchange them for other resources, to avoid wasting them.

The Eight Headed Dragon was too strong, if he took it out without thinking, it would not be long before others realized that his Totem was unlike everyone else’s. But once he obtained the Cloud Crow front, it made up for the shortcomings that he faced on a daily basis in this aspect.

Once he Spiritualized it to its final form four powers to adhere it completely to his daily needs, the stronger Eight Headed Dragon would not need to always show its face anymore. The current Eight Headed Dragon would always be in an imaginary form when it was released, as if its entire body had been Elementalized already. During a short span of time, he could pretend that it was merely in a spiritualized possessed form. However, after a long time, even a Totem user would know that this was abnormal.

Chapter 381: Purge 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In a forest on the border of Ender and Kovitan.

The afternoon sky was a shade of dark yellow near the top but gloomy and black in the middle. It was overcast and filled with large black clouds that rolled past.

The wind blew past, sometimes in strong gusts and other times weaker, making whooshing noises as it shook the trees.

Inside the forest, lots of boxy, square Chinese gardens stood upright in the middle. The gardens were only ten meters long and wide, quaint and quiet, and completely empty on the inside.

The interior of the gardens were filled with rows of black headstones, and in the middle stood a black minaret that was shaped like a sharp pencil lead.

The minaret was dark and gloomy, and was full of embossed portraits on its surface, while its surroundings were blocked off by protective metal fences.

On the right side below the tower, on the fresh green grass, Garen and Windling were standing beside the tower, and looking up at the minaret.

Both of them were dressed from head to toe in black clothes, but the clothes on Garen’s body was obviously much cleaner and tidier. Meanwhile, Windling’s clothes were torn and ruined, and somewhat embarrassing.

Garen walked inside through one of the broken fences, and reached his hand out to touch the surface of the minaret gently.

It was cool, and felt wooden to the touch. Hard shells were also stuck on the top, but big chunks of it fell off the moment they were touched, exposing a fat yellow caterpillar underneath.

"It looks old and worn. Are you sure this is the place?" Garen turned around and looked at Windling.

"I’m sure!" Windling shook his head vigorously. "This is one of the bases that I know. They don’t know that I’ve been captured by you, so they should not have shifted yet."

"It’s right below this tower?" Garen asked again.

"Indeed, it’s here!"

Garen squinted both of his eyes slightly.

"Step back."

Slight chills ran down Windling’s spine, as he backed off quickly and ran further away.

He walked not more than ten meters away, before he looked at the spot where Garen was standing, and noticed that a large cloud of black fog had started to diffuse there.

The black fog turned into Cloud Crows that circled around and rushed upwards, before releasing countless ear piercing cawing noises.

More than a hundred Cloud Crows gathered together, and charged downwards in a smashing movement. They seemed just like a black hammer.

Bang!!!

A heavy crashing noise could be heard, as the floor near the right side of the minaret instantly sunk in completely. Throughout the ten meter range, everything was smashed many meters deeper. A deep pit that had a radius of over ten meters suddenly appeared beside the minaret.

"Go!!"

A sharp voice that was unidentifiable as male or female rang out suddenly, as four human figures rushed out of the soil on the ground, like arrows that were flying in all four directions.

Garen groaned, and the hundred over Cloud Crows turned into a black stream that rushed towards the four people and wrapped around them. On the ground where he stood in the center, they now resembled a large "yuan" coin.

The Cloud Crows possessed a terrifying speed, which caused an afterimage, and moments later, they had managed to force the four figures backwards.

These four figures were all clad in black robes, and their leader had a physique that was unidentifiable as male or female, but was obviously skinny and weak.

"Who are you!?" After feeling the strong force field waves around them, the black robed person that was heading this group questioned Garen in a shrill voice, and glared at him angrily. "Do you know where this place is? This is the main Obscuro Society branch! How dare you attack this branch!? Do you not want your life!?"

"I was looking for your Obscuro Society!" Garen sneered, waving his right hand.

Strange cawing noises sounded through the air, as a large flock of Cloud Crows rushed towards them like a torrent, before submerging the four people completely.

There were only four people. One of them was a form three lower ranking general, while two others were merely Field-level, and were too weak.

The four of them had just released their totems, a black giant elephant and two dark yellow giant birds. They may have had other totems that were not released yet, but everything was completely submerged by the torrent of Cloud Crows. Even their cries of pain could not be heard.

The Cloud Crow torrent washed over after ten whole seconds. Then, it exposed the condition of the four people once again.

The four black-robed people had completely turned into four skeletons, as all of their flesh seemed as if it had rotted off cleanly, and all that remained were clean white bones.

A crisp whooshing noise sounded, as the four skeletons collapsed on the floor at the same time.

Their totems had also been instantly submerged by the Cloud Crow torrent, and the large elephant’s trumpet noises could not be heard anymore, as it had instantly turned into a large elephant skeleton, that quickly collapsed as well.

Garen raised the pocket watch in his hand and returned all of the Black Cloud Crows into the pocket watch, before glancing at the humans and totems on the ground.

He then glanced at his own Attribute Pane and noticed that his Potential Points were increasing, causing a satisfied expression to appear on his face immediately.

"Let’s go to the next base."

He lead the way into the outskirts of the woods.

A forced smile appeared on Windling’s face as he rushed to keep up, before both of their shadows disappeared quickly into the nearby forest.

*****************

Inside the light yellow arboreal forest

Clouds of black fog that looked like a snake wound through the forests, constantly searching for something. They would transform into crows occasionally, before turning back into black fog once again. It loomed in the background.

A little red bird with a lump on its head had just flew down and perched on a tree branch, before it was jolted by the passing black fog. The feathers of the red bird fell off quickly and turned into black dust, exposing the red muscles and skin underneath. Immediately, its skin shriveled up instantly as well, and less than a few seconds later, all that remained was the skeleton of a small bird, that made a cracking noise as it fell off the tree branch.

Windling stood below it, while a forced smile appeared on his face.

Boom!!

Near the front not far away, a loud quaking noise could be heard as a large number of trees were cut down, and fell down one by one with a crashing noise. The leaves made scratching noises as they brushed past one another.

A ray of white light was reflected outwards, and formed a silver light wheel when it gathered in the midst of the forest. The light wheel shrunk suddenly, and began to disappear.

Tch!!

Down below, a sharp black thorn dashed towards the sky and crashed towards the silver light wheel violently. Instantly, the same thing happened the second time, and the third, and the fourth…

Lots of sharp black thorns burst out suddenly, and pierced the silver light wheel in midair precisely.

Finally, the light wheel began to vibrate.

"Windling! You better wish you were dead!!!" The voice of an angry old woman echoed in the air.

During the silence, the light wheel finally disappeared, and turned into multiple dots of silver light that fell down slowly. They resembled drops of rain.

The sharp thorns that appeared suddenly also softened into twists instantly, and turned into clouds of black fog, before flying downwards towards the forest again.

Moments later, the sound of calm footsteps could be heard as Garen walked out of the thicket with the Cloud Crow front pocket watch held gently in his hand.

"You know each other?" He looked at Windling who was waiting at the side.

The latter nodded his head.

"Should we continue?"

"We haven’t captured the two people that escaped earlier," Garen said faintly. "Do you have any suggestions?"

"No clue. They are of the same level as I, but only joined after they received my invitation," said Windling as he removed his watch, signalling that he was powerless. "You wasted too much time in the library, and they must have ran far away long ago."

"The next one then," Garen nodded as he continued walking out of the forest.

"We can only look for the bases that are nearby now. The rest would definitely have received the news and evacuated by now, so we can only rush over before they leave to stop them," reminded Windling.

"Lead the way."

****************

During the next three days, Garen allowed Windling to lead the way, as they raided seven bases quickly.

They were all the Obscuro Society’s secret bases, and out of the twenty over Obscuro Society members that were killed, four of them were elite General-level members.

They crossed over into the Ender Kingdom’s territory, and hurriedly passed through the wilderness and forest areas.

But after that, the nearby bases began to retreat, in order to evade their hunting territory. It was obvious that the Obscuro Society had finally retaliated, and had determined their approximate location.

After countless unfruitful raids, Garen allowed Windling to lead the way, as they crossed into a forest and entered the town area in the hinterlands of Ender. They began to notice the bases in these human town areas.

***************

Nearby a town in Ender, inside a small birch forest.

The white tree barks stood upright, while the floor was covered in grassy lawns dotted with little white flowers and a few white butterflies that flew around them.

"Anselm, has the target arrived?"

Three people in black robes stood inside the forest, as they quietly observed the little village road that snaked through the forest.

"Not yet," said a woman’s voice that came from the black-robed person that was standing right in front. She removed her hood and exposed an average-looking, slightly plump face. "Why must we absolutely execute Avic? Isn’t there another method?"

"What other methods are you thinking of?" The man who had just spoken began to tease her slightly. "Avic obstructed the movements of our branch, so his fate has already been decided. And we should count ourselves lucky, as we stand on the side of the adjudicators that will decide his fate."

"Don’t harbour innocents thoughts like these anymore, Anselm," said the last man indifferently. His voice was hoarse, making it impossible to guess his age.

Anselm had frankly never thought of joining this Obscuro Society branch, but she had no choice, as her husband chose to join, and in order to ensure that her household was harmonious, she chose to join as well.

But not long later, her husband died in a monster raid. Hence, she was left all alone by herself.

The higher-ups allocated her into this little group.

She did not like the two other people in her group. One of them was a cruel deviant, while the other was a selfish person with a revengeful heart. However, she was left with no other path, and once she entered the Obscuro Society, she did many bad things, and could only hesitantly continue on and move forward.

Now, just because of a minor issue, she was about to assassinate an old friend that had been by her side for a long time.

Anselm felt that she had started to hate this type of life even more.

"I’ve heard that a bastard that specializes in attacking bases appeared at the border territories. The higher-ups have increased their surveillances, and created special groups codenamed "Hunt Cloud Crow". One of the General-levels from our branch has also been selected to go over. Did you guys know about this?"

The black-robed man with the hoarse voice started to speak softly and slowly.

"Most of our bases in the border areas have evacuated, I was wondering why the manpower in the branch became sufficient suddenly, when I realised it was due to the disappearance of so many bases." Surprised, another man said: "With the current situation, are there still people alive who are able to oppose the Headquarters?"

"That’s right, that man person is amazing! I heard that this was caused by him getting raided by the higher ups, which made him furious. Back then, he captured one of the elite members from the Headquarters and began to attack bases everywhere in revenge." The man with the hoarse voice croaked in agreement. "The Headquarters established the hunting group, but were too afraid to make a move, and right now they’re just withdrawing again and again."

"Wasn’t that like the Blood Tower and the Royal Family? Something like the Green Dragon Swordsman? When they raided Blood Tower, I heard that it ended in failure as well," praised another man.

"According to the information I received from my cousin, southward of Mason Town, after the Maple Leaf bridge is where the Cloud Crow’s hunting territory lies. If you have nothing to do, don’t go there. If not, the outcome will be hard to anticipate."

The two men chatted noisily for half a day, before the soft noise of horse hooves could be heard coming from the little road suddenly."

The three people became silent suddenly, and hid themselves in the forest.

Before the horses appeared on the little road, a low rumble echoed from behind them suddenly.

Bang!!!

The earth felt as if it was being hammered down by a metal hammer, as it continued to quake violently, as if it was about to jump upwards.

Chapter 382: Purge 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Roar!!!!

A sharp, ear-piercing siren exploded through the sky, as a white pillar of light materialised behind.

"It’s the warning signal from the branch!!" The three Obscuro Society members were alerted at the same time.

"The branch has been raided!" Anselm reacted immediately. "What do we do now?"

"Don’t panic…" The man with the hoarse voice was thinking of what to say.

Suddenly, ear-piercing cawing noises echoed from behind them, as a large flock of crows gathered there in an exceptionally noisy manner.

The man suddenly remembered the warning he received from his cousin. He also remembered the characteristics of the Cloud Crows that the Headquarters had reported.

"F*ck! This area is close to the Ender Headquarters base!! Are the people in the Headquarters just eating shit? How did the Cloud Crows get here suddenly??!!" He scolded them in a foul mood.

"Fall back!" He growled softly. He was the first person to turn around and run away.

The other two people followed closely behind.

While they ran, a strange glow began to glimmer in Anselm’s eyes dimly, but no one noticed it.

The three people’s informational records were all kept at the branch, and if they did not return them after the warning signal, they would be persecuted by the Headquarters. Thus, although they were helpless, the three of them decided to go back and take a look.

On the way, the trio removed their black robes quickly and exposed the normal clothes they wore within, storing all of their specialized Obscuro Society accesories at the same time. They plastered fake surprised expressions on their faces as they rushed towards the source of the noise.

****************

In the middle of a thick birch forest, there was a large platform that resembled a gigantic black biscuit, where around thirty figures in black robes stood sparsely.

On top of the black platform, a light gold air current was suspended in mid air, spiralling downwards like a ribbon as it circled around the black circular area. The air current turned circles in the air, as if it was dancing.

Golden rays of sunshine beamed downwards, and the ribbon became an even more beautiful and eye catching sight.

However, no one was appreciating this sight before them right now, as the gazes of all of the black robed people were directed past the ribbon in the sky.

There was a little cloud of black fog floating there, and on top of the cloud stood a tall man who was clad in full-bodied black armor. The man’s long blonde hair was blown around his handsome face, and he had three red birthmarks on his forehead.

"Cloud Crow Garen! Do you really wish to start a war with the Obscuro Society?" From the crowd shielded beneath the golden air current, an old man stood up slowly. He was not wearing a hood, and his face was covered in wrinkles like the bark of an old tree. He held a white wooden walking stick that was taller than him in his hand.

"Before you made the decision to ambush me, you should’ve thought of the consequences of your actions." Garen stared at the light gold air current in the air with interest, as this ribbon-like translucent air current had a slight threatening presence.

He had only recently discovered the precise controls for the Cloud Crows, and now he had complete control over using them to allow himself to float in mid air. When he used them with the Black Light Array tools that the Royal Family had given him, he could move around freely in the air.

Once he had discovered this method, he’d used it immediately. However, this method required strong and precise control abilities. They were powerful to the extent that Windling gaped at him as if he’d just seen a deviant monster.

But Garen fully understood the convenience of this method. Thus, he became more interested in allowing his power to flow within so that he could experiment with the methods of using the Cloud Crow front.

Regarding this, Windling was completely speechless. He watched Garen control every one of thousands of Cloud Crows in an extremely orderly manner, and noticed that they bent to his will completely. This was not an ability that an ordinary human could acquire.

Light was a consumable energy, and in the blink of an eye, it was enough to make a regular Totem user exhausted to the point of collapsion.

Once he had come to his senses, Garen carefully observed the Obscuro Society members that had appeared below him. During this mission where they travelled deep into the the hinterlands of Ender, through Windling’s directions, they had finally found a large-scale base.

It was within their expectations as there were almost thirty Obscuro Society members, but none of them had planned to release their Totems to fight yet. This way, their strength was not gathered in one area, and it was easier for them to separate themselves to attack.

They used the Totem Light from their bodies and the Totem Light from their Totems to saturate both areas.

The formation was still suspended in mid air, as the golden air current continued to circle around the black circular base. It was unusually beautiful, as it loomed in the air.

The other important thing stood on the ground of the black circle; a large white stone statue.

Only the top half of the stone statue could be seen above ground, as the bottom half of its body had been buried by the black soil.

The sculpture appeared to be of a monster with a dog’s head and a human body. There was even a crooked horn growing out of the top of the dog’s head, while a goat-like beard grew below its chin. Its body was strong and muscular, and a toga was wrapped around its chest, covering the left side. One corner of the toga was fastened to his left shoulder with a round, gold button. It gave onlookers a rough, ancient and mysterious feeling.

"Not done yet?" Garen looked at the stone statue that was vibrating quickly now.

"Arrogant!" exclaimed the old man coldly. "You will pay a price for your arrogant ignorance!"

He struck his walking stick against the ground angrily at once.

"Rise!"

The dog-headed statue on the ground opened its eyes immediately.

Its eyes were jet-black with no white sclera, and were merely two empty jet-black holes.

A crashing noise could be heard, as the black soil on the ground flipped over suddenly.

The large dog-headed statue began to remove itself from the ground slowly. It braced both of its palms against the ground, as it lifted out of the ground slowly.

The crowd of black robed people moved out of the way quickly to give it space.

The dog-headed human statue finally stood on the ground in one piece.

It was apparently over a hundred meters tall!!

Its large body was perfectly muscular, and its body was covered in a white stone toga. Both of its black eyes glared towards Garen who was still suspended in mid air.

A moment passed.

The dog-headed man stretched his big mouth open immediately, and rushed towards Garen, while howling silently.

One of its large hands came swinging towards Garen, as if it was an adult swatting a fly or a mosquito. Its broad palm cast a dark shadow over Garen’s entire body.

It stretched over the defensive range of the gold air currents, and seized Garen directly.

Garen narrowed both of his eyes, as the black pocket watch in his hand began to release large clouds of black fog.

The large amounts of black fog continuously transformed into Cloud Crows, as the flock of black crows rushed in all four directions and spread out everywhere.

From far away, the large torrent of black crows flew out from Garen’s position continuously looked like a black stream flowing from him.

An entire kilometer-long range within the sky was now covered in flocks of black crows. They attacked every living thing within their range, causing the once golden sky to darken as it was covered up completely. They looked like black clouds that floated along continuously.

A gust of black fog transformed into a large black crow that was over ten meters long, which then rushed over in the direction of the dog-headed man’s hand.

The large black crow had an incomparably sharp beak, and when it outstretched its wings, it was shaped like a shuttle. It pierced through the air violently, as it jetted towards the giant stone statue of the dog-headed man.

Tch!!

A sharp, ear-piercing screech rang through the air.

The large black crow and the large hand of the dog-headed man statue began clashing with each other violently.

Boom!!!

Both of them were of similar sizes, and between the large white hand and the black coloured Cloud Crows, an explosion of black fog and white gravel erupted. It formed a midair sphere and unleashed white circular shockwaves.

The dog-headed man’s statue began to move slightly before it continued to claw at Garen.

"Is this the strongest formation this branch has to offer? It’s very impressive!" Garen chortled. Black light lit up below his feet suddenly.

A cracking sound was heard before his figure moved backwards quickly and turned into a black line as he left the range of the dog-headed statue’s hand instantly, and floated back up into the sky again.

Bang!

The gigantic hand smashed down on the forest, crushing a cluster of birch trees and leaving a deep hand print on the ground as well.

The dog-headed man’s statue used its other hand to swing across the area silently in a fan-like motion towards Garen.

This time, its large hand brought a dim layer of black light with it.

The old man holding a walking stick in the middle of the area sneered.

"If the ancestral god statue was such an easy opponent, why would we waste so much energy on it?"

"Master, if this drags on for too long, I’m afraid that the people in the Royal Alliance of Luminarists will…" Beside him, a girl in a black robe reminded him softly.

"It doesn’t matter, once we get rid of the Cloud Crows, we’ll have a way to fix that. The governing lord of this area is one of us, and in order to resist terrorists, awakening the ancestral god statue was the logical thing to do. When the time comes, we’ll just have to change our clothes and everything will be settled right?" The old man replied distractedly.

"But if we do that, our plan will…"

"What plans are you thinking about now?! He’s arrived to kill us!" The old man glared at her with both eyes. He was not interested in paying any attention to this woman.

Midair, the large white hand with its black aura began swiping towards Garen furiously, forming gusts of strong wind. This strong wind surrounded Garen on all four sides, trapping and immobilising him in one spot.

"Hnngh!" Garen’s face became cold. Unable to shield himself with anything else, he used his hand with the pocket watch to push forward.

Hiss…

At the same time, clouds of black fog surrounded the area where Garen stood and formed a large black torrent, as the strange cawing noises of the Cloud Crows filled the air, as if the non stop humming noises had been enveloped, causing the whole sky to become noisy and chaotic.

The black torrent transformed into a black spike suddenly, as it charged towards the large hand violently.

Hum!!!

An incomparably violent fight broke out suddenly.

The sound waves spread everywhere quickly, but the noises could not be heard by anyone. They could only feel pain in both of their ears, as their vision started to blur because of the violent soundquakes.

Large clouds of black smoke spread out in all four corners of the sky, and continued to flow out endlessly from the large hand of the giant stone statue.

The Cloud Crows and the giant statue were caught in a fierce standstill.

Garen continued to float in midair and stood behind the black coloured Cloud Crows as he watched the black smoke diffuse out from his body and spread everywhere. His face was devoid of even the slightest movement.

The dog-headed man’s statue was truly powerful. It possessed immense strength but it was obvious that its sources were insufficient, as he could feel that this stone statue was not really using all of its true strength right now.

But he was different. Although he had already used the Cloud Crow front to its limit, his Secret Technique training allowed him to have a strong body, and once he had given himself a dragon’s heart, his vigour now surpassed that of an average person greatly, allowing him to reach a terrifying stage.

Moreover, his Master-level Precision Blueprint made it extremely easy for him to control the Cloud Crow front. He was able to release all of its strength completely.

Most of the black fog dispersed in mid air, and transformed into chirping black crows again as they flew towards the statue’s large hand, as its energy sources circulated continuously while it confronted the large stone statue.

Garen did not go back to observe the standstill between the giant statue and the Cloud Crow front. Instead, he bowed his head and stared at the crowd of Obscuro Society members that were protected by the golden air currents.

According to Garen who had now possessed a dragon’s heart, the consumption of the Cloud Crow front only used one third of his Totem Light. Next, he was going to get rid of the golden air currents that were blocking his path.

"He still has strength left??!!"

The people inside the black circle began to make soft, frightened noises.

Garen smiled slightly, as the three red dots on his forehead began to be illuminated with red light.

He raised his hand slowly, as eight shapeless swirls that were a meter long began to float up beside him slowly.

"Go!!!"

Both his eyes lit up suddenly.

Roar!!!!

As the roars of the dragon reverberated through the air, eight snake-like red dragon heads snapped downwards from the sky suddenly. They came down from different angles and directions and bit at the crowds of Obscuro Society members. They glided down in a straight line like a waterfall.

While Garen watched from afar at the center, the eight red long dragon necks hurtled downwards from the sky, and attacked the black circle below it violently.

Chapter 383: Intelligence 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Eight long, ferocious dragon heads appeared from the sky like red strands, lunging fiercely towards the Obscuro Society’s men below.

Ssss…...

After a subtle hiss, the golden air flows condensed into eight gold dots in mid-air, blocking the dragon heads head-on.

The red and gold collided.

Howwwlllll!!

The eight dragon heads let out loud howls in the air. The surrounding forest appeared as though it was swept by a hurricane. The sound waves blew the leaves off trees and created a huge ripple that spread through the surroundings.

Awww!!!

As the main head of the eight headed dragon roared to the sky, two of its strong limbs apparated ominously from thin air and took form.

With two bangs, its two giant limbs landed on the ground.

The eight headed dragon seemed to crawl out from thin air. The back part of its body was slowly forming. It’s over twenty-metre long frightening body chilled the souls of every bystander.

This terrifying creature seemed to have crawled out from a legend, but this time there was no hero to defeat it.

Garen’s three red dot-birthmark on his brow glowed dark red, as if blood was about to burst out.

He quietly floated in mid-air as the giant eight headed dragon was ferociously attacking the golden air flows.

Crash!!!

Suddenly there was a loud, clear noise.

A crack was appearing on one of the golden dots, which was made up of condensed air flow. Subsequently, the crack quickly grew and enlarged and overwhelmed the whole gold dot.

There as a crash.

One of the gold dots shattered.

Then the second one and the third one.

The long, ferocious heads lunged forward and headed directly to the Obscuro Society’s men below.

The group in the black circle instantly panicked and ran. Several red lights flashed, which seemed like a unique escape tactic.

This tactic only increased their speed for a brief period of time. Before they could react in time, the nimbler eight headed dragon had caught up, and lunged at them.

Pitiful cries and screams filled the area. The black-robed men instantly scattered and fled in all directions.

A few of the black-robed men were protecting the old man as they fled towards the northwest direction. They were far quicker than the rest of the group. They seemed to be forming a black-red round tactic formation, which drastically increased their speed.

The old man in the circular formation glanced at Garen. He looked abnormally calm, without any sense of panic. From his eyes, it seemed that he was in deep thought, thinking about something.

Garen looked into the old man’s eyes from a distance and was surprised by his lack of fear. From afar, he saw the old man open his lips, as if he was mouthing words.

"We...will meet again.."

Garen let out an intrigued smile.

"Interesting."

As there were many Obscuro Society members and the giant Dog Humanoid Statue present, it wouldn’t be wise for him to give chase.

The eight headed dragon went on a rampage against the Obscuro Society members on the ground. It seemed as though every bite created another casualty. Some of them released their totems to defend, but they were snapped into two without putting up a fight.

It was complete annihilation.

As some of them tried to escape, the eight headed dragon once again roared towards the sky.

Roarr!!!!

The fury of the sound waves spread out in the widest range. It was like a wave of white waves, spreading out a huge white ring.

　　**********

In the distant forest, Anselm and the group of three hurried towards the division.

As they continued to run, there was a dim black light beneath their feet. They were moving with astonishing feet.

"We have to move faster! Once the golden defence circle is activated, there would be no way for us to return!" A man with a hoarse voice urgently called.

"We can also stay out here. The crows will certainly be pushed back. We might not be in time even if we return now." Another man muttered.

"Not necessarily. This could be our chance to earn merit!"

As Anselm stared at the two people in front, the idea in his heart grew stronger.

The three of them quiet down and continued hurrying.

Howwwll!!!

Suddenly, a ferocious howl came from the front.

Booom!

The tree leaves were crushed, and from the sound waves came a powerful hurricane, blowing some of the trees askew.

A white sound wave collided with the three men.

Ommm…...

Anselm couldn’t hear anything in that instant. His brain and ears were filled with humming noises due to the sound waves crossing the limit. His brain was in a mess, and his eyes were disoriented. Everything turned blurry and tears were dripped down the corners of the eyes.

The three of them were like tiny worms in a storm. They were heavily suppressed by the huge sound waves, as if a huge rock was on each of their bodies.

The three men were completely deafened. Their vision blurred and all they could do was cling to the trees tightly.

The strong wind and sound waves came from the front, messing up their clothes. It was as if they would be carried away by the huge sound waves with a lapse in concentration.

Large rocks and weaker tree trunks were lifted by the huge sound waves and blew backwards. Huge amounts of grass, barks and mutated bugs, and even a small group of white deers were swept up by the wind. They were blown backwards and on and off, they would knock against big trees, letting out eerie sounds of the breaking of bones.

The three of them bowed their bodies and proceeded with much difficulty, withstanding the sound waves and wind.

"What.. What is this!!??"

The hoarse-voiced man shouted with all his might.

As the trees in front fell to the ground, the situation in the distant could roughly be seen.

Anselm forced his head upwards to look forward.

Finally, the sound waves came to a halt, and everything calmed down.

The whole woods were in a mess.

The three of them gathered together with their remaining strength.

"What in the world was that just now!? Was that the howl of a monster?"

"I don’t know.. Could it be the division’s special weapon?"

As Anselm was about to speak, his expression changed.

"Its coming again! Duck!!"

He couldn’t even finish his sentence.

Howwwll!!!

Another huge white sound wave headed towards them. The three of them crouched on the ground to prevent being injured by the huge sound wave.

A strong wind came with the frightening sound wave. It ignored totem light and collided with their bodies.

This time it was much shorter. Within a few seconds, everything resumed calmness.

The three men did not dare to proceed further. They stood still and entered into a state of hesitation instantly.

"We are not far from the division. We have to find a high place to see what is going on." Anselm suggested.

"True. We can’t go any further." The hoarse-voiced man agreed immediately.

The three of them retreated and quickly found a black hill and swiftly climbed up. They stood on top of the hill and looked in the direction of the division.

"My God! What is that!!??"

As Anselm move forward to look into the distance, his expression changed.

Both of them also stood up and looked at the sky above the division. They couldn’t utter a single word, and could only gape at the sight before them.

"Division….What happened?" After a while, the hoarse-voiced man whispered bitterly.

The three of them glanced into the distant sky. They sky above the division was utterly dyed black. The big black cloud hovering over was made up of countless groups of crows.

Below the black clouds, a red, gigantic eight headed salamander was twisting its eight heads. Its long snake-like necks dived down from time to time. Every time it raised its head again, there will be a couple of black-robed men in its mouth. Blood continuously flowed down the sides of his giant mouth.

The eight headed dragon was surrounded by countless murders of crows, looking more ferocious than a mutated creature.

At this point of time, the division was completely still. Only the eight headed dragon was letting out roars of victory.

Then the three of them noticed a black-gowned figure hovering on top of the eight headed dragon.

Even with the distant of a few kilometres, a red glare could be clearly seen on the figure’s forehead.

"Could that be Cloud Crow?" Anselm uttered.

　　******************

From time to time, the eight headed salamander let out roars of joy, signaling that Garen was in a good mood.

Although the complete situation on the ground could not be seen, most of the Obscuro Society’s members had been eaten by the eight headed dragon.

Possibly because of the eight headed dragon’s overeating, Garen faintly felt that the eight headed dragon was releasing a form of poisonous mist. It seemed like the eight headed dragon’s waste after digesting, yet it was extremely corrosive.

As long as the eight headed dragon was summoned, the gas would naturally be released, severely corroding everything in the area.

It was even around his own body. The gas had a faint fragrance, inducing living beings to relax. They would then unknowingly fall into the danger of being corroded, unable to get themselves out.

Garen suspected that this could be the final and ninth head’s ability that comes with its imminent evolution.

Shortly, the chaos below quietened.

The Dog Humanoid Statue was surrounded by the crow formation. As the Obscuro Society was being defeated, it also lost its power. It had laid on the ground since, unable to move.

Garen looked towards two directions in the distant.

There was a group of people from another force which had been hiding there for some time. From their aura, it should be people from the Royal Alliance of Luminarist. Or maybe it was some commoners, or normal totem users from noble families.

They hid in the forest where they thought it was safe, then looked at the commotion.

As Garen gazed over, all of them held their breaths, afraid that he would notice them. The whole forest went totally silent, not even the sound of a bug could be heard.

Garen let out a faint smile. He did not want to relate with Ender’s Royal Alliance of Luminarist. They were from a different system.

The opposition seemed to have no intention on coming over to greet him as well.

Suddenly, Garen raised his head towards the right sky. There was a group of black eagles in the distant, seemed to be swiftly heading over here.

On the back of the giant eagles were black-robed figures, obviously someone from the secret service.

Their auras on their bodies were murky. They seemed weak, but were actually strong.

Garen mildly closed his eyes.

"Let’s go, Windling."

As a ray of black light flashed beneath his feet, he dived down like a rocket into the forest.

In that instant, the gigantic eight headed dragon became a ray of red light, disappearing in the forest. The countless hovering black crows retreated and disappeared into the forest below.

Both Garen and the helpless Windling were surrounded by a ball of black mist. They sped through the forest into the distance.

Chapter 384: Intelligence 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Aren’t those people from the secret service? Why don’t you go meet them?" Windling whispered to Garen, who was beside him. As he seemed to be a good mood, hopefully his temper would not flare up.

"I do not want to meet my colleagues yet. The Three Departments should have noticed something when I took action. Or they might have known for long that this is an Obscuro’s division, but they chose not to act." Garen smiled as he explained.

"You do know a fair bit." Windling smiled bitterly. "The Three Departments are indeed strong, but their ground forces are only a few people. The strongest of them are only a handful, and some of them had joined our Obscuro Society. No, I can no longer say our Obscuro Society. After doing so much, I can no longer be considered as an Obscuro Society’s member. I think my bounty is almost ten million dollars in the society."

"Do you know the origin of this generation’s president of Obscuro?" Garen suddenly asked.

"You noticed." Windling didn’t seem surprised. he sat on the black mist behind, which was soft like a sofa. Crossing his legs, he was surrounded by the black mist and they were moving forward at astonishing speed.

"President Hellgate, one of Daniela’s major nobles. Instead of looking at Obscuro as an independent society, think of it as a portion that left the group of nobles. The elite members of Obscuro are all outstanding elite noblemen. Being unsatisfied with the Royal Alliance’s stagnant ruling system, some of the elite noblemen left, forming Obscuro. Some of them formed The Three Departments because of differing philosophies, under the support of the council of elders. In other words, nobles are the cause of everything."

"Only the nobles have such rich deposits of knowledge." Garen nodded and agreed. "A normal person wouldn’t be able and qualified to access such elite knowledge."

"What should we do next?" Windling look at Garen on his left.

"How many strongholds have we destroyed?"

"Including this, nine. Whether it is Obscuro or other forces, most probably information on you would definitely be on the desk of their intelligence department. Can this be considered as the fastest way to fame?" Windling was getting increasingly confused by Garen’s motives.

"That giant statue is a pity. If we can bring it along it would be useful." Garen abruptly changed the topic as he stroked his chin.

　　*********************

In the following four days, Garen and Windling continuously attacked Obscuro’s strongholds all over the Ender Kingdom. However, many of them were empty. It was obvious that Obscuro had urgently withdrew their men.

Other than the few major strongholds in Ender, there were not many people in the other divisions.

Eight Headed Cloud Crow replaced Garen’s old Cloud Crow nickname. The rumor was widely spread by bystanders and people who have seen his battles.

Eight Headed represented the eight headed dragon, while Cloud Crow represented the flock of black cloud crows. These were the two strongest characteristics of Garen’s abilities.

His track record was dug out and sent to the intelligence departments of major forces.

It was because of his incredible speed. He attacked two countries within a couple of days. Furthermore, he destroyed an Obscuro division within ten minutes in Ender Kingdom, before their headquarters could even send back-up.

Due to his strength and track record, Garen gained fame overnight.

At this time, Garen received a call from the nearby Secret Service.

　　**********************

Garen and Windling sat in the lush forest, on a thick layer of fallen leaves. They set up a piece of white cloth between them and placed some food on it.

Jam and bread, lamb jerky and two bottles of apple cider. That was their lunch of the day.

As the faint golden sunlight shone through the leaves above onto the two people, there appeared to be patterns on their bodies.

A brown and furry squirrel with three big tails was crouching beside the white picnic cloth. It wagged its three tails like a wheel with all its might, sweeping leaves all over the place.

The squirrel was gulping down a small pile of jam that Garen threw away, looking very satisfied. As it tucked its butt, it's tail wagging became more rounded.

"So relaxing.." Windling, with a palm on the floor, rubbed his stomach lightly and swallowed the last piece of bread. "Oh no..I might have eaten too much.."

He spied at Garen who was opposite him.

The handsome man was nibbling on a piece of jerky. His eating speed remained consistent and there was no expression on his face. His actions were elegant. As he tore off each piece and put it into his mouth, not a single crumb fell. The picnic cloth in front of him was clean, as if it had been completely wiped clean. There was no food remaining.

They’d split the food portion into half. While Windling had a huge portion left, only a smile bite remained on Garen’s side...

"Your appetite...is really...spectacular.." Windling thought for a moment, before using a more proper description.

"It's your appetite that is small." Garen replied softly.

Windling was speechless.

Pupu...pupu….

Suddenly, a soft patting sound came from the small black box on Garen's collar.

Garen slowed down, put down the food he held and wiped his hand with a napkin.

There was a voice coming from the black box.

"Cloud Crow? You are the eight headed cloud crow Garen?" It was a guy’s voice. It was clear yet slightly reserved. "This is the Secret Service, Kovitan’s Headquarter. My name is McCain, the current director, and also the leader of the strongest White Silver Group . I am currently communicating with you through a long distance signal. We only have three secure minutes, where we won't be snooped on by other forces."

"Ah it's the director." A smile quirked the edge of Garen's mouth. "May I know the reason you're contacting me?"

"You should be currently in the Ender division right? I have a mission here. I was wondering whether you would be willing to accept it?" Director McCain spoke in an extremely polite tone.

"Just say it."

"Alright. In the Ender Kingdom, the Geometry Service’s elite, Dark Bell and the masters from the Obscuro Society are fighting for a unique precious heirloom. The majority of elites from both their forces have been mobilized over. I hope you can represent the Secret Service and participate on the battle for a chance to obtain the precious heirloom, since you are currently nearby. The mission will be within five days."

"No problem. What's the reward?" Garen asked without hesitation. After experiencing the power of the precious heirloom, it was dear to his heart. He also understood why various forces placed high value on it.

In simple terms, a precious heirloom was the combination of countless complicated tactics. It could inject totem light and totem strength at any time to activate a large or multipurposed strength. An imitation precious heirloom like the cloud crow formation only needed sufficient totem strength or totem light. Without the need for tactics, a mediocre totem user could elevate into an elite spiritualized master in the blink of an eye.

"Naturally, the reward won't be bad. There will be a satisfactory tactic formation. Furthermore, considering your father and the loyalty of the Trejon Household towards the Royal Alliance, I have resubmitted a request to the higher ups for a fief. As long as you complete this mission, Trejon Household will regain a satisfactory fief in the new housing area." There was a tone of rich laughter in McCain’s voice. A fief and a strong and complete tactic formation would be surely sufficient in this chaos.

Garen got slightly excited. With a fief like that, he could move the whole Trejon Household there to protect them. His underlings, family, friends and relatives. There was also teacher Emin, whose current status was unknown.

Garen searched his memory for the location. He planned to visit his teacher first.

As he regained focus, he quickly expressed sincere thanks.

"Then director, let me express my gratitude first. With such generous rewards, it seems like this precious heirloom isn’t simple."

"Naturally. The Geometry Service initially wanted to keep it for themselves, but they did not succeed. Now, we and the rest of the organizations stand a chance." McCain smiled as he answered. "The Geometry Service are a bunch of cocky guys. Now that they’ve gotten entangled with the Obscuro Society, they must have been humiliated. Let’s see how they solve this, haha."

He paused for a moment. "Besides, aren’t you sweeping the Obscuro’s strongholds? Let me send you a more detailed map, which is a treasure we have just obtained."

"Send? How are you going to send?" Garen was surprised.

"I’ll say and you memorise."

"Alright." Garen was initially worried about Windling’s limited knowledge on the location of strongholds. As he was too thorough during his killings, the sweep was coming to an end. Now it was as if someone brought him a pillow just as he was about to sleep.

This time he was addicted to the killings. Although most of them were first form and second form low level totem users, the numbers were huge. It was similar to when the Petrifying White Dragon was around.

One first form totem or creature could provide around 25% of potential points. One second form could provide two points, while one third form could provide five points. For spiritualized form, the value jumped to fifteen points.

After memorising the information that McCain gave on the strongholds, Garen glanced at his potential points.

After killing over hundreds of Obscuro Society members, his potential points had surpasses two hundred without him realizing.

After careful thought, Garen decided to increase his agility to its limit.

His fixated his gaze on the agility pane.

The potential points quickly depleted.

Agility swiftly increased from 6.00. After increasing it by 5 points, every increase required 20 potential points. Very quickly, 40 potential points disappeared and his agility was raised to 8.00.

From 8.00 onwards, 60 potential points were needed to increase one attribute. Very quickly, from 160 points, only about 40 points remained.

As his agility finally reached 10.00, it completely stopped moving.

Garen clenched his fist in satisfaction. It was as though his body was surrounded by invisible wind. He only had to move lightly. It felt like his body weight had disappeared, and he could float around without sluggishness.

He sensed the state of the eight headed dragon. Sure enough, the ninth head on the back of the eight headed dragon was rapidly expanding. The huge lump of flesh grew bigger and redder.

Chapter 385: Feud 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As Garen sat cross-legged on the ground, mild black gas dissipated from his whole body. It was like fog spreading throughout his surroundings.

He quietly sensed the ninth head of the eight headed dragon. The blood tumor was growing bigger and redder, as if it was about the explode any minute.

Unconsciously, Windling noticed his unusual behaviour. Without saying a word, he kept his distance.

As this situation had happened multiple times over the journey, he was used to it. It was not just once or twice, but multiple times. It was as if he was examining the state of his body, similar to the masters among commoners.

But it seemed to be different this time.

Windling carefully observed the black smoke surrounding Garen. It smelt good. It was incredibly rich, like fragrance released by burning various spices together. The smell could not be identified, but it was not pungent; a little like incense.

Suddenly he was stunned as he felt the skin of his body stiffening. As he pinched his skin on the back of his hand, there was totally no feeling.

Windling panicked and retreated more than 10 metres. Only then did his senses returned.

"What's this smell. It can unknowingly numb the senses!" Windling fearfully glanced at the nearby Garen.

At this point of time, Garen's body was surrounded by a faint-black fog. Even his face was a little blurry

"Again...Always doing dangerous things without telling me, don’t you know this could lead to death!" Windling complained softly. "My beloved Weiwei, when can Papa see you again...and my cute Bartow."

His mood was tinged with sorrow. With a long sigh, he ignored the dirt and sat on a green rock in the distance.

Seconds and minutes passed by. The midday sun gradually rose, throwing red tinged sunbeams across the forest.

The forest breeze carried a gentle warmth.

Windling sat on the green rock and yawned. The best thing about travelling with Garen was that being beside him, there wouldn't be any dangerous creature within a 1-2 metre radius. Whether it was mutated beings or monsters from experiments, there was completely no sign of them.

It was as though the monsters could detect Garen’s dangerous aura and fled. Therefore he was able to rest in complete peace every time.

As Windling was drowsily sleeping, he faintly heard a weak cry for help.

"Help...help…hu...hu…" Between the sounds of fleeing and panting, came an immature child's voice from the distance.

This forest wasn't far from human population. It was probably some kid who couldn’t survive and came out to look for a living, but fell into some danger.

Windling thought to himself. He was different from Garen. He was familiar with the life of a commoner in this chaos.

Both of his children were normal humans. They were not qualified to become Luminarists. If it wasn’t for him, both of his children would have died of hunger much earlier.

"Who cares." Windling didn’t want to bother. They had met multiple situations like this throughout the journey. There were adults, elderly, strong men and beautiful girls. But both Garen and himself were lazy to bother.

In this chaos, commoners had no fields to farm. Without any special abilities, all they could was risks their lives to gather rare herbs to be used as raw materials for various potions.

In the areas that have been preliminarily cleared, the danger was relatively lower. Many rich commoners would hire one or two totem users to gather herbs. It wasn’t often that they met dangers.

Only at the first line of defense were there daily intense battles between life and death.

It was extremely difficult for commoners in times like this.

As the voice drew closer, it seemed more and more like his own child’s voice. Windling was becoming more and more irritated. A thought of his own children flitted through his mind; what if it was them who met this situation...

He finally stood up and headed towards the direction of the voice.

Garen usually took some time to finish anyway.

　　***********************

Garen slowly opened his eyes. There was a flash of red light in his eyes. He had failed once again.

The ninth head couldn’t successfully emerge. His agility was already at the limit. The only attribute left was intelligence.

"I have to completely upgrade my body to the limit?" This thought flashed through Garen’s mind.

He regained awareness.

"Windling?" He was taken aback when he did not see Windling around.

As the wind blew through the forest, there was the sound of rustling leaves.

Other than that, there were no other noises.

A non-mutated scorpion slowly crawled past the side of his foot and fled into a hole in the ground.

On a branch far away, the three-tailed squirrel was carrying some jam that was filled with crushed leaves. Its bottom was sticking out as it attempted to stuff the jam into a nutshell.

Garen refocussed his gaze and looked around.

"Boss, there could be something over here." Windling shouted from afar.

Garen stood up and headed over, crossing through a small portion of forest. He saw Windling crouching down in front of a deep hole investigating something. He looked serious.

"What happened?"

Garen furrowed his brows as he walked over.

"There’s something strange about this hole."Windling whispered. Although he wasn’t a match for Garen, he was at least an Elemental General of the Obscuro Society with decent abilities. Even without his precious heirloom, normal spiritualized forms were no match for him. But now, with a nasty look on his face, the situation might be troublesome.

"What’s going on?" Garen hurried over and stared into the hole. Suddenly, there was a horrible stench coming from the hole. He held his breath and frowned.

He abruptly sensed weakness in the eight headed dragon totem, which seemed to be caused by the horrible stench.

"What in the world is this?!" Garen was about to retreat when a force suddenly shoved him from behind.

The force wasn’t malicious. It was just a simple push.

"You!!" Garen turned and saw a weird smile on Windling’s face.

Strangely, although Garen was strongly pushed, his body only slightly leaned forward. His feet did not move at all.

Both of them were stunned for a moment.

Garen was shocked by Windling’s weirdness.

Windling couldn’t understand how Garen only leaned slightly after he pushed Garen with all his might.

"How..How can this be!?? The swamp night lizard’s poisonous gas has no effect on you?!" Shock was all over Windling’s face, as if he couldn’t believe it. "This gas can weaken five spiritualized totems instantly..!"

"Poisonous gas?" Garen looked grim.

An invisible whirlpool suddenly appeared behind Windling.

Crack!!

The giant dragon missed.

Windling’s figure was like an illusion. It started to disappear slowly, lighter and lighter, fainter and fainter.

"Idiot! You thought I would stay still and wait for your attack? Are you an imbecile? Do you have muscles for a brain?"

A secretive smile appeared once again on Windling’s face.

"You’re not Windling, who are you?" Garen looked at his quickly disappearing opponent. His five senses were carefully surveying the surroundings, trying to find out the location of his opponent.

"The Obscuro Society’s second Elemental General. You can call me the Enchanter." His figure completely disappeared and only a faint voice remained.

"Enchanter?" Garen snorted. There was a flash of bloodlust in his eyes. He glanced at the black hole on the ground. The odor quickly dissipated, as if it had never been there.

His brows emitted a red light.

The eight headed dragon’s eight head slowly appeared behind him.

Roarrr!!!!

The ferocious roar became a circle of white sound waves and spreaded to the surroundings.

The big maple tree leaves were shaken.

There was no movement in the vicinity.

A black light formation lit up beneath Garen’s feet. He leapt into the air and released black fog midair, holding his parcel.

Gaga!!

A huge amount of black fog flooded out, forming over a few thousand crows. They were like ink, flying all over to search for something.

Garen looked grim. He had thoroughly searched in a ten-metre radius. As he couldn’t find anything, his expression turned cold.

At this moment, the surrounding environment had been slightly distorted. The surroundings seemed to have changed.

A flurry of dull crashing sounds came from the distance.

Then only Garen realized, he had always been in the Enchanter’s illusion. He didn’t even notice!

His opponent’s illusions had reached a incredibly frightening level. The simulated environment was exactly the same as the forest in reality.

He quickly suppressed the panic in his heart.

Between the crashing sounds in the distance, Garen faintly heard Windling cursing.

He crossed a portion of forest and walked over. He saw Windling stuck in a triangular, semi-permeable tactic formation. The tactic formation was glowing in faint yellow. It was built on the base of the three white rocks below..

There were slight cracks on the three stones.

Crash!!　　

The triangular tactic formation finally cracked.

Windling was furious as he walked out.

"That Enchanter bitch!!" He was more enraged than usual. "He dares to toy with my feelings!"

He saw Garen’s displeased expression, quickly shuddered and stop speaking.

"This Enchanter is a hassle." Garen felt the lingering poison gas in his body. He was extremely unhappy.

Even the eight headed dragon, a supreme poisonous being, couldn’t completely resist the poison gas. If that was the case, it was conceivable that the Obscuro Society was starting to use their most precious items.

The purpose of the Enchanter’s appearance was most likely to poison him and weaken his abilities.

The next wave that would come should be ruthless hunts and attacks.

He carefully sensed his body’s condition.

Garen was slightly relieved.

Although the eight headed dragon wasn’t immune to the poison, its resistance dramatically weakened the effects of the poison.

Of the eight headed dragon’s heads, two fell into deep slumber; unable to move. It’s skin had been mildly corroded, weakening the defense of dragon skin. With this, the Dragon’s Roar power had also been weakened to three quarters of its original strength. It was currently only three times the level of the dual headed salamander. Only six of its heads were functioning.

"Boss. He got you?" Windling carefully analyzed Garen’s expression.

"There are some complications" Garen faintly replied. "The Enchanter said it was the poison gas of something called the swamp night lizard."

"Swamp night lizard!!?? My God!" Windling opened his eyes and scratched his head fervently with his two hands.

"It’s over it’s over… This toxin is rumored to last for ages! Without the antidote, you’ll be unable to remove it for the rest of your life! It will permanently weaken the core totem’s condition by half!!

Chapter 386: Feud 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen had never heard of such a poison.

"Anyway, let’s leave this place first! We’ll have our revenge on the Enchanter later."

"Right. They most definitely will be here soon." As Windling had already betrayed the Obscuro Society multiple times, he’d long been named upon the Obscuro’s bounty list. The reason they’d not met any danger so far was due to their elusiveness and speed. It was hard to grasp their position, hence they have managed to avoid any crisis or pursuit.

Their strategy was actually dependent on time - Quickly destroying the strongholds before the opponent’s backup arrived, then fleeing.

Now the Obscuro’s assassins had finally caught up to them.

The Enchanter’s illusions were far stronger than any illusion totems Garen had ever encountered. Whether it was the five senses or human’s basic instincts, all of it were within the opponent’s calculations. Even when he was poisoned at the end, the Enchanter did not show any form of malice, or Garen would’ve noticed immediately.

Without hesitating, the two of them quickly left the place. They were swept up by the black crows and headed towards Garen’s teacher Emin’s location.

Along the journey, Garen was constantly on guard against the Enchanter’s illusion environment.

Even he himself could not tell the difference. It was evident that the Obscuro Society was serious. The team they’d mobilized was abnormally powerful.

He was also trying to experiment with Red Jade Palm, a poison removal martial art.

He was in luck. The Red Jade Palm did have some effect, although it wasn’t very strong. It mildly soothed the corrosion on the dragon’s skin, but there was still no way to restore the two weakened dragon heads.

********************

In the maple forest where Garen and Windling were previously standing.

"I have already poisoned him." A voice came out of thin air. No figure could be seen, but there was a neutral voice. It sounded like neither a man nor a woman.

"Thank you Your Excellency. What was the effect?" A black-robed girl with a graceful figure walked out from deep within the forest and stood in front of where Garen previously stood. Her voice was enchanting and clingy. There was some form of respect in her question.

"Nothing much. Eight Headed Cloud Crow has a strong resistance towards poison. He has consecutively destroyed so many of our strongholds, humiliating the entire elite department." The neutral voice spoke again. "The rest depends on you guys. I still have another mission. This is your father’s final favor. Don’t bother me again."

"Many thanks. From now onwards, you and my father no longer owe each other." The black-robed girl spoke in a calm voice.

"Good." The neutral voice could no longer be heard.

The black-robed girl waited for a moment until the voice was completely gone. She instantly relaxed her tensed body. It was only then that she noticed the abundant beads of sweat coating her forehead.

Briskly, a black-robed figure strode out from behind her.

"Has the monster left?" The black-robed figure was a man with a sharp voice. From his tone, he sounded somewhat relieved.

"He left." The girl let out a long sigh. "Facing that guy requires 120% of energy every single time. If we’re not careful we’d fall into his tricks. Why is it me who has to face him every time!?"

"Since you’re the only one that can move him?" The guys shrugged helplessly.

"If it wasn't my father who specified me to get rid of him, I wouldn't even want to come!" The girl said with lingering fear. "That Eight Headed Crow Cloud destroyed father’s plan in Ender. If the opponent wasn't removed, it would be a difficult obstacle to overcome for our family."

"Where's your brother? He hasn't arrived?"

"Soon." The girl answered softly. "After getting the news that father was almost wounded, he dropped his mission immediately and rushed back. He also brought along some friends who might be of assistance."

"That's good. The team for the headquarters should be reaching soon. Let’s go and meet up with them."

"Alright."

*****************

Bang!!

The shapeless whirlpool in front of Garen violently collided with a ball of white lightning.

He walked through the blizzard of countless white lightning orbs and raised his head to look up at the white giant birds rapidly spitting them out.

These giant birds each had a wingspan of more than 10 metres wide. There was not a single feather on their full-white bodies. Their wings were fleshy, like dragon wings.

Thousands of them flocked together and filled the whole sky. They appeared like white feathers waltzing in the sky.

Numerous of lightning orbs accurately homed onto Garen and battered at his body. They were like guided homing missiles, twisting and turning.

Garen took out his black pocket watch and gently rubbed its surface with his fingers.

Copious amounts of black fog flooded out from the watch and formed into black crows. They let out strange cries and soared towards the strange white birds in the air.

The black and white birds were engaged in a tussle. From time to time, there would be white birds falling from the sky, and crows dissipating into black fog. They were unable to recondense together, as the electricity from the lightning orbs had a strong numbing effect.

After summoning the cloud crows, he promptly ignored the sky to directly survey his surroundings.

He was standing on an empty grassland. The green grass swayed to the wind. Green hills were everywhere and nothing seemed unusual. Golden sunlight glowed from above, gilding everything with a touch of gold.

Windling followed behind, looking bored.

"Where shall we head to now?"

"A small town near the borders of Kovitan." Garen raised his head. More and more white birds were killed. The rest of them panicked and cried out as they fled into the distance like broken white clouds.

He glanced at the gain in potential points. It was decent.

A creature group that could defy his aura and challenge him, such as this flock of white birds, wouldn’t be an average group. They could spit out homing white lightning orbs which would follow their enemy. Each ball was as big as a soccer ball with terrifying power. It could electrocute any second form totem in a split second.

This allowed the white bird flock to reign over the region between the forest and the plains.

Garen’s intrusion had enraged them which caused them to attack. However, they were badly defeated and ultimately fled.

"Let’s move on." Garen withdrew the black cloud. Two balls of black fog picked up the duo and carried them forth.

They were floating in the air a meter above the ground as they swiftly headed towards the red river along Kovitan’s borders.

Two days had passed since they left the forest. When they were not travelling, they killed creatures all day. Along Garen’s flight, he would relentlessly try to remove the poison during his break, but his efforts were futile.

A single Enchanter had eliminated his underestimation of the Obscuro Society. He was once again on his guard, surveying his surroundings at all times.

The swamp night lizard’s poison was already overwhelming. If there were a few more types of poison, could he still survive?

Along the journey, he consistently interrogated Windling on the level of the other Elemental Generals.

He managed to briefly grasp the Obscuro’s distribution of power among their top ranks.

In the East Continent, the Obscuro was led by two Marshals, God Cloud and Hack. Under them were three departments - the Elite Department, the Military and the Black Sky. The other departments like the Intelligence Department and the Logistics Department were under the Black Sky, which was where Windling was previously from.

This was also the reason he was familiar with the Obscuro Society’s situation.

Under the two marshals were their two strongest subordinates, known as the Elemental Generals. Hack’s subordinate was the Enchanter, while God Cloud’s subordinate was a man named Ice.

The two elemental generals were the two strongest members in the whole of Obscuro on the East Continent. The Enchanter was ranked at number two.

In comparison to the West Continent, the East Continent’s bureau was slightly weaker. Hence, they only had two marshalls leading it. The Enchanter’s strength would still be ranked among the top three if the two Continents combined. At times, even the marshals would have problems commanding him. Furthermore, the Obscuro was an organization completely driven by benefits. Every single member had huge family forces behind them. The strength of the members themselves and the power of their families were complementary.

As Garen was removing the poison, he was memorising the Enchanter’s name by heart.

Along the journey, Garen continuously increased his intelligence with his potential points. Slowly, he realized that the lump of the eight headed dragon’s final head was enlarging. As he checked his core totem, he also realized that the poisonous gas that he released was getting thicker.

The thing that delighted him the most was that the totem’s poison was slowly easing with the eight headed dragon’s evolution.

He believed that by increasing his intelligence to its limit, the eight headed dragon would evolve into the nine headed dragon. That would be the time of neutralising the swamp night lizard’s poison.

The both of them consistently changed routes and soon they arrived at the edge of a muddy river.

On the grassy plains, the red river was like a curved centipede, stretching towards the horizon.

At the river bank, there were groups of animals playing in the water.

Garen and Windling were surrounded by the black fog and headed forward along the river. As they passed overhead, the animals below panicked and fled.

From afar, both of them could faintly see the small town of Vinker.

The town was still standing among white and yellow flowers. But the houses within had collapsed. Some of them were in shambles, and the atmosphere appeared silent and empty.

A few mutated rabbits with spikes on their back were running around on the streets.

Garen and Windling landed on a bridge at the entrance to the town. They quietly looked at the deserted town.

"A new food chain has formed within such a short time?" Windling studied the grey rabbit with white spikes. He had a complicated expression on as he pondered.

"Let’s go in and have a look." Garen entered the town first.

Although he knew from history that teacher Emin was definitely alive and would appear in the final war, he wasn’t reassured and wanted to confirm it.

Very quickly, with Garen at the lead, both of them directly headed towards the familiar building by the end of the town.

It was a completely wooden red-brown building. Miraculously, it was in perfect condition, identical to the moment Garen left after his learnings.

Garen pushed open the gate outside the building. There was a loud creaking sound. Garen directly entered the yard.

The flowers in the yard were as dazzling as ever.

A relaxing smile reappeared on Garen’s face. He walked towards the entrance of the building, raised his hands and gave it a light knock.

Suddenly, he froze.

Chapter 387: Unexpected Discovery 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s gaze fell on a white substance on the edge of the door.

It was a white powdery substance which was emitting a faint white light.

He reached out his index finger and gently dabbed at the white powder, then put it to his nose for a sniff.

"Pollen?" Garen’s expression turned cold. "This power fluctuation…"

"What’s wrong?"

Windling’s questioning voice came from behind.

"The building is still intact. There is something strange going on." Windling came up from behind. "Why don’t you enter?"

Garen withdrew his hand.

"Forget it. I’ve already gotten what I wanted to know."

He turned, walked down the steps, and headed out.

"Hey! Why not enter and have a look since we’re already at the door? Why did you actually come here?!" Windling followed closely.

Garen ignored him and directly walked out of the yard.

He turned and gave the familiar building a final glance.

"Let’s go. We’ll go directly to the next stronghold."

"Still going?" Windling was startled. "We’ve already swept so many strongholds. You still want more?"

"Since even you didn’t consider it, they definitely wouldn’t be expecting it as well. If we attack them now, the success rate would definitely be quite high." Garen muttered.

Windling scratched his head. He had been terrified each time they went to an Obscuro stronghold. He had to find a place to hide and avoid being detected by the Obscuro Society’s men.

Every time Garen swept, he would carefully survey the surroundings and inform Garen if there was anything amiss. His safety was heavily dependent on Garen.

"Aren’t you worried about the poison in your body at all?" He ran up to Garen and asked out of curiosity.

"Not an issue. I’ve already found a way to remove it." Garen smiled. He seemed to have returned to his normal state.

As the two people left the building, the small town in front of their eyes looked different.

From the flawless building, out came several dark blue, human-shaped flowers.

The flowers had white human limb-shaped roots for their four limbs. They were like noodles swinging and twisting. Each of their heads was a huge, basin-sized blue flower.

The flowers stepped silently towards Garen’s and Windling’s position.

On the streets, in the neighboring house and on the roof. The blue flowers were everywhere.

They were like tiny dwarfs, quietly surrounding Garen and Windling.

As Garen furrowed his brows, his body released a cloud of thick, black gas which spread out in all directions.

Countless black cloud crows were formed. They let out cries and pounced at the flower humanoids.

The cloud crows gathered their wings and shot out like sharp arrows. It was like a harvest, with the surrounding flower humanoids dropping like flies.

Ssssss..

Abruptly, Garen turned and looked at the yard behind him.

In the small garden in front of the reddish-brown building, an over three metres tall blue flower humanoid swiftly stood up.

Its head was a big blue flower with a two-metre radius. It was completely like a human as it stood up and stretched its back. In the middle of the blue flower giant’s flower was a blue, O-shaped mouth. It was like a fish’s mouth, opening and closing non-stop. There was even some sticky acid flowing up from it.

Garen blinked and twisted the air in front of him.

Chaa!!!

A transparent, shapeless dragon head attacked ferociously.

The blue light in front of the blue flower giant shattered instantly, leaving huge amounts of blue light shards. Its head was instantly bitten off and disappeared into the shapeless dragon’s mouth.

Windling was holding a silver-black round mirror at the side, attempting to check something. When he saw that the flower giant’s head had suddenly vanished, his expression darkened.

"Can’t you wait for me to calculate its data before you devour it!?"

Poof!

Suddenly, Garen’s expression changed as he grabbed his abdomen.

A giant, red dragon mouth opened beside him and instantly took form. Then came a crash. The dragon vomited large amounts of torn blue flower petals and yellow-green acid.

"Sure enough, I can’t simply eat. It hurts my stomach." Garen did not look well. His body had gradually connected with the eight headed dragon. The state of the eight headed dragon would affect the state of his body.

Additionally, his state would also affect the eight headed dragon. This was also the reason why upgrading his body attributes would affect the evolution of the eight headed dragon..

However, this connection had negative side effects now.

Garen felt his stomach lurch. He had an urge to throw up.

After the red dragon head beside him had vomited out the remnants of the flower giant, it weakly disappeared into thin air.

"Haha, hurt your tummy? Your fault for eating random things!" Windling burst out laughing.

Garen gave him a stern stare and he stopped laughing, frightened.

Among the flower giant’s remnants on the ground, there was a yellow-green porridge like substance. It was releasing a strong acidic odour, causing Garen and Windling to back off.

The cries of the whirring cloud crows was ongoing, but there was not a single flower humanoid in sight.

Other than the acid, this type of first form monsters was good for nothing. Even the strongest one among them - the flower giant, was just a second form monster. Surprisingly, this strong odour and acidity could hurt the eight headed dragon’s stomach.

Garen realized that he had to be more careful. He shouldn’t attempt to eat everything he saw.

Both of them completely cleared one side of the town of all of the blue flower humanoids. The surroundings mutants were all frightened and fled; too afraid to come close. Only then did Garen relax slightly.

He casually walked into someone’s house. Only after squatting for more than half an hour in the toilet did his stomach felt better. At times, the eight headed dragon’s overly quick digestion rate was quite a disadvantage.

To completely heal the predicaments on his body wasn’t difficult for someone proficient in the martial arts like Garen. After excreting the acid, he used the Red Jade Palm to clear the remaining toxins. Only then did he fully recover.

In fact, the blue flower giant wouldn’t be considered poisonous. It was the acidity of the odour that Garen’s stomach couldn’t take. Instead of saying the poison caused diarrhea, it was actually the odour.

As he came out from the toilet, Garen leaned on the wall and walked into the living room. He saw Windling playing with the green, round mirror in his hand.

He walked over and saw a row of words and symbols bouncing on the mirror. He recognized some of the tactic symbols, but he hadn’t seen most of them.

A black dragon whirlwind was on the mirror. It was around ten centimetres tall. It floated in front of Windling, like a miniature tornado.

The black whirlwind was completely made up of black gas. As it spinned relentlessly, blue bolts faintly flickered on its surface. It was as though a real whirlwind was shrunk and placed on the mirror in front of Windling.

The whirlwind was just the size of a palm. It constantly changed its direction and speed on Windling’s hand.

"What’s this?" Garen asked out of curiosity. "Is this used for weather forecasting?"

Windling held the black whirlwind with both of his hands, as if he was controlling it.

"This is a black whirlwind that i brought from the Black Sky. It was mainly used to create and repair heirlooms and equipments." As he summarized, he controlled the end of the black whirlwind and kept drawing something on the mirror’s surface.

"Black Whirlwind?"

"Yes. Since my life is now tied to boss, people from the Obscuro definitely wish to eat my flesh and drink my blood. After considering for a long time, I realized you’ve treated me well. Hence, I’ve decided to do put in some effort for our safety." Windling replied as he controlled the small whirlwind.

"What effort?" As Garen has never seen the process of creating or repairing heirlooms and equipments, he looked on with interest.

"There. There is one on the table. Its specially made for you." Windling pointed at the small table on the right with his mouth.

Garen looked over immediately and saw a green mirror on the black stone table.

He walked over and picked up the mirror, surveying it. It was like a common dress mirror. The only difference was the decoration.

"What does this thing do?"

Windling retrieved the Black Whirlwind. The small whirlwind dissipated into black gas and quickly wriggled into the black gem ring on his hand.

He lifted the repaired mirror, looking pleased. Hearing Garen’s question, he answered.

"Detection. Mainly for detection. According to the various scenarios we’ve met these few days, I made some calculations."

He turned to face Garen.

"In the coming days, we might be facing the Obscuro’s pursuers. Do not think that because you have your final card, you have nothing to fear. The Obscuro has countless heirlooms and poisons. Just by accumulating four or five types, your abilities will instantly drop to the bottom. I’ve created this thing as a counter to those situations.

He lifted the small green mirror.

"I shall call it Windling’s fury!" He looked satisfied. "Those old bastards in the Obscuro were heartless. They thoroughly angered me! Hence, I’ve decided to make a testament to my anger. Oh, but the fighting shall still be left to you."

"You don’t have much talent in giving names." Garen was speechless.

"I think this name is very domineering though?" Windling shook his hands. "All of this is not important. The most important thing is its function."

He gently placed the mirror on his shoulder and gave a hard press.

Crash!!

The mirror directly latched onto his shoulder blade.

From afar, it looked like a diamond-shaped green armor on his left shoulder, mildy reflecting a mirror-like luster.

The armor extended from his shoulders. Its end protruded slightly, forming a sharp edge.

"Isn’t it domineering?" Windling looked satisfied. "This thing has two major functions. Number 1: It gathers the wearer’s actual body condition and makes a comparison with the surroundings. If there are threats to the wearer, it would emit mild, red light. The intensity of the red light represents the threat level."

"That’s not a bad function. Can it test the level of toxins?" Garen was suddenly interested.

"Of course." Windling nodded. "The second function: Encrypted Messages. This function is simple. It only has to identify an used frequency. I’ve encrypted in five times. It is absolutely impossible for anyone to break it!" He looked pleased. "With this, we can directly have short distance communication without being snooped on. The distance limit is fifty kilometres. For it to be stronger, it would require too much. Remember the time I was tricked and captured and couldn’t contact you, these kind of situations can be avoided.

"This thing is not bad." Garen nodded his head in approval. "Can you create a few more?"

"The materials required are quite a hassle. They are not considered as rare, but many types are required. I gathered them as I followed you. After so many days, it was only sufficient for two. If you want more of them, I think it might take some time." Windling helplessly opened his hands.

Garen imitated his ways and pressed the mirror on his left shoulder.

With a crash, four claws automatically appeared from the mirror and tightly held on to his shoulder. Its end swiftly extended, forming a beautiful sharp-edged shape.

"Heyhey, can you hear me?" A soft, low voice suddenly came, as if from an earpiece. It was Windling’s voice.

Garen gave him a glance. He noticed that he pressed the pauldron with one hand and gently moved his lips.

"Your voice doesn’t have to be loud, just being clear would do. Oh yes, I forgot to mention. For the threat detection, I’ve differentiated five levels."

Windling said in a serious tone.

"Number 1: No light. If the Windling’s Fury doesn’t light up, it means there is no threat and can be ignored.

Number 2: Mild light. If there’s only a little red light from green to red, it means that the threat is small.

Number 3: Mild red. The red is clear, but not dark. A stronger threat that has to be respected. You have to pay attention and be on guard to avoid being tricked by not being careful.

Number 4: Bright red. It is an opponent on your level. The opponent has the potential to severely injure you or kill you. It all depends on performance to determine who has the upper hand, but be careful of secret heirlooms and the sort.

Name 5: Dark Red. Incredibly dangerous. Flee if you meet this kind of opponent without hesitation. Whether you will be able to flee is also a problem. This means the opponent could severely injure you with a casual attack."

Chapter 388: Unexpected Discovery 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"That detailed? This thing is able to measure totem light?" Garen was stunned.

"Of course. The totem light is the main thing." Windling explained. "The working principle of this device is rather complicated, but the only thing you should know is that it can measure the totem light of your opponent and compare it with your totem light. Naturally, different people will have differing strength and information, so the result will be different as well."

Garen nodded to indicate that he understood what was said.

"Alright then, let’s go and give this thing a try."

"Be patient."

Windling told Garen.

"This item requires an activation phrase in order to get it up and running."

"An activation phrase?"

"Yes. Didn’t you know this? These types of custom made heirlooms require an activation phrase so that no one will take advantage of it, right?" Windling shook her index finger as she explained.

"What is the activation phrase then?" Garen nodded.

"Activate! Windling’s Fury!!"

Windling raised both of her hands up with all her might and laughed three times. "Ha! Ha! Ha!"

"..."

The atmosphere had become cold…

Windling placed her hand down as she realized Garen’s unfriendly gaze.

"Alright alright. What a man without any sense of humor. No wonder you can’t get a girlfriend, even though you’re so handsome."

"The real activation phrase is print it, magic mirror."

As Windling finished her sentence, her shoulders" pauldrons glew red and immediately disappeared.

"That’s about it."

Garen’s cold gaze then disappeared.

"Alright then. Let’s go to the next location and have a look at its effect."

"No problem!"

*********************

Somewhere in a mountain valley, thousands of kilometers away from the Red River Valley.

The sky was grey and cloudy, shrouding the sun completely. The whole sky was covered with clouds.

The mountain valley was filled with green fern plants. There were a variety of them, from small to big and short to tall. They covered the whole mountain valley, just like a forest.

White mist lingered between the ferns and caged the whole valley, covering the whole scene in a layer of white. It was almost as if someone were looking through a pair of fogged up glasses.

The mountain valley was like a small basin, covered by elevated green hills.

The entrance to this basin was a small green fern forest.

Two black silhouettes flew passed the fern forest at great speed, and slowly landed at the entrance of the mountain valley as they formed into two black shirted human figures.

As the black smoke dispersed, Garen looked into the mountain valley from afar, and through the white mist, he could see that the mountain valley was filled with levitating stones.

These stones, big and small, were levitating quietly in the middle of the air inside the mountain valley, as if they were supported by something from below.

The largest stone was at least ten meters wide and even had a little tree and a small grass field on top of it.

"Is there some error in our route? We have been to three places and there isn’t anyone around." Windling asked skeptically as she followed Garen from behind.

"No. It’s not that the route is wrong, it’s just that something had happened here recently so these places are empty." Garen replied coldly.

Both of them put on their magic mirror pauldrons on their left shoulder. The faint green colored pauldron looked like a beautiful jade stone.

"This location is the largest nearby. Should we enter it directly?" Windling asked as she looked at Garen.

Silent, Garen squatted down as he touched the dirt on the ground.

"Someone was here before us, about ten minutes ago." He said coldly. "This smell, I’m afraid, might be from the one who had been stalking us."

"What should we do?" Windling frowned. "Should we proceed or retreat."

Garen’s lips curled, giving off a cold smile.

"Since we’re here, we might as well meet our friends."

The shadow of the eight headed dragon slowly appeared behind him.

************

Within the deep zone of the mountain valley.

Two crowds, in black and blue, were facing each other.

The people in black shirt were obviously from Black Sky. All of them were wearing black masks and were different from the lot from before. Every one of them had black gas surrounding them, giving off a rather strange presence.

The one who stood at the front was their leader. He was in a black robes and white mask, which had three red lines on the mouth and eyes. The design was very simple, where the red lines formed into a smiley face on the mask as it gave off a strange and mysterious vibe.

The people they were facing against were a group of people in ice blue armor. There were a total of four of them, and were staring coldly at what was in front of them. The one who stood at the front was a flat chested woman with a brown ponytail.

She had a brown whip in her hand, half of it had dug into the ground, as if it were a wiggling, living creature.

There was a golden staff in the middle of both parties.

There were layers of small circles on the staff, which was placed on a white stone. What was strange was that the staff was surrounded by a thin layer of ice.

"Black Sky, haven’t you guys crossed the line? You have become too greedy." The girl with a ponytail said coldly as she tried to retain her anger and stared at the people from the Black Sky.

"We discovered the Golden Staff first, and we’re also the one who discovered the activation phrase as well. What right do you have to say that it is yours?"

"It doesn’t matter who discovered it first. What matters is you people have discovered this heirloom in our territory." A sharp voice came from the white mask.

The woman was annoyed. "Then what about the activation phrase? We are the ones who deciphered the activation phrased first. Why do we have to pass it to you!?"

They had went through a great ordeal and spent countless of resources and gemstones here. They hand spent countless days deciphering the activation phrase of the golden staff, and the members of the Black Sky appeared and attempted to remove the gemstone out of it. The members of the Black Sky claimed that this heirloom was left by their ancestors, and they just happened to forgot the activation phrase.

As they had a grasp of the opponent’s strength, they decided to retreat, but the people of the Black Sky didn’t allow them to do so unless they gave them the activation phrase. Hence they were currently in a stalemate.

They had heard rumors of how strong the people of the Black Sky were, but they didn’t expect that they would be so much stronger than the rumors had suggested when they faced them in reality.

As one of the captains of the powerful ice castle, the girl with the ponytail was filled with rage. They were stronger in terms of power as they had two form three totem users and two form two elites, whereas the Black Sky only had one form three and two form two totem users.

However, the Black Sky had a stronger identity, which made them unable to make any moves, and were oppressed by the opposing party instead.

Shey knew that she was stronger but was forced to restrict herself. These made the four people of the Ice Castle start to fill with anger. Although it was just an imitation product of a heirloom, it was still important to the ice castle. Within this chaotic era, every ounce of strength attainable was considered precious, including the heirloom.

"Last warning. Give us the activation phrase and you can leave." The white masked man said coldly.

The ponytail woman gritted her teeth as she gave a deadly stare towards him.

She didn’t dare to attack as she knew that the Ice Castle might be annihilated if she were to attack now.

Suddenly, the white masked man looked at the other side of the mountain wall.

"Same goes to you. Leave now and don’t let me see you again, or else."

Movement could be seen from the mountain wall and three men appeared. They were in hunter attire and looked very well trained.

"Lord White Ghost, we’re here under the command of the chief of Fung Clan…"

"Don’t use the name of Black Tiger King as leverage." The white masked replied coldly.

"Lord White Ghost…"

Ah!!

Suddenly the man beside him screamed as he shriveled at an incredible speed. He looked like a deflating balloon, and soon dropped onto the ground with only his skin left.

The remaining two of them were stunned and immediately retreated as they scanned their surroundings in fear.

The White Ghost let out a shrill laughter.

"This is the result of not listening to me. You guys are still alive because of the Black Tiger King, and you guys think that you are some hot shot?"

Two of them were sweating cold sweat. Although he was just a form one totem user, it was terrifying to see him killed abruptly.

The people of the Black Tiger King and Ice Castle didn’t say another word and they kept quiet, falling into a deep dilemma. It seemed that the White Ghost was not an opponent that could be easily dealt with.

At that moment, two black, misty figures appeared behind the white masked man, and soon condensated into two tall humanoid figures.

"Lords." The white mask turned around and greeted the two with a bow.

The two figures were a male and a female, who had a black and green hair respectively. Both of them looked young, and seemed to be in their early thirties. Both had on their shoulders black robes, with golden-green armor on their feet.

The black haired man nodded.

"What’s the current situation?"

"The foundation has been set." White Ghost replied respectfully. "However we have accidentally discovered a new heirloom, the Golden Staff."

"Not bad. Tell these people to scram and execute the operation immediately, or else we won’t have enough time." The green haired girl said softly.

The man nodded as he looked at the groups of people from the Ice Castle and Black Tiger King. These two groups were the major power players in the nearby area. All of them naturally were no small characters since they were able to survive in such an environment.

The man started to become impatient and was about to open his mouth.

Suddenly he felt that the sky had become cloudy.

"What’s going on? Is it about to rain?" The man looked up suspiciously, and his pupil shrunk.

Everyone in the area looked up and was stunned as they saw a gigantic mouth in the sky.

A black cloud was slowly approaching from the mountain valley.

It was a cloud filled with countless black crows!

The black haired man recalled something and his face went pale.

"It’s the Cloud Crow!! The Eight Cloud Crow! Retreat! Retreat!!"

He suddenly shouted.

The people of the Ice Castle were stunned as well, as they looked at the sky that was being swallowed by the clouds of crows. These crows, which had some strange mist surrounding, them kept producing a rather weird scream.

As they looked up, they couldn’t see any part of the sky at all.

"The Eight Cloud Crow… It’s the RAL! The RAL has arrived!" The ponytail woman was emotional. She couldn’t feel any more happier as she looked at the people from the Black Sky panicking in front of her. If they couldn’t obtain it, she naturally wished that no one else could.

Compared to the Black Sky, the RAL was much more powerful.

They didn’t allow anyone to oppose them. Whoever did would be considered going against them, and going against them meant betrayal to the Alliance, and betrayal to the Alliance meant a rebellion, a rebellion that needed to be eliminated!!

The subordinates of the Black Tiger King didn’t dare to make any move at all. With such a huge superpower arriving the scene, whoever provoked them meant that they would drag the Black Tiger King into the issue with them.

Chapter 389: Meet Again 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kaw Kaw!!

Shrieking Cloud Crow cries came from the sky abovee the mountain valley. The whole mountain valley was shrouded in darkness, only a tiny bit of sunlight could be seen in between the wings of the cloud crows.

The three parties were preparing to defend themselves.

The people from the Black Sky were the most anxious, as the main target of the Eight Cloud Crow had always been Black Sky. The Eight Cloud Crow was angry at Black Sky, as he was being hunted by the them and had been taking his revenge all over the area.

Pew!!

A Cloud Crow dived as a black streak was drawn in the sky and landed on a member of Black Sky.

His left chest was filled with yellow totem light, but under the attack of the Cloud Crow, it was being torn apart like paper.

As the crows continued shrieking in the sky, no one could hear his scream of pain.

All members of the Black Sky were under attack by the Cloud Sky.

In a blink of an eye, multiple members of the Black Sky had died, leaving only White Ghost and two of the recently arrived members standing firm on their ground.

They effortlessly defended against the attacks of the Cloud Crows. After an attack, whether it be a success or a failure, the Cloud Crow would always turn into black fog, and morph into the Cloud Crow again once it gained enough altitude.

What was strange was that the majority of the Black Cloud Crow didn’t come after them, but flew past them and went deeper into the Mountain Valley.

There were two human figures being covered within the Cloud Crows as they went deeper into the Mountain Valley.

One of the silhouettes looked down at the three groups, but none of them dared to return his cold gaze..

That man above had three brightly lit dots on his forehead, and eyes that were dyed blood red. He was surrounded by countless Cloud Crows, and looked like a demon among the clouds.

Within minutes, the Cloud Crows disappeared, and like a stormy cloud, moved deeper into the mountain valley.

It was only then that the three parties noticed that the Golden Staff in the middle had been broken into two pieces during the Cloud Crow’s attack. Silver liquid leaked out from the staff as if it were bleeding.

The Heirloom had been accidentally destroyed by the Cloud Crows.

Both the Ice Castle and Black Tiger King’s men felt happy as they looked at the Black Sky.

There were only three members left in the Black Sky, and the green haired woman was in lead. She looked at the mountain valley’s deeper areas with a pale face.

"Bring the corpses along, and let’s go!" She finally made a decision.

The Heirloom hidden deep inside could be found at any time, but it was pointless once your life was gone.

"Eight Cloud Crow…!" She stared at the black clouds with rage. "Sooner or later someone would kill you! Your arrogance won’t last forever!"

The three of them immediately release a Four-armed Giant Mantis, and each of them placed the corpses on it and left the mountain valley with great haste.

The ponytail woman from the Ice Castle looked at the black cloud.

"We should make our move too. We’re lucky to encounter the Eight Cloud Crow, but we won’t be this lucky next time. The Eight Cloud Crow kills anyone he fancies and without mercy. We need to tell the Fort Master about this and Inform all the clan members to be cautious when they’re out."

"Big sister, who do you think is stronger, this Eight Cloud Crow or the fort master?" A youngster who had recently grew a moustache asked curiously.

"They’re both strong, but the fort master is on our side, and a leader who will protect us from any creature. The Eight Cloud Crow is a very powerful individual, but he killed people without mercy, so he definitely isn’t someone good." The ponytail woman explained softly.

"Bring the remains of the Golden Staff and let’s head out. Although the material was a waste, it still possesses some value."

The people from the Ice Castle gathered the remains of the staff with indiscernable feelings. Their long term training had shown their fruits, as none of them really made any noise. However, they would unconsciously looked deep into the mountain valley every once in a while.

That overwhelming power was deeply etched into everyone’s minds.

The old men were in awe, whereas the youngsters’ hearts were burning with motivation. Perhaps one day they would possess such power! Such strength!

To be able to make your enemy panic and retreat by just hearing your name!

No one noticed that the subordinates of the Black Tiger King had already left the scene.

Similar to the Ice Castle, the legendary Eight Cloud Crow’s power had definitely left an impression.

That man, with three red dots on his forehead, standing among the black clouds was carved deep into the recesses of their minds.

************

At the very bottom of the mountain valley.

In between the big field of dark green ferns was an empty land filled with black stones. There was not a single blade of grass on it; it was completely barren.

The largest levitating stone was floating among the black land.

This giant stone was at least ten meters wide, and even had a small yellow-green forest on top of it. In addition, there were even small flocks of birds dancing about around the giant stone, chirping happily.

These white and red birds were very active and adorable, as they chased each other around under the sunlight.

Within the forest at the top of the levitating stone.

Two groups stood quietly in front of an old tree.

On one side, there were two groups, in black robes and red masks. They had an eye of the black sun emblem on their chests, indicating that they were members of the Black Sky.

On the other hand, they was a young, fair skinned man, who was their leader. There were a total of four of them, three male and one female. The male leader was in a white robe, and his expression, although rather pale, was calm. The most eye catching feature of his was his eyes; a faint gray.

Both the red masked person and the silver eyed youngster were both very quiet, as if they were lost in thought.

The only thing that moved between them was time.

However, something seemed to be coming from the sky beyond the forest, similar to a huge murder of crows, coming closer and closer.

The leader in red masked finally spoke up.

"Looks like we have a new person arriving soon. We may have to retreat without obtaining our objective again." Her voice was of a gentlewoman, where it gave off a soothing and relaxing vibe.

"Do your stuff." The silver eyed man nodded his head and didn’t speak further as he stared at the wilted old tree trunk.

The old tree was very sturdy, its circumference was about the girth of two people. However, what was strange was that a clear human face could be seen at the center of the black tree. It had two eyes, a nose, a mouth and even had a beard underneath its chin. The beard was the tree’s black roots.

This tree’s face had its eyes closed, as if it were sound asleep.

The red masked person smiled slightly and looked at the sky afar.

"Let’s go. That man had a deep misunderstanding towards the Black Sky."

The other people bowed slightly and followed the red masked person into the shades of the forest at great speed. Two wisps of black fog appeared and covered both of their bodies. As the fog disappeared, it took the two of them with it.

"How is it? Do you have any idea, Beckstone?" A woman in a fiery red armor asked. The armor revealed her perfect body as she stood beside the silver eyed man’s side, suggesting that she relied entirely on his decision.

"If only Darian was still around." Beckstone sighed. "He’s best at guessing riddles. We would definitely be able to solve this if he were."

The red armored woman kept quiet as the atmosphere became rather dense.

"Sorry, I shouldn’t have mentioned the incident." Beckstone apologised softly.

"No, it’s all my fault. If only I wasn’t being held hostage by that fellow, Darian wouldn’t have died." The red armored woman was Berlina. She was held hostage by Garen, and forced Beckstone to fight ‘squarely’ with him.

The cries of the crows grew louder as they approached.

Soon, two black armored figures came into the forest. Both of them were male, and the one in front was a man with golden, shawled hair, with a handsome face and three red dots on his forehead. His expression was cold, his body surrounded by the black fog that had yet to disperse.

As he entered the forest, Beckstone turned around and looked at them.

In a blink of an eye, Beckstone was filled with rage.

"It’s you!!"

Garen smiled at him.

"Beckstone, I sensed you and the Black Sky bastards from afar. Once I knew you were here, I immediately came over." His gaze was calm as he was very confident in himself.

"The days we had in the manor were rather peaceful. Who knew it had been so long. How nostalgic."

"Garen Trejons!!!"

The red armored Berlina who was standing beside Beckstone grit her teeth as she stared at Garen.

"It’s nice to see you again, my lady." Garen’s smile was even brighter.

Whoosh!!!

A sharp red light was pointed towards Garen.

Bam!

The red light was blocked by a cloud of black fog, dispersing and disappearing once they collided. To be precise, as the red light fired, its speed was strangely reduced.

That streak of red line could be seen hanging in the air. Besides that, the ground was burnt black, as if a line of fire had razed it.

Soon, the burnt ground reverted back to its usual green state.

Berlina retracted her right hand in rage.

"I will kill you eventually! I will avenge Darian!!"

"Whenever you like." Garen smiled gently. "That is, if you can leave this place alive."

"Do you want to fight!?" Beckstone replied coldly. "This is the territory of the old tree, whoever has bad intentions will be restricted. As long as one harbours the intent of destruction, their strength would be sapped, and they wouldn’t be able to lift a finger at all."

Garen was surprised, and suddenly felt something was wrong. He had an urge to not want to destroy the peaceful surroundings.

It was a strange feeling, similar to of someone who wanted to keep sleeping when they were half awake. All intentions towards destruction was diminished, and could no longer be brought upon.

As he carefully basked in this strange vibe, Beckstone and Berlina were seemingly under its influence, too, and didn’t speak a word afterwards.

The situation had come to a standstill.

Chapter 390: Meet Again 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Minutes passed. Both parties stood still without movement.

Windling stood behind Garen and kept yawning, evident to how suited this place was for a nap.

Soon, noon arrived. The scorching hot golden rays came from above and bathed the whole forest in sunlight.

At this moment, the old tree opened both of its eyes. It opened its mouth, and an old voice came out.

"It has eight legs, and is able to hold water. While its speed is slow, it runs very steadily."

"It's a repetition from the previous riddle." Beckstone muttered.

Garen heard it from afar as well. It was as if the voice had directly entered into his mind. Although he didn't know what language it spoke, he somehow knew what it said.

He started thinking about the riddle.

"This is the Spirit Tree's Riddle, one of the only two strange phenomena that could be understood." Windling said from his back as his face was filled with excitement. "I can't believe I can experience the Spirit Tree's Riddle in my life. As long as we can guess the riddle, we will be able granted a drop of Life's Dew by the Spirit Tree."

"What's the use of it?" Garen looked at Windling even though the sound is transmitted through the magic mirror.

"It's very beneficial. It's most useful trait is lengthening ones' lifespan. One drop of Life's Dew is able to extend your lifespan by forty years! This is a recently discovered mysterious phenomenon. Naturally, the Black Sky has already calculated this data in detail, but I didn't expect this group of people to know of its existence as well." Windling cast a surprised look at Beckstone and his team. He didn't expect other people outside of the Black Sky to know of this place.

"Even I have only heard of it. I do not know the exact location of the Spirit Tree's Riddle. This is one of the Black Sky's top secrets."

Suddenly, Beckstone's eyes glowed, as if he remembered something and said a phrase.

"The answer is the Spider Teapot!!"

The old tree was stunned. Its face melted into the tree's bark and soon disappeared.

Soon the old tree wilted. The large amount of branches that littered the tree followed suit, its leaves curling up and turning into a dark brown. Then the leaves started shedding water.

Swiftly, a black branch arched down in front of Beckstone.

There was a black petal on it, and it slowly opened up, layer by layer, showing off the countless petals revealing what was encased and hidden within. It was like a black Peony flower, complicated yet beautiful and delicate.

At the center of the black petals laid a clear and sticky dew.

"That's the Life's Dew! We've gotten hold of a drop of Life's Dew! This is very exciting indeed!!" Windling was cheering with happiness. "Quickly boss! Kill them and grab hold of the Life's Dew! They have lived long enough!!"

"We haven't kept it properly yet, why are you so excited?" Garen looked at Windling with a speechless look. "You should try and go against them."

He had already felt that the restriction within the surrounding had been lifted as the old tree's face disappeared.

"I am just a clerk.. A clerk… Hehe" Windling quickly retreated with a ridiculous smile on his face.

Beckstone put away the Life's Dew and turned away quietly.

"Next, we should pick up from our previous business."

"I think so too." Garen smiled.

Slowly, black fog and golden light started surrounding them.

Two intense powers collided with each other as the black fog and golden light kept disappearing and reappearing.

Two different energies emanated within the forest.

Black and gold, separating the forest into two different areas.

"Your Sunflower has grown gain." Garen took out a black pocket watch as he looked at Beckstone with interest.

Beckstone looked at him coldly and raised his hand. Goldenl light suddenly appeared by his side, forming Golden Whirlpool Beasts. It was different from the Whirlpool Beast from the past as the current Whirlpool Beasts were golden, as if they were forged from gold. As they formed into solidified bodies, these Whirlpool Beasts started growling at Garen.

Growl!!

The golden light kept shaping the Whirlpool Beasts one at a time completely surrounding Garen and Windling.

Garen flicked his pocket watch.

Ding!!

With a soft ring, a huge column of black fog spilled forth from the pocket watch, forming countless numbers if Cloud Crows as they started revolving around his body.

Kaw!!

The Cloud Crows confronted the Whirlpool Beasts with its strange cries.

"Impressive Technique!" Beckstone's eyes were filled with surprise, but he didn't express it thoroughly. "That's to be expected. If you were to be taken down by me this easily, won't my hardship and pain be all wasted?"

Somewhere during their conversation, a green seed the size of a thumbnail found its way into his right hand.

With all his might, he crushed the seed into his left shoulder.

The seed was thoroughly embedded within his skin.

Szz Szz… A shivering sound came out of the wound. The seed had started to sprout and grew directly from Beckstone's left hand.

The green bud dug out of his skin and grew rapidly as it became tall, thick and sturdy.

Soon it grew to the point where it was as tall as Beckstone.

The green plant soon sprouted a black bud. The bud slowly opened up, revealing a human eye inside it.

As the eye opened, it instantly looked at Garen.

Suddenly, Garen couldn't see anything else as his vision went pitch black.

At the same time, the Golden Whirlpool Beasts leaped towards Garen and attacked. Each of the Whirlpool Beast were much stronger and bigger than last time. They had already reached Spiritualization, and went toe to toe with the Cloud Crows.

"Sight Vision, stolen!" Beckstone stared coldly at Garen, as a giant golden tree slowly appeared behind him. A golden pupil could be seen in the middle of the big tree.

A transparent strong bending force landed onto Garen's territory.

Boom!!!

A large part of the Black Fog was pushed away, even the Whirlpool Beast had no choice but to step back as they did not dare to go closer to it.

Large amounts of grass and dirt were flung away, leaving a huge crater in the forest.

The whole levitating stone trembled violently and a hole was created underneath. A shapeless ray of light burst through the rock from the top.

Garen landed just beside the crater with a smile on his face.

"Impossible!!?" Beckstone shivered as he took out another seed and planted it once more in his left shoulder.

After a series of horrifying noise of the seed being planted into the hand, the new seed sprouted and out came a new bud. This time, a human ear was inside it.

"Hearing! Stolen!" Beckstone's face was getting more and more pale.

"Beckstone…" Berlina stood at one side and couldn't do anything but to worry for Beckstone's wellbeing. She knew the horrible side effects of these Secret Tactics. Although its effect was potent, it was extremely damaging to the caster's body!

"I can definitely kill him!" Beckstone's eyes were filled with confidence.

Pew!!

Another shapeless bending light pillar was shot out again.

However, Garen moved slightly to the left and was merely grazed by the light pillar.

Pew pew pew!!!

Beckstone didn't believe his eyes and started to attack nonsensically with his Sunflower. He was the only one who knew how strong the opponent was after the fight in the manor. Hence he knew that this high density attack was the only way to damage him.

However…

Garen would occasionally move to the left, jump, and leap forward. Each of his actions allowed him to perfectly dodge the light pillar.

"Impossible!! Impossible!!" Beckstone focused his light pillars once again and the golden tree behind him would shoot out a high speed light pillar every two seconds or so.

However all was in vain.

Beckstone took out the third seed.

"Beckstone stop!! You've gone crazy!!" Berlina attempted to grab hold of Beckstone's hand.

"Get out of my way!"

She was pushed down to the ground.

Beckstone had completely gone insane. His humiliation back in the manor where Darian was killed right in front of his eyes and combined with cruel and bloody scenes in the experiment laboratory, these images incessantly flooded his mind.

He planted the third seed into his chest.

The silver light in Beckstone's eye suddenly glowed brighter.

A new black plant sprouted once again, giving birth to a new black bud. As the bud opened up, A human nose was revealed.

"Smell! Stolen!!"

Garen's body nudged slightly.

Beckstone was ecstatic and decided to attack him with his sunflower erratically.

A near infinite amount of shapeless light pillars burst forth.

The explosions entirely covered the surface of the levitating stone.

The explosions were nothing short of thunderbird roars in the sky.

Both Berlina and Windling had ran far away as they didn't dare to stay close to the battlefield. Everyone had their attention on this battle it unfolded in front of them.

However, everyone could see that there was too much of a difference in their strength.

Beckstone was still at the spiritualization level but Garen had obviously gone up to another new level.

Beckstone's lips started to crack, as his original, smooth skin had started to dry and shrivel up.

"Impossible!! How is this possible!!?? Where did I go wrong!!?"

He was unwilling to accept the reality.

The holes on the ground kept appearing, but Garen still slowly walked towards him without difficulty.

Garen didn't even activate his defensive totem light and he walked towards him with ease.

The light pillars passed through his legs, but he did not take any damage whatsoever.

Beckstone couldn't help but to feel a fear in him as he looked at the approaching Garen.

"I will not lose again! Never…" He muttered as he took out the fourth seed.

Boom!

Suddenly, all of the budded flowers exploded and Beckstone took a few steps back.

Garen opened his eyes and all his stolen senses were given back to him.

"The Life's Drew… It's a rare item indeed. You won't be able to protect it if you don't have enough strength." He put on a smile on his face once more.

"You!" Beckstone was defeated but he took out a golden diamond crystal once more.

"Is that the item you're going to rely on this time?" Garen looked at the crystal in his hand. "You're really weak."

He shook his head.

"I once killed thirty two Field-level members and three General-level members of Black Sky in Victoria. I killed five middle-class general-level in the Long Northwest Slope. I have battled the Giant Divine Statue in Ender Kingdom and intercepted the Underworld Carriage in the abandoned city. I have faced hundreds of battles and I have yet lost one of them."

"I thought that you would have achieved something after such a long time but I didn't expect you to improve just this little bit." Garen's face was emotionless and the three markings on his forehead was brimming brightly in red color. "If you only have this amount of strength, I'm afraid you won't be going back today."

"I will not accept defeat!!" Beckstone held the golden crystal tightly as he stood back up. Tte silver light in his eyes glowed brighter and brighter to the point it was unbearable to see.

Chapter 391: Meet Again 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Even among the people there, only Beckstone understood well how heavy Garen’s words were. This was especially true if it were the Underworld Carriage. If it really was pointing towards that item, he didn’t even dare to imagine how powerful his current opponent was!

Suddenly, a familiar voice came from behind Beckstone.

"Garen?"

The person, one of the two who stood behind Beckstone, hadn’t spoken up until now.

Garen was stunned as he heard the familiar voice and looked at where the voice came from.

The opponent came out from the shade. He was in long grey robes and had a black wooden ring in his hand. He gently took off his thin hood with his hand, revealing a pale and old face.

He was Teacher Emin that Garen had been searching this whole time!!

"Garen… is that really you?!" Emin couldn’t believe himself as he stared intensely at the incredibly powerful man in front of him.

The image of the opponent overlapped with the face he had recognized when Garen was still under him.

"Teacher…" Garen’s tone was fused with shock, yet relief, and bitterness as well.

With this reply, Beckstone, Berlina and the little boy behind Emin had their eyes wide open.

This meant that Garen had admitted to his identity and he was indeed the sole student of Emin in the past.

Emin was the person who guided Beckstone to the Spirit Tree’s Riddle. He was also the luminarist who joined Beckstone’s team in the middle of the expedition. Although he didn’t have much strength, his knowledge was unparalleled as he was the successor of the famous Tasura Academy. No one expected that he was the teacher of the Eight Cloud Crow Garen.

Emin looked at Garen with a complicated look.

"I once believed that you would become a very powerful totem user, but I didn’t expect it to be this soon…"

He pondered for a while as his eyes filled with sadness..

"You finally ended up in the Royal Alliance…"

Garen stayed silent. He didn’t have any choice. Vanderman’s territory determined that his only path was to side with the Royal Alliance.

However, the Royal Alliance would eventually collapse in the future…

From the very beginning, he had no choice but to become a member of the Royal Alliance.

Vanderman had seriously offended the Terraflor Society, and the Obscuro Society had been trying to assassinate Vanderman. Eventually his relationship with them turned out to be incompatible.

However, the Royal Alliance was different. Vanderman had contributed a lot towards the Royal Alliance, and he had gave the result of his life long research to its Monarch as well, which formed a very solid relationship with them.

Perhaps it was due to the increment in his Intelligence attribute that caused him to think more than necessary.

Was his only path to follow the Royal Alliance until its collapse? This belief once again appeared in his mind as he saw Teacher Emin.

As he came back from his thought, he looked at the little boy behind Emin. The little boy had a delicate red butterfly on his shoulder. This butterfly was the one small scaled poisonous type totem that he had discussed with his teacher before.

He didn’t expect him to create one.

Emin noticed Garen’s gaze and pushed the little fellow out.

"This is your junior that I have recently recruited. His name is Bertin and he is quite talented."

"Bertin, please call him senior."

Bertin was a small boy with red short hair and had freckles on his nose.

"Sesesese...nior!" He stuttered, not because he was afraid but overly excited. "Can.. Can I be as strong as you someday!??"

"You can as long as you keep working your way up."Garen revealed a gentle smile.

Bertin’s eyes glimmered as he felt his senior was easy to talk to, yet he hesitated and seemed rather slow in voicing up.

"Big brother Beckstone is a good man, can you not make his life difficult?"

Beckstone couldn’t hold himself from his anger and tried to speak up but he vomited a pool of blood instead. Berlina immediately rushed towards him and pulled him up.

"Big brother Beckstone was coming after the Spirit Tree’s Riddle because of teacher’s health. Senior please stop making things difficult for him. Teacher is already ninety four years old and without the Life’s Dew…" Bertin couldn’t finish his sentence as his eyes turned red.

The teacher and disciple had different allegiances. One was of the Terraflor Society, and the other, the Royal Alliance. Although they had no conflict in their current standings, Garen knew that these power players would eventually collide against each other, and they would have to face against one another someday.

Garen understood well what Bertin’s words, and Emin’s intention was.

He didn’t expect that the Life’s Dew to be something requested by Emin. Furthermore, he didn’t expect Beckstone to come here to find the Life’s Dew just for Emin.

As he looked at the current situation teacher Emin was in, he couldn’t help but to feel remorse.

He focused his sight gaze on Beckstone. He knew that Beckstone’s hatred towards him would never be resolved when he killed his friend Darian in front of his eyes. Furthermore… The opponent was the seedling the Terraflor Society had been nurturing with everything they had, and so wouldn’t go down quietly.

However, he was here to find a solution for Emin, yet his teacher’s intention was to…

Garen calmed down.

Berlina and the others stared anxiously at Garen. He would be the one to decide whether they would be at war or make peace with each other.

A shapeless pressure slowly caged everyone, as if the air had solidified.

Berlina felt that she started to have trouble breathing. She would try her best to inhale but didn’t dare to make any sound. This feeling, where her life was in the hands of someone else, she didn’t want to experience it any longer…

Beckstone… She couldn’t help herself but to look at Beckstone in that moment.

This man who was usually calm and quick witted turned overactive when he faced with that man. It was obvious that Garen had scarred him for good.

Sweat started to form on Beckstone’s nose, and he couldn’t even use his hands to wipe them off. He could only continue his deadly stare at Garen. He had fallen into a defeat he had never tasted before since he was firmly defeated last time.

The taste of the sun turning into grey ash was still very fresh in his memory.

He was muddling along listlessly for days, and didn’t want to achieve anything at all. He daydreamed inside his home everyday like a zombie. He slept after eating, and daydreamed after his sleep. It was as if he had totally forgot everything.

The effort and sacrificed he had poured out was a total waste.

After that, his teacher had sent someone to deliver a white shelled diary to him. It was sent by Leanna’s parents, and inside were descriptions of Leanna’s everyday life.

Then he heard about his teacher’s terminal illness. Even as he rushed to see him, he was too late to see his teacher for the very last time. It was raining heavily that day, and he kneeled in the rain. Whether the water droplets on his cheeks were that of the rain or his tears, he didn’t know..

From that day onwards, he vowed that he would fulfill his teacher’s ambition.

No matter how much anger he had that dangerously obstructed his rationality, Beckstone finally restricted his urge, the irresistible urge to fight Garen with his life!

A breeze blew and leaves whistled.

The broken sunlight landed on each person present.

"Teacher… When did you join the Terraflor Society?" Garen suddenly asked.

Emin hesitated for a moment but he eventually answered.

"I have been a member of the Terraflor Society from the very beginning. The whole Tasura Academy is actually part of the Terraflor Society’s setup academy."

Garen closed his eyes as he lost himself in his thoughts.

On the other hand, Berlina and Beckstone were completely shocked, as if they just found out that Emin was actually a member of the Terraflor Society.

"In respect to my teacher’s wish, you guys can leave now." Garen finally came to a conclusion. "As the chaotic era came upon us, I didn’t come to see teacher Emin immediately, so I’ll use this as a compensation. Beckstone, don’t let me see you again."

Beckstone vomited another pool of black blood. As he was being carried by Berlina, his lips trembled and it was obvious that he was heavily injured. Every breath he took seemed bear the weight of the world.

"If you let me go today, I will make sure I’ll be the one letting you go once in the future!"

He was a man of arrogance, and yet he was humiliated by Garen twice. This made his desire grew ever stronger than before.

"Let’s go!" Beckstone barely pushed Berlina away as he turned around and leave.

Emin and Bertin looked at Garen one last time before turning around and leaving the scene as well.

The four of them walked to the edge of the levitating stone. A green light flashed and a giant Jade Hawk appeared.

The hawk’s wing span was at least twenty meters wide, and his back was close to six meters wide. The party climbed up onto the hawk.

Garen looked at them from afar until they ascended beyond his sight

***************

At the other peak of the mountain valley inside the red fern forest.

There were a few figures in green shirts, each of them were in tight white full body armor, with their heads fully covered, the only visible parts of their bodies being their eyes.

The white armored men had a well trained air about them as they stood silently in the forest. Two of the white armored men who stood at the front observed the situation unfold between Garen and Beckstone from afar.

"Interesting. I didn’t know that Eight Cloud Crow was actually Emin’s disciple." The green armored leader whispered in a male’s voice.

"Beckstone must be very angry to be humiliated by this fellow twice in a row. What a pity." The other person was a female, her voice was rather frivolous.

"If you feel pity towards him, why didn’t you help Darian out back then?"

"We only care about Beckstone not dying. All this other stuff is very exhausting!" The lady complained.

"Then stop complaining." The male leader said impatiently.

"Don’t you feel excited when you look at this kid’s battle? Isn’t it good to feel excited?" The lady said. "Oh right, take a look at that Garen kid, isn’t he a character? He facial figure looks good and has a good fitness as well. He’s clearly a few times stronger than you! I wonder how good he tastes…"

"Stronger than me? I can squash him with just my finger!" The man started to become angry.

"A finger? You can squash him with just a finger?"

"Perhaps two fingers!" The male said angrily.

He stared at Garen in rage as he planned when he wanted to teach Garen a lesson to let him know that there were much stronger people above him.

Chapter 392: Meet Again 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Suddenly, Garen looked the bottom of the mountain valley.

His eyes were glowing red and blood was about to flow out from his triangular birthmark.

From afar, the white armored leader felt a shiver up her spine.

"Damn it!" He scolded.

"Did this kid just spot us? The Stealth effect from the Light Tree should be flawless." The female leader felt skeptical.

"It shouldn’t be possible. Although he’s a form four, he is too inexperienced and shouldn’t be able to master everything. It’s impossible for him to notice us… Fuck! You can’t be serious…" As the male leader hadn’t finished his sentence, he saw Garen pointing his fingers towards him.

In an instant, a huge columns of black fog came out from Garen’s body and morphed into a giant black cloud crow.

Kaw Kaw!!

The Black Crow spread its wings. Its forty meter wings created huge vortices that were directed straight towards them that brought along with it the black fog.

The male leader’s face turned pale as he knew that Garen had indeed noticed them. Through the black fog, he could faintly see Garen’s mouth moving.

"Looking forward… to meet… Officially."

"Fuck me… This fellow is this strong?!!"

Before the male leader could finish his sentence, he saw a giant black crow flying towards him, drawing a clear line of black lines in the middle of the sky.

Kaboom!!!

The whole red fern forest was covered in black fog. The tip of the mountain which spanned a few hundred meters was bent over by the impact and started to slide down to the other side.

Boom!!

Huge boulders rolled downwards, disturbing huge amounts of dust and pebbles as they made their descent.

Garen wasn’t trying to provoke them when he sent the black crow towards them. He wanted them to pay the price for peeping at them for such a long time.

"Let’s go." He turned around and walked towards the entrance of the mountain valley.

"Why did you hit that mountain?" Windling couldn’t understand his actions.

"I was bored."

"Fuck you!" Windling looked at the peak of the mountain, as he left together with Garen, none the wiser.

***************

"Cough cough… cough!!" Within the broken summit, a group of burning green flames covered the white armored men, who were smack in the middle of ground zero.

The male leader’s face was caked with dust as he tried his best to cough them out from his throat.

"Even the Light tree couldn’t defend it, and I had to activate my totem light. Fuck me!"

"You deserve it!" The female leader said so as if she was completely fine. "You have underestimated this handsome boy so you have to pay the price."

The remaining white armored men were completely silent. Those who were caught in it quickly got themselves up without any change in their expression, as if they were used to this.

"What are the old fools from the society thinking! This crazy fellow is only in his early twenties! And they pushed him to the Royal Alliance." The male leader was scolding in rage. "Are you sure he noticed us?"

"He most likely didn’t see us but felt our presence." The female leader tensed up and didn’t dare to joke any further. "We may have gone too far this time. To be honest, that is most likely a warning from him. If we were to really go against him, what are the chances do you think we can win against him?"

The male leader deactivated his green flame and recovered his composure.

"He definitely has something up in his sleeves. The Eight Cloud Crow. The Cloud Crow is most likely his sleight of hand, and the rumored Eight heads have yet to be presented in front of us. Rumor has it that his eight head is used in close combat and his cloud crows are used for long range battles. However, as a strong character, he definitely has more than one or two trump cards. I am sure, just from his gaze! He definitely has a huge trump card that he has yet to reveal to the world. With that confidence, he is definitely on par with the old fellows in the Society."

He had stopped calling Garen fellow and started using his name as a proper word.

The female leader knew that this meant that he had obtained his respect. To be able to notice them when they were under the protection of the Light Tree, this meant that he was qualified to be in the middle class of form four. As partners of countless of years, these both of them understood one another very well.

"Next up…"

"With Emin around, we better not provoke him. That fellow has already provoked the Obscuro Society and those monsters from the Black Sky will definitely go after him. We will let them fight against each other and we will just expand our territory in the dark." The male leader said.

"The Black Sky…" The female leader sighed as she heard this term. "They were once the strongest academy in the Tactic world. I didn’t expect them to form the Obscuro Society. What are they trying to achieve?"

"Who knows. The academy, nobles, royals and even those immortals had their own plans. They are the ones who control the board, we are merely the slightly stronger pieces." The male leader explained hopelessly.

"Don’t say that or else your father may be angry if he finds it. To be called an immortal by his own son…"

"Fuck him. The society is willing to send out only the both of us. Although they have a lot of trump cards up their sleeves, they never really dared to use them at all. In the end they will only rely on us. I will stop my involvement if they piss me off!"

The female leader covered her mouth as she laughed.

**************

Outside of the Mountain Valley, two blobs of black fog passed through the green field at an incredible speed.

The scorching hot golden sunlight could barely penetrated the black fog, and two human figures could be seen covered within it.

The white clouds passed them by and the strong winds blew against their oval shaped totem lights.

Windling placed his hands on his head, as if he was sitting on a sofa within the black mist as he looked at Garen, who is at the front, with much boredom.

"Boss, is it true that that old man is your teacher? How can your teacher be so weak? Are you the legendary weird kid who learnt everything himself?"

The guy’s face had become really thick as he could call out someone who was younger than him his boss without any change in facial expression.

Garen ignored him as he knew that he possessed no threat to him after interacting with him for so long. He was a man who would complained if he had nothing to do.

"It’s unforgivable that your junior would use the pity tactic to attack you." He was slightly unsatisfied. "What a pity. I really wanted that Life’s Dew since it’s an item that can make me live longer… If only I could get it on my hands and do some research on it… for just a little while."

He felt even more bored as Garen didn’t even respond to him.

"Where are we going next?’

"We will go for some raiding, so we’re going to the mission’s location now." Garen replied coldly.

"Where’s our objective? Is it that mission from the Headquarters director?" Windling was surprised.

He sighed as he saw Garen ignoring him, suggesting that it was what they were going to next.

"Oh my god! Why do we constantly go into these dangerous places… I feel like I’ve fought more battles than I have for the past ten years within these few days! Aren’t we looking for trouble?"

As he droned through the magic mirror, Garen was too lazy to respond to him, choosing to arrange his thoughts instead.

This accidental encounter with his teacher had raised a problem that he had never thought about before.

His current stance had been determined. He could only be with the Royal Alliance, but the Royal Alliance would eventually collapse. By then, both Terraflor Society and Obscuro Society would definitely not welcome him. What should he do then?

Judging from the current situation, the Royal Alliance was still the strongest player in the world, but its internal structure was rife with spies. The Royal Alliance would soon slowly crumble from the inside out. What seemed to be a powerful force was actually just a wooden house; one push could cause some real havoc.

This push would not be from the Obscuro Society or Terraflor Society, but the Royal Alliance themselves.

The assassination of the Kovitan’s kingdom was just a setback. There were still other incidents that could be a huge impact to them. The Royal Alliance would eventually anger the commoners and they would start a rebellion.

"Szz szz…" A sound could faintly be heard from the black box.

"This is the Kovitan’s Headquarters with an important news broadcast. This is the Kovitan’s Headquarters with an important news broadcast."

A clear young woman voice came out of the black box.

"Yesterday, Daniela has announced its intentions to build the largest commoner’s castle -- to be named the Heart of Life, for citizens seeking refuge. Interested parties are instructed to contact your respective branches. There will be specialised doctors guiding you throughout the moving process."

The voice repeated its announcement once more, then again in different languages.

As Garen listened to the voice, his face was filled with an inexplicable look.

"The Heart of Life… This is also one of the major turning points." He remembered the original history where a civil war broke out in Daniela after a massive genocide in the Heart of Life. This occurred after the assassination in the Kovitan Empire, and the same assassination happened in Daniela, where its most pampered princess was assassinated. Hence a major investigation became a massacre. The Obscuro Society took this opportunity to butt in and Daniela finally fell in March.

On the other hand, the Ender Kingdom was slightly different as its king itself was the strongest totem user. The King of the Ender Kingdom played himself into his own hands as he was searching for greater strength. In the end, he merged with the strongest Giant Divine Statue and attempted to become a God! As he tried to become the strongest player in the world, he had declared war against all its inhabitants.

It would be ideal to call the king of Ender Kingdom a madman who was after the pinnacle of strength instead of a Sovereign power. He betted the whole kingdom against the road to become a God. In the end the three heroes who had always supported him gave up on him.

The original history suggested that the Royal Alliance had killed themselves during the whole process.

Garen was lost deep in his thoughts.

"What if I could change the history of these major incidents?" He understood that these huge incidents were hard to twist as it was the combined wish of countless citizens. Even if he could delay the path of this history, he could only give some time to the Royal Alliance before their eventual collapse.

Then where would his escape route be?

At this point in time, Garen didn’t have the time to think of an impractical way to go back to his original world. If he could not ensure his own safety, then it would be pointless to consider anything else.

In this world, the mysterious phenomena of the Ancient Endor had started to become obvious as its number increased. The hidden secrets hidden here couldn’t be solved within such a short amount of time.

As the large amount of information kept flowing in his mind, Garen’s gaze started to become clearer and clearer.

"The strongest player in this history is the Hellgate of the Obscuro Society. Once they wake up from hibernation, they would soon surpass the Royal Alliance. Since I have already made an enemy out of the Obscuro Society, I would need to achieve the hellgate’s level if I want to survive and uncover the secret in the future… This is the first thing I should be doing.

Secondly, I need to find the real reason why I transmigrated to this world. The legendary Tactics most likely exist. As this world is changing its pace, perhaps I could find out some hidden secret from within."

Chapter 393: Lost 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the evening, only half the pale golden sun remained hanging above the horizon, scattering light with only a hint of warmth.

In a small territory between Kovistan and Ender.

Two clouds of black mist flew across the plains, going across the plains, and entering a mud-yellow mountain region.

This piece of mountain land had bright yellow sand, and there was the occasional blackened tree, dry and leafless, scattered all across the mountain.

In some places, there were even white bones and half-rotten corpses to be seen. Most of these were from aberrated animals, but there were humans as well.

Small flocks of black scavenger birds were gathered together, pecking away at their food.

Garen looked down, and could even see some people with black skin, all dark, skinny, and only wearing a few rags, crouching by the corpses and greedily eating the rotting meat by the handful.

As though sensing his gaze, the person underneath raised his head, revealing a rotting black face.

There were only black holes in his eye sockets, tiny black bugs crawled in and out of his nostrils, and his mouth no longer looked like that of a human. His entire chin and lips were utterly gone, his creepy white teeth directly exposed to the air.

This person didn’t have much flesh left on their bones, and even the bones inside were vaguely visible. There were many wounds that hadn’t healed yet on his body, so his black innards could be seen even from outside.

"That person is still alive?" Garen was slightly shocked.

"What?" Windling glanced over curiously, following Garen’s gaze to look down, and was instantly also taken aback. "It seems to be a person, fly lower."

The two black mists slowly descended, hovering about a dozen meters over this group of scavengers.

By then, Windling had also clearly seen the face of the person beneath them. He took a sharp intake of cold breath.

"What is that?! A new Aberration?!"

"I’m afraid not…" Garen’s expression was solemn. "Let’s go on and see."

The two of them were enveloped by the black mist, and continued flying ahead.

Soon enough, a small human village appeared on the ground ahead of them. Some of the mud-yellow mud houses had collapsed, while others were barely standing, damaged beyond repair. It was all quiet in the village, not a single soul in sight.

Looking down from mid-air, the whole village was like a mud-yellow round biscuit, it was just that it was covered with holes and gaps.

Before long, the two discovered yet another black and skinny person on the right side of the village. This person was also crouching in the middle of a heap of rotting flesh, chewing greedily.

This heap of rotting flesh was actually also a human corpse. It was a human man, and his entire abdomen had been cleared out, the organs inside covered with a greenish-white fluff of mould. Buzzing flies pranced constantly around the corpse.

"Let’s go down and take a look," Garen said, his voice low.

Windling nodded too. Both of them were feeling rather low and solemn right now, the situation seemed to be going out of control. Both of them were thinking of a terrifying possibility.

The two clouds of black mist descended slowly, landing on the ground behind the dark and skinny person. The most scattered, quickly returning to the pocketwatch in Garen’s hand.

The two of them watched that humanoid figure more than ten meters away, quietly.

This person looked as though he was severely dehydrated, his skin just like old, wrinkled and worn cloth. Some parts had fallen off in chunks, and was connected to the body by just a strand, whereas others were just full of holes, like a worn sackcloth, so that the black, dried-up muscles and tissues could be seen through the holes.

As though he had smelled something, the person suddenly stopped in the middle of chewing, and slowly turned around. A pair of utterly lightless eyes were staring intently at the two behind him.

Hiss…

He emitted a strange sound, taking in a breath, as though trying hard to smell something.

"You’re still alive?" Windling yelled loudly. He quickly repeated the question in many different languages.

Rawr!!

Suddenly, the other person opened his arms wide, flailing them as he pounced at Windling. He moved unnaturally fast, as though he had springs fastened to the bottom of his feet, and he had practically bounced there in one leap. He opened his mouth wide, revealing sharp white teeth, his gaze greedy and naked. As though in his eyes, Windling was the most delicious dish of food.

Seeing how mindless the other party acted, Windling frowned slightly, raised his hand and pointed.

Tree roots and wispy yellow roots shot out of the ground, entangling themselves around this person in a moment, and tripping him to the ground.

With a whoomph, the person continued struggling on the ground, hands clawing and crawling madly on the ground, eyes fixed dead on Windling, as though on the verge of insanity.

But the roots at his legs continued to extend, and quickly reached his waist, securing him tightly to the spot.

"Forget it, let’s go, this person isn’t human anymore." Garen said softly behind him.

Windling glanced at the figure on the ground.

"I have a bad feeling about this."

"Me too." Garen turned around and released the black mist, "Just up ahead is the capital of this country, if we want to know what on earth happened here, we should be able to find some survivors in the capital, and maybe then we’ll have some idea."

The two of them furled up the black mist again, and advanced at high speed forward.

Under them, on the surface of the ground, more and more of those figures appeared. Some were all black, others were all red. Some chased madly, some were sprawled on the ground chomping on rotting flesh, and there were also some that kept repeating certain movements.

There were more and more of these people, they gathered in denser numbers.

The two of them flashed past through the sky, both their hearts sinking.

Soon enough, within an hour, their current destination appeared before them, Veivar. The capital city of this country.

The city wasn’t large, spread on the ground like a large yellow biscuit.

It was completely surrounded by a tall yellow mud wall, but the inside was empty, and unnaturally quiet. Looking down from above, the mud yellow buildings, some tall and some short, were scattered about, but mostly whole. The streets were strangely quiet, without a single soul in sight.

The two of them slowly lowered their altitude, and the city beneath them became larger, wider.

The whole city was unnaturally huge, and from midair, they could see that the whole place was divided into four parts, and each part was divided into four more. There were sixteen areas in total, and each area was filled densely with more than a hundred buildings, of all heights and sizes.

The two of them landed in a small area, directly on top of a house.

Compared to this whole area, the two of them write like two little ants in a bathtub, completely inconspicuous.

Garen and Windling stood steadily on the edge of the roof, looking down. The streets beneath them were covered with abandoned heaps of rubbish, some already blackening and unidentifiable. Some seemed to be large piles of food and clothes in bags.

But these weren't the conspicuous, the most obvious was the blood red words written all over the building walls, their meaning unknown.

Garen glanced at Windling, who frowned and shook his head.

"It's not the language from around here, neither does it look like any country's language.I'd rather believe it's an unconscious scribble."

Garen frowned slightly as well.

The blood red graffiti was everywhere, on the walls, on the roads, on some carriages waylaid by the roadside, on the street lamps. They were practically everywhere.

These words were scrawled and messy, looking a lot like some words, though occasionally they had some figures like curves or circles.

Garen tugged at his collar, pressing the little box on his collar.

"Is there anyone here from the departments? If yes, reply immediately."

Beside him, Windling glanced over as well, seeing if there was anyone else here.

Soon enough, the black box began emitting a clattering sound. And then there was a man's voice, barely suppressing his joyful surprise.

"Phew… phew… I’m the leader here, Chavanna, could you… could you be Lord Eight Headed Cloud Crow?!" His voice was very small and very rushed, as though he was purposely guarding against something.

"I am Cloud Crow, how’s the situation now, how did this city become like this? Where are you now?" Garen asked a string of questions.

"Please come over, we’ll explain to you in person once we meet." The person on the other end of the box laughed bitterly. "Our location is… Ah!!!"

Suddenly there was a scream from the other side of the box, it sounded like that of a woman.

"Dammit!""Kill ‘em! Use tactics!!"

"Leo!!""Chavanna! Save me!"

And there was a flurry of noise, a smacking sound from the box, as though it had fallen to the ground.

"Hello?!" Garen yelled hurriedly.

No more voices came from the box. There was only silence.

Garen patted the box, his expression unhappy.

"Is there anyone left on the public channel? All department members, reply immediately if you can hear this question! Now!!"

After changing the box to the public channel, it was still completely silent.

It was starting to grow dark. A cold breeze blew past, lightly furling some thin wooden planks on the roof.

The chattering sound came from the box again, as though there was vaguely a noise of chaos.

Bzz…

The noise got louder and louder, larger and larger, until it was almost piercing to the ear.

Smack!

Garen closed the black box, and glanced at Windling next to him. Windling was also more serious than he had ever been.

"Looks like the situation is kinda bad," Windling said softly. "Something not quite right seemed to have happened in this country. It’s not as we guessed, that it was simply an infection of people that caused Aberration."

Garen nodded.

"The situation now is that we first have to find the people that arrived here before us, where are they?"

"When I was at Black Sky before, I had come across this phenomena. Although I only saw it in the information, it’s very similar to our situation now. I’ll check again and tell you. This is a homemade compass with a pointer, let’s first ascertain where we are and the strength of the earth’s magnetic field here." Windling took a small white round plate from his waist pouch, there was a silver circle embedded in it.

He crouched down, and put the plate upside down on the ground.

After waiting for a few seconds, he picked up the plate again.

Just then, a clear white circle appeared on the ground, some of the fine dust in the circle quickly lining up into a pointer needle made of dust. It even had some miniscule carvings on it.

Windling carefully checked the needle on the ground. "No, the magnetic field here shouldn’t be like this. We’ve walked several thousand kilometers to reach here, this direction…"

Suddenly, in the circle of the ground, a new needle formed.

Windling was slightly surprised.

Soon, the third needle appeared as well, the fourth, the fifth, the sixth!

A breeze blew past, and all the needles scattered and vanished.

Windling was stunned by the sight.

"What’s the matter?" Garen had no idea what he was thinking.

"I used our departure point as a pole, and set it as the departure point. I should be able to tell you how far we’ve gone, and which direction we are in relation to the points. But now, it indicates…" Windling swallowed, rather at a loss for words.

"What does it indicate?" Garen frowned.

"It says that we haven’t gone a thousand kilometers away from where we started…" Windling said somewhat guiltily.

Chapter 394: Lost 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Is there a problem with your method?"

"Impossible! This method was used in many unique locations and circumstances, it can prevent most interference. There can't be a problem!" Windling retorted immediately.

Garen fell silent as well. Frowning, he looked around himself. This was the tallest building in the vicinity, so they had a good vantage point to see how everything is going nearby.

There was nobody in this whole part of the city, not a soul in sight. It was utterly quiet.

"There were so many Aberrated people outside the city, so why can't we find anything at all in here?" Garen said softly.

"Shall we go down and check?" Windling glanced at Garen. I suspect this isn't where we wanted to go, Veivar."

"Under these circumstances, the best method is to find the sign of a famous shop, or post on message boards and the like." Garen nodded.

He looked around his surroundings, and quickly locked onto a target, releasing two Black clouds that enveloped the two of them once more and flew downwards.

Flying in mid-air, the buildings next to them were more than ten stories tall, the windows all pitch black like many dead and quiet empty holes, emitting a chilly cold.

The two of them landed soundly on the corner of the street, in front of an announcement wall.

On the mud-yellow wall, there were some torn newspapers and notices. Some had mostly fallen off, some were still considered whole, while others were covered with red graffiti.

The two of them split up to survey the notices.

"Found it!" Windling tore a small piece of newspaper from the wall. He began reading the words on it out loud.

"Gudan City, modified file number twenty-three, could all the infected please go to the nearest hospital at your soonest convenience to join the headcount, and receive a free vaccination. For those specially infected… Most of the back part is missing." Windling raised his head. "Gudan City? I've heard of the city before, it's the biggest and most prosperous city in this country, even bigger than the capital."

"Where is it, roughly?" Garen asked in a low voice.

"It's on our way. No, wait, I calculated our speed, there’s no way we only flew such a short distance after so long." Windling was confused.

"Be it Veivar or this Gudan City, they're both large cities that belong to this Nevis Empire. After the riot last time, how has the situation been in this country?"

Windling shook his head.

"I never heard about anyone appearing from this country. After the riots, everyone's focus went to the larger countries. Who would give a damn about these small countries? Even less so for a tiny territory like Nevis, where it's basically a country within a country. What do we do now?"

"We’ll check around this place for a bit, and find out exactly what had happened here," Garen replied calmly.

The sky had already gone utterly dark.

Everything around them was somewhat dim, and unclear.

Windling took out two flints from his waist pouch and a small assemblable torch.

Once he put the tip of the torch onto a wooden bat, it became a small and simple torch.

"This torch is a specialty only I have, it can burn for five hours at once, and that’s the minimum! And the materials are easier to find too, so it’s very convenient," Windling said somewhat proudly.

He started knocking the two flint stones together.

Psst-psst… psst-psst…

"Eh? Why isn’t it lighting up?" He picked up the flints to check, somewhat curiously.

"Let me try." Garen took a match from his pouch.

Psst!

The match brushed past the striking surface, and didn’t release any sparks whatsoever.

"Eh?" Garen was slightly surprised. "Did it get damp?"

"I know an illumination tactic, I can illuminate temporarily for ten minutes." Windling was also beginning to sense something amiss.

The surroundings were getting darker and darker, until they couldn’t see any slits in the clouds at all. The dark clouds grew thicker. There was no moon, no stars. It was as though the whole city was slowly being swallowed by the darkness.

Windling acted quickly, a small white light appearing on the tip of his finger as he quickly drew out simple tactic gestures in the air.

Psst!

After a light sound, the glyphs scattered in the air.

"Something’s not right! I can’t use the illumination tactic!" Windling’s voice increased by eight degrees, as he tried desperately again to make it work.

Garen noticed something was wrong too. The surroundings were getting darker and darker, and now they couldn’t light a flame for illumination. This didn’t seem like a coincidence.

Windling was still unable to make a light, be it with totems or an actual flame, neither could light up anything.

"This place doesn’t seem to allow any light," Garen said lowly. "Let’s get out of here first!"

"Okay!" Windling felt something was off too.

The two of them were wrapped in the black mist, and they took off into rapid flight, flying towards the outskirts of the city.

Before the whole city turned pitch black, the two of them quickly exited the city wall perimeters.

Psst!!

Windling kept repeating the gestures for the illumination tactic, and as soon as they left the city, the illumination gestures he carved out instantly shone with a white light.

"It worked!!"

A ball of light was suspended quietly in the air between the two of them.

"One of my totems is a fire elemental, so I can use it for illumination. I just don’t know why, we can’t light anything inside the city."

Garen didn’t reply, and just stared dazedly towards the direction of Gudan City, where they had just come from.

Windling turned around to look, shocked.

The whole city area was completely empty, it was practically a stretch of deserted plains. There weren’t any buildings or city walls there, nothing at all!

Only a few lonely small trees were planted there, looking as though they could die of dehydration at any time.

"Where’s Gudan City?" Windling’s expression was pure shock.

"I don’t know…" Garen shook his head slowly. He took in a deep breath. "Could it be that everything we saw just now was an illusion?"

"Impossible!" Windling shook his head determinedly. "Let’s look around," he suggested directly.

Garen nodded.

Wrapped in the black mist, they began to patrol the area.

The moon and stars were visible in the sky once more, the faint light shining down and scattering onto this piece of ground. There were no cities, no buildings, and even those Aberrated people from before were nowhere to be seen.

As though everything they had seen in the daytime was an illusion.

The two of them wouldn't give up, so they turned around and searched again. All the Aberrated people they had seen in the daytime were all vanished, not a single one remaining.

Garen actually already had a hypothesis in mind.

Unlike Windling, he had experienced the paranormal phenomena of Grindor twice, and after this strange encounter, he quickly found a possible counterpart from the Grindor legends.

Ghost City, a strange city from Grindor legend.

Anyone could enter and leave in the daytime, but once it got to the night, the city would disappear completely, entering an unknown darkness. If anyone didn't manage to leave before the darkness fell, they would remain forever in the city. Nobody knew where they went, nobody knew where the Ghost City came from. The next day, the Ghost City would remain as empty as ever, still as a grave.

According to legends, after figuring out how dangerous the Ghost City was, the aging hero Morgster brought the Lost Chain given to him by his wife, Starry Night Queen. After entering the Ghost City, he never came back out. That was also the ending point for his adventurous life. The great hero, who could even stand up against the Earth Mother’s five sons, finally fell in this Ghost City, full of the unknown. And the Ghost City quickly disappeared as well, leaving behind only a mysterious legend.

Garen thought back to this legend, feeling vaguely grateful. Thank goodness the two of them were decisive enough, and quickly left Gudan City before the light disappeared completely. If even a deified hero couldn’t leave Ghost City, it was practically the most mysterious and dangerous place to be. If they really got involved, who knew what would happen.

"It’s another black copper phenomenon…" Windling looked down at the empty space beneath them, his gaze complicated as he said, "These strange phenomena caused by the black copper, we call them black copper phenomena. No one knows which direction this world will go in the end. From the moment black copper was discovered, this world was destined to change."

"Black copper…" Garen was thoughtful.

"What do we do now?" Windling splayed his hands, indicating that he was completely at a dead end.

After a moment’s musing.

"Continue with our original quest, then. Although we don’t know why we’ve only made such little progress, things still need to be done." Garen replied.

After a pause, he finally took one last glance at the empty space where Gudan City had been.

"Perhaps once everything is over, we might still come back here."

"Well, I don’t wanna come back." Windling continued immediately. "If you wanna come back, you do it yourself. You can tell just with one look that this place is more than dangerous."

Garen was too lazy to reply.

The two clouds of black mist surrounded them, and they flew at high speeds in their original direction.

*********************

Amidst some white mountains, far away from Garen and Windling.

Somewhere among the snow-tipped mountains.

On the white mountain slopes, on the white snowy ground, there were large black trees scattered sparsely, some in a straight line, others standing alone. Large sharp mountain rocks created a broken black surface amidst the snow.

The black trees and white snow mingled, as though the peak here only had two monochromatic colors.

The black rocks and soil, the black cedars and weeds, were embedded in the white snow. As though the pure white wool carpet was splashed with black mud.

Under the large swathes of white snow, in a gap between the layers of snow, a young woman dressed all in white was lying with her eyes slightly closed, as though she was in a state of hibernation.

The woman was hugging a dark golden round wristband in her arms, many black tactic glyphs carved densely into the bracelet. These glyphs looked independent, but some were strangely linked up, like a pitch black bracelet-shaped snake. The snake’s eyes were two embedded green diamond shards, emitting an eerie green light.

Avici hadn’t eaten for four days, and was hanging on with solely the little bit of pure water she carried around with her.

She hid under the snow, restraining all her body’s aura, even slowing her heartbeat down to the barest minimum. This was to reduce the smell of her body and her metabolism, to bring all her living processes as low as they could go.

As an elite researcher with the Geometry Service, her results in the wilderness survival training class were the best. She just had to send this heirloom into the hands of the receiving teacher from the Geometry Service, and her quest would be complete.

As for when the receiving teacher would arrive, she had no clue.

What she did know now was that the people from Black Sky were still looking for her on the surface. Or perhaps there were other desperadoes trying their luck, also on the lookout for her. Even the Secret Service, another one of the three departments, were part of the search party.

If the National Service weren’t so low on manpower, there would be another batch of people searching for Avici.

Chapter 395: See the End 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

She didn’t know what the situation was like outside, were there still so many people outside? Are those damned black dogs still constantly sniffing for her trace on the snow? Wouldn’t that Robina from Black Sky have gotten more and more helpers?

Avici’s mind was half awake and half asleep.

She could only wait, leaving fate up to God. If the people from the Geometry Service didn’t find her before the enemy did, then what awaited her may be a fate even crueler than death.

*****************

Several days later…

In the sky above the snowy peaks, several pitch black flying birds kept darting around, patrolling the scene beneath them. The birds were as big as sparrows, but eerily, they had two front limbs like scythes, like a sharp tweezer.

They swam through the savage winds soundlessly, as though they were barely affected by the force of the wind at all.

On the edge of an ice cliff at the snowy peak, there were several figures in black standing.

They gathered together in a circle, with a large black metal pot between them, an emerald green potion rippling inside.

Strangely, scenes of the geography and scenery around the snowy peaks appeared on the surface of the potion, as though it was a green sandbox.

The lay of the land on the surface even kept changing minutely, it was unbelievably realistic[1], as though they were looking down from above in the sky.

"The people from the department are coming. Swanke, you still can’t find ‘em?" A person in black asked softly, speaking in accented Enderian, as though he wasn’t very familiar with it.

"I searched the whole mountains, but I still can’t find a trace of that fellow, those are some decent hiding skills." The other man in black shook his head and replied, "What about the others? A lot of people seemed to have come since then, are they trying to muddle our eyes or take advantage of the situation?"

"They’re probably adventurers here to try their luck. There are monster herds everywhere here. To think they could break past the defense line and get in as well, we oughta be slightly more careful."

"Got it, inform Robina."

"Sure."

**************************

On another area in these snowy peaks, on the snowy white slope, there were many little dots scattered about. Some were red dots, some were black dots, but most were little white dots.

These dots were so many delicate little totems, rabbits, foxes, squirrels, mice… There were all sorts of totems.

They ran about and darted into holes everywhere, as though they were constantly searching for something.

There was a white flying squirrel sprawled on a black-robed man’s shoulder, as he walked on the snowy ground with one leg sinking deeper into the snow than the other. A thick white smoke was breathed out of his mouth, and his feet made clear crunching sounds as they stepped into the snow, leaving deep footprints.

Suddenly he stopped in his tracks, and cast his eye about his surroundings, vaguely seeing the figures of adventurers in the distance amidst the forest of cedar trees.

"Damned stink beetles!" He cursed under his breath, these adventurers were all desperadoes who had survived different places, and they were always unreliable with questionable courage. But after the batch of new adventurers joined in, the situation became slightly complicated.

These new adventurers were led by a man called Bloodhand, he was cunning and crafty, and decently powerful. He also seemed to have excellent hiding skills, avoiding a direct confrontation with their Black Sky.

But these people obviously hadn’t found that little fellow either. Otherwise, they wouldn’t be following them so closely.

The man in black relaxed a little.

Suddenly he stopped his steps slightly, his right hand reaching into his pocket, like he was pressing something. He closed his eyes, as though listening to something.

Abruptly, he raised his head to look at the sky, his expression slowly changing.

He began to retreat, step by step.

"Uh-oh… This is trouble… Celine, inform everyone, retreat!"

"What’s the matter?" A woman’s voice came from his pocket.

"I think it’s the people from the Geometry Service, they’re here." The man in black looked up at the sky in front of him, and three red dots were flying towards them rapidly.

The red dots grew larger and larger, clearer and clearer.

After clearly seeing the new arrival’s face, the man in black took a sharp intake of breath.

"Everyone! Retreat retreat retreat!! It’s Hellfire!! If you can’t make it in time, hide!"

The man in black’s retreating footsteps grew faster and more panicked. As though he was drawing out a clear black line in the snow. The footsteps under his feet kept forming a line, retreating towards the distance behind him.

Psst-psst!

The three red dots instantly reached the position right above the place where the man in black had been standing.

It was three men and women in red robes, two men and one woman, led by a middle-aged man with red hair.

There was a slight killing intent between his eyes, his gaze scanning the traces left beneath him.

"You dare touch the people from our Geometry Service! Looks like it’s been too long since we walked the earth, and some people have forgotten the scars from back then."

"Teacher[2], we should look for Junior Sister first," the other woman in red said in a low voice.

The middle-aged man nodded, and then looked at the young man.

The latter nodded.

"My little friends are already determining the situation. The ones searching here are the adventurers and Obscuro, the noteworthy ones are Bloodhead and the five-man Ring of Gluttony team from Obscuro. Also, I found the other juniors who had lost contact with Avici. They were hiding underneath a snow hill, and haven’t eaten any cooked food for three days."

Bam!

A ball of crimson flames exploded from the middle-aged man’s hand.

"Those damned, harebrained brats!" He seemed to be squeezing the words out of his clenched teeth. "You guys go receive those poor little things."

"Then Teacher, you…"

"Of course I’ll show those idiots with a death wish what pain tastes like! Sometimes death is a lot kinder than living…" The middle-aged man said, his expression cold.

Balls of flames burned in mid-air, surrounding the middle-aged man inside.

He was just about to leave, and take his revenge on those enemies who had dared to defile the honor of his department.

Suddenly his eyes narrowed, looking directly at the trees to his left.

"Come out!" he roared in a low voice.

From among the cedar forest, two mysterious figures, completely black, walked out slowly.

The man in front pulled away his hood, revealing a head of golden hair, cascading over his shoulder. His face was handsome, his skin fair. The most eye-catching part, however, were the three marks like cinnabar dots between his brows.

"The Secret Service?"

"Hellfire?"

The two of them spoke at the same time.

The other person’s expression was relaxed and carefree, as though he had just come out for a stroll after dinner.

"You guys only know how to hide in the cracks, so why are you here now too? Don’t tell me you want the Heirloom of Greed too?" Hellfire said coldly. He had no good feelings for the Secret Service at all.

Unlike the National Service and the Geometry Service, the inner workings of the Secret Service were bloody and cruel, full of cunning and deceit. Although they were all part of the three departments. But the Secret Service’s feelers reached everywhere, and their information network was all over the place, completely unpredictable.

Compared to those adorable students in the Geometry Service, Hellfire began to hate those shadow hounds, without any quality of nobility, more and more. They were like wild wolves who had caught the scent of rotting flesh, their traces could be seen everywhere.

It wasn’t just him, the two people next to him also had expressions of wariness. Staring hard at the golden-haired man who had just shown up.

"It’s the Eight Headed Cloud Crow Garen. A noble from Kovistan. He’s very strong." The young man in red moved his lips slightly, reducing his voice so only Hellfire could hear him.

Hellfire nodded almost imperceptibly.

"We would never give you guys the heirloom!" He yelled loudly at the people opposite. "We sacrificed so much, and it’s already in our hands! This is the fruit of our Geometry."

Garen’s expression didn’t change.

"The quest I accepted was to retrieve the heirloom, it doesn’t concern me whose hands the item is in." He said calmly, as though everything was only natural.

Hellfire’s eyes reddened, and he immediately repressed his anger.

"Very well, we’ll settle the conflicts outside first, and then I’ll come experience Your Excellency’s techniques."

"That was my intention as well." Garen slowly retreated, and disappeared into the cedar forest together with the other person.

Seeing the other party retreat, Hellfire’s expression grew more displeased.

"Teacher, you don’t need to worry. At least before we settle all the outsider enemies, the Secret Service won’t openly declare war on us." The young man in red said softly, "I just received the news, Obscuro is sending more reinforcements here. Other than the Ring of Gluttony, there’s also the Ring of Greed, and the Ring of Wrath. And according to some of our newest intel, some people from Terraflor are here too."

"Terraflor?" Hellfire’s emotions began to calm down slowly. "Forget them, first go figure out what Obscuro’s newly-founded Rings of Evil are made of! I’d like to see, who gave them the guts to challenge the honor of the Geometry Service!!"

"Teacher, you’re not thinking of fooling around again, are you…" The red-robed woman said hurriedly.

"Relax." Hellfire raised his hand, indicating that she didn’t need to worry.

He looked at the direction Garen and the other had disappeared to, and raised his hand abruptly.

Psst!

A line of fire shot from his hand, flying straight into the white pine forest before vanishing.

************

In the pine forest.

Garen looked at the group of people in white bowing politely at him, these people in white all looked a mess, their expressions exhausted, but they seemed to be very excited about his arrival.

"So you’re saying we lost quite a few people from the Secret Service in this operation?"

"Yes." The leader of the people in white lowered his head and said guiltily. "Lord Cloud Crow, Obscuro’s men would want nothing more than to turn the snowy peaks upside down, they come at any of us Secret Service members with the intention to kill! We couldn’t avoid them completely either."

Garen touched his chin, thinking wordlessly.

"Boss, it must have been because you were a burden and held them back."

Windling threw in a few jibes from the side.

How many of Obscuro’s people had the two of them killed outside? General-level, Field-level, this hit-and-run method caused many of Obscuro’s plans to fail before they started, so of course they would be mad.

In fact, most of Garen’s reputation was built on casualties from Obscuro.

Looking at the messed-up subordinates from the Secret Service, Garen couldn’t help but shake his head slightly.

Suddenly there was a clear sound from behind. A line of fire shot through the pine forest, headed straight for Garen.

Pom!

Garen raised his hand and caught the flying fire thread, the flames stopping in his hands and revealing its true shape. It was a cube-shaped red jade, with inscriptions like glyphs and figures carved onto it.

Hellfire’s voice came straight from the red jade.

"Eight Headed Cloud Crow, you and I will split this snowy peak half-half. We’ll settle the matter of the heirloom internally after cleaning up here, what do you think?" His voice was strangely clear.

"Perfect for me. I want east."

"Then I’ll take west."

Translator’s notes:

The raws say ‘真是无比’, but I’m pretty sure it’s 真实无比.

Lit. 导师, so ‘master’ doesn’t work but ‘tutor’ or ‘coach’ sounds weird.

Chapter 396: See the End 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The voice instantly dimmed down.

Boom!!

Suddenly, a huge red cloud exploded from Hellfire’s direction.

The red cloud expanded first, and then quickly shrunk and was compressed, becoming a huge red bird more than thirty meters long.

"Those who dare defy we the Geometry Service, face the wrath of Hellfire!!" The enormous voice reverberated in the sky over the whole west side of the snowy peak.

Squeee!!

The red bird flapped its wings, screeching loudly.

Instantly, large swathes of red clouds starting emanating from its body, shooting away in all directions, like so many red threads, almost lifelike in the sky above the snowy peak.

It was as though these lines of fire had a mind of their own, searching everywhere for enemies who didn’t belong with the three departments.

Soon enough, there were irrepressible screams and shrieks of shock.

Every time these lines of fire touched anything living, they would be completely enveloped and ignited into flames, becoming so many torches of fire.

The sky above the snowy peak was mostly covered by the red clouds, like the fiery clouds of twilight!

"Hellfire Monchetto!! Don’t think we from Obscuro are afraid of you!!"

A furious old voice came from somewhere else.

Garen saw his subordinates from the Secret Service looking at him expectantly.

Although the three departments were forbidden from infighting, there was evidently some competition between them, and neither side wanted to lose to the other in terms of presence.

He smiled slightly, stretching out his right hand, the black pocket watch twined around his wrist hanging down.

Boom!!!

A large gust of black air rushed into the sky. It rapidly scattered into countless black cloud crows, flying into the air in flocks and making piercing squawks.

The large flocks of black crows rapidly scattered together with the black mist, quickly dominating the entire west side of the sky, forming a stark contrast against the bright red clouds in the east. One black and one red, the two sides were like two huge and tightly neighboring screens, neither giving way to the other.

"The Secret Service is clearing out here, if you don’t want to die then leave these snowy peaks!"

The Secret Service members at the side stared, mouths gaping.

The elite fighters from the Secret Service were never this showy and arrogant, to the point of challenging the enemy head-on.

The Secret Service dealt mainly with assassinations, and not a single one of them had been as open as Garen was being now, releasing his energy and letting the enemy see his exact location.

At first they thought Garen would lead them to secretly get rid of these damned pursuers. But now…

For some reason, though, this feeling wasn’t too bad either…

There were the flames of excitement in everyone’s eyes.

The sky full of black crows, a huge presence of power, this was all from their very own leader/ This was the legendary peak-level fighter, who had a title of his own!!

Just then, all of the people from the Secret Service had a new and fresh emotion, one they never felt before.

*****************

The huge red cloud bird in the distance looked towards the flocks of black crows, a hint of surprise in its eyes.

"Eight Headed Clouded Crow? I think I kinda like this guy now. To think the Secret Service has someone who likes to fight face-on as well."

"What an attitude."

Somewhere in the snow on the peaks, several people in black robes and red masks looked up to see the red clouds and black crows.

One of them had a hoarse voice underneath that mask.

"How pretty, I like huge scenes like this." One of the other voices was very gentle, like a rather young woman.

"Don’t bother with all that, hurry up with the arrangements, don’t delay the plan."

Another person reminded softly, with also a woman’s voice, but hers sounded deeper and raspier.

The three didn’t say any more, hurriedly walking towards a secret place amidst the snowy peaks.

Boom! Boom! Boom!!

Huge explosions kept coming from the area covered by the red clouds.

Some completely blackened survivors stumbled out under the protection of their totems, running down towards the foot of the hill. Some even had limbs blasted off. They didn’t even dare to turn around, running directly down the peak. Looks like there were several dozens of them.

In comparison, from the area covered by the black crows, there were only a handful of escapees. The rest vanished without a trace.

The squawking of the cloud crows was drowned in the sound of the explosions, until all that could be heard was the vague screaming from inside.

******************

In the following two days.

Garen and Hellfire used their respective large-scale attacks, clearing up most of the weaker guys around, and then they reined in their power again. The remaining groups were not people that could be easily destroyed by large-scale attacks.

These remaining groups had tactics that could gather everyone’s power, enough to hide and avoid the highly diluted spread of attacks.

Somewhere on the west side of the snowy peaks.

Several black lines blasted into the snowy ground in front of them.

Soon enough, the black lines threaded out, flying back into Garen’s hands.

Fresh and gory blood oozed slowly out of the snowy ground.

"How’s it like on Windling’s side?" Garen raised his leg and walked slowly ahead. This was how he had destroyed several hiding spots over these past few days.

"Lord Windling’s side has settled four hiding spots." There were two people following beside Garen, both subordinates from the Secret Service and in charge of the operation this time.

They were one man and one woman, both rather young. Looks like they were just raised to this position recently.

Garen nodded. "Let’s go to the next spot. These people won’t give up until the end."

"Yes, sir."

Both of them were vaguely excited. They were actually siblings, the older brother and his younger sister.

The man was Bell, and the woman was Belanie. They had joined the Secret Service together, because their home had been destroyed. In order to get revenge, they had no choice but to join the three departments, that fought the monsters and Obscuro.

And right now, they were full of sincere admiration and respect for Garen. This feeling of sweeping over everything was too awesome, they just bulldozed through, and killed every living thing that wasn’t on their side.

If they had this power as well, when their home was destroyed, when their country was destroyed… perhaps there wouldn’t have been so much tragedy…

...….

"Wait!! We surrender!! We’ll pay the price to pay for our lives!"

Several people in grey walked out of a huge black boulder, yelling loudly.

Psst-psst!

Two black threads went through them, piercing right through their chests and splattering fountains of blood onto the snowy ground.

"Next one!"

Garen walked over the bodies calmly, leaving behind a person in white to deal with the bodies. The one man and one woman from the Secret Service kept following behind him.

.....

In the pine forest, two people in white were looking at their surroundings in surprise.

"We had just discovered traces of the other parties here… sir…"

Garen raised his hand and stopped their report.

His gaze glanced instantly at the left of the pine forest.

"Fools!"

Psst!

A black crow turned into a black thread and shot out.

There was a distortion in the air, and a woman in white armor appeared out of mid-air.

A layer of white Totem Light appeared around the woman, but was instantly penetrated by the cloud crows.

"Have mercy!!" She yelled loudly.

Bang!

A circular, bloody hole was instantly opened up in the woman’s chest. She looked down blankly, staring at the bloody hole in her chest, before she fell to her knees with a whumph, and falling flat on her face.

"Sir, we just discovered a new hiding spot…" A person in white ran up to Garen and reported quietly in his ear.

After listening to the report, Garen didn’t even look at the woman’s corpse.

"Let’s go."

He turned around and walked down the direction they had come.

.....

Rawr!!

A huge black lion was running quickly in the snowy land. His speed was surprisingly fast, and covered over a hundred meters in the blink of an eye, sending a trail of white snow up in his wake.

There was a knight in black armor riding on the lion. He was panting, his face bloodless, and he turned around occasionally to glance behind him.

Behind him, a large flock of black could crows was chasing him rapidly. Black mist wrapped around Garen as he followed behind.

Looking at the escaping black lion in front, Garen raised his hand, ready to finish the opponent in one hit. Now, opponents who weren’t at least Spiritualized didn’t pose any threat to him at all, and were basically like ants to him.

Raising his right hand, the black mist slowly gathered into a black crow in his hands.

Suddenly, Garen’s movements stopped.

His whole body suddenly stopped on the spot, and he landed onto the ground. His eyes narrowed, his long golden hair flying slightly to the left.

"Come out, all of you."

Garen said calmly.

Clap-clap-clap-clap…

The sound of crisp clapping came from behind Garen.

With the sound of the clapping, five shadows in black robes and red masks slowly appeared around Garen at the same time.

Each of them was holding a purple crystal, a smidge of silver liquid shining inside.

"Garen Trejons, how long has it been since we met?" A familiar woman’s voice came from directly in front of Garen.

It was the two red-masked, black-robed people who walked out slowly, both women by the looks of their figures.

The one on the left took off her mask lightly, revealing a seductive and fair face, a black eyepatch over one of her eyes, with a head of short purple hair.

"Demetrius…" Garen immediately recognized the woman’s voice.

"Looks like, you’re doing pretty well as an illusionist, huh?" The other woman took her mask off as well, revealing a beautiful and delicate face. Her long hair was pitch black, woven into many cylindrical curls, making her look especially graceful and noble. Most obviously, there was a purple-black diamond pattern on her right cheek, like a short dagger, entwined with snakes and tree leaves.

"Nice to meet you, I’m Antherella. I am now the NO.1 Elemental General with Black Sky."

Garen’s heart gave a jolt.

******************

On the east side of the snowy peaks.

Boom!!

Hellfire waved his hand, his expression calm, as he blasted the snowy ground underneath him into a charred black, bloody water and fresh blood mixing together to form currents of water that were quickly frozen into red ice.

"Monnie… It’s been a while, you’re still as impatient as ever."

Suddenly, there was a deep man’s voice from behind him.

Hellfire suddenly stiffened, floating in mid-air.

This voice…

"I still remember, back then when I personally helped you edit your tactic formation design, you were still only as tall as my waist." The person behind him reminisced calmly.

Hellfire’s whole body was stiff as he stood, and he turned around with great difficulty. A silhouette made of countless black clouds floated behind him. The countless black clouds were still distorting and gathering, and even rapidly gathered into a body like that of flesh and blood.

That was a man who had a hole in each shoulder, and black chains going through those holes. The chains in his shoulders seemed to extend into the unknown, connecting to an unknown space. It was as though he was chained to the abyss.

"Teacher… God Cloud…" Hellfire squeezed out those words through an unbelievably dry throat.

Chapter 397: Ambush 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The snow filling the sky slowly scattered down. Like white cotton, softly and gently.

Amidst the snowy ground, the five people in black had Garen surrounded. The purple crystals in their hands were emitting a faint silver light.

The purple light slowly formed a semi-circular membrane of purple, slowly enveloping Garen in the center as they stretched to merge above the top of his head.

Garen raised his hand, but couldn’t move an inch. Before he had noticed it, many translucent silver strings had penetrated his whole body.

His arms, the backs of his hands, his shoulders, knees, all his joints were being yanked at by those silk threads.

The source of these silk threads was a black-haired woman in front of those people in black.

"Poison again…" The crimson mark on Garen’s brow looked like it was about to drip blood.

Antherella smiled lightly. "Honeysuckle poison, enough dosage to fatally kill a beast twice. Aren’t you already starting to feel weak, and isn’t your Totem Light already diminishing?"

Garen didn’t speak.

Antherella’s voice grew more gentle.

"Honeysuckle poison isn’t that powerful, but when mixed with the existing poison in your body, it becomes a brand new, more powerful, and even more stubborn poison."

"If I recall correctly, the strongest Elemental General among you Obscuro in the East Continent uses ice, right?" Garen said calmly.

Antherella’s expression flashed with a hint of unnaturalness. But she immediately recovered. "Ice, is it? That traitor has already been confined to a lightless prison, for revealing Society secrets and ruining the Marshall’s plan, acting out of order. That is his fate."

"In other words, you lucked into this NO.1 position, huh?" Garen’s lips curved, his expression contemptuous.

Antherella’s expression grew unfriendly.

"You’ll be our prisoner soon, and yet you speak insolently!"

Bzz!

Just then, the purple membrane of light finally closed up above his head, emitting a strange buzzing sound.

In the veil of light, looking from above, a silver needle appeared in the entire circle, turning slowly in the light veil.

Like a silver clock.

And Garen was locked in this clock, the silk threads around his body disappearing, The clock needle brushed past his body, looking illusory but vaguely taking a wisp of black air away from him.

"This is the heirloom, Primal Needle." Antherella laughed daintily, "Eight Headed Cloud Crow, this heirloom is activated by the combined power of five of Obscuro’s carefully chosen Elemental Generals, it’s not something the forgery in your hands can imitate."

"You really did luck into the number one position, don’t tell me you think you’ve won already?" Garen’s expression didn’t change.

"Are you saying I’m wrong?"

"I think I know now, why you’re still scared of ice to this day." Garen’s expression was contemptuous again.

Boom!!

Large clouds of black mist surged out of the pocket watch in his hand, about to gather into the form of a black crow.

But strangely, before the black crow could form, the silver needle brushed past it, and took away most of the black mist.

The silver needle was like a vacuum, rapidly absorbing most of the black mist.

Garen was shocked, and quickly pulled back the watch’s black mist, but he was still rather late by now, the watch looked slightly dimmer. This forgery heirloom had a constant amount of black mist inside, and could only be refilled using certain special methods, but now that so much has been absorbed away, the power of the pocket watch would have instantly fallen by a large chunk.

"Do you still think something that had come out of our hands like that would work?" Demetrius said coldly from the side.

"Do you think you can keep me contained just like this? How ignorant!" Garen’s expression was cold.

He raised his hand and pointed forward.

Rawr!!!

Two invisible dragon jaws rammed mercilessly into the purple membrane.

Crack…

The light membrane shook a little, but didn’t move.

Four dragon jaws rammed into the same direction again.

Bang! ...Bzzz…

The sound of the impact kept reverberating throughout the light barrier.

Garen’s expression didn’t change, and was about to bring in more dragon jaws. But he suddenly felt weaker.

"Don’t waste your strength, in order to capture you, we’ve set up large-scale tactic formations all over this area, almost a thousand meters in all. There are even about a hundred General-level and Field-level Obscuro members outside. With so many people working together, even you can’t possibly get away so easily. Now we just need to wait for our Commander to settle matters on the other side, and then come destroy you with his own hands!"

Garen’s expression was beginning to waver. The poison had taken away half of his dragon heads, and now there were so many people gathering their power in this tactic formation.

"One more time!"

A flame of fury was burning in his heart. A neon red light lit up on his brow.

The four dragon heads instantly appeared from the void, bringing with them the four other drastically weakened dragon heads, and the huge body of the Eight Headed Dragon was suddenly squeezed into the purple light barrier.

It climbed out of the void, as though about to burst the small purple membrane open at the seams.

Rawr!!

The Eight Headed Dragon raised its heads and roared, the huge sound spreading out in all directions, but it was reflected back in full upon hitting the purple membrane. Reverberating back and forth within the light membrane.

The whole light membrane began buzzing and vibrating intensely, emitting unnatural cracking sounds.

The five Elemental Generals were beginning to grow impatient, turning their gazes on Antherella.

Antherella’s expression changed slightly, throwing a glance at Demetrius’ direction beside her.

The latter immediately understood, and held a strangely black dagger in his hand, tossing it lightly towards Garen’s direction.

The dagger flew in a beautiful arc, spinning as it landed on the purple light barrier, and actually sank into the light in an instant, vanishing completely.

The light barrier had initially shown cracks, but now it stabilized rapidly.

But just then, the sound vibration in the light barrier had already become several crests and valleys of waves.

Just then, Garen sneered contemptuously, the red light on his brow growing brighter.

He bent his finger, and slowly flicked it against the light barrier.

Clang!!

This sound just happened to be on the highest wave crest.

Ker-chack… Bwah!

With a crisp sound, the whole light barrier collapsed and shattered, a red figure shooting out in an instant, headed straight for Antherella.

Garen’s eyes glowed with a crimson light, his left hand darting out straight like a snake, biting the opponent’s neck with unnatural speed!

Bzz!!!

A white Totem Light appeared around Antherella, and she had no time to react at all, rapidly retreating by instinct alone.

Psst!!!

Garen’s left hand pierced through her neck in an instant. The Totem Light couldn’t withstand that pierce at all, that bloody red light completely unstoppable, like a tragedy.

Just then, Antherella’s body actually began to disappear slowly, vanishing into nothing.

His attack didn’t hit, so Garen retreated hastily. He hit a tree beside him with a backhanded fist.

Ker-chak!!

The tree trunk exploded from the middle, countless wooden shards flying backwards like bullets.

Mmgh!

There was a groan from behind him.

The huge shadow of the huge Eight Headed Dragon appeared behind Garen again, opening its four jaws and biting towards the four Elemental Generals around him.

Strangely, the dragon jaws closed with a clatter, and had bitten down into nothing, not reaching the Elemental Generals at all.

"Illusionists…" Garen didn’t turn around, merely cocking his head slightly.

Behind him, a man in similar black robes was slowly appearing behind him. He was also wearing a red mask, but his hand was on his chest, as he coughed lowly. There were actually several wooden shards embedded in his chest.

The people around him looked at Garen in shock. He could break the purple light barrier with only his body, and even the wooden shards he broke out could injure the illusionist!!

Antherella imperceptibly took a slight step back. Looking at the blonde man standing in the center, there was a feeling of dread in her heart.

A small black bat appeared on her shoulder, soundlessly, completely unmoving as though it was dead.

"Second Form!"

She roared loudly and suddenly.

Instantly, the countless shards of purple light gathered in her hands, like the whirlpool in a purple ocean, sucking everything around her inside.

In the blink of an eye, there was a purple-black scimitar in Antherella’s hand, its blade embedded with countless thorns of purple crystal, while the sword’s handle was like a living thing, squirming constantly, as though it was four spiders tangled together in a hug.

"Demonic Blade Kunta!!" A general gasped from somewhere. But Antherella couldn’t bother with all this now, the moment the Demonic Blade appeared, and the purple light faded, she was shocked to see Garen’s face appear in front of her. His demonic and bloody left hand was about to touch her nose. No! That was not a hand! That was a sort of incomparably sharp claw, Antherella could even smell the blood and odor from it.

Without any thinking whatsoever, she swung the Demonic Blade hurriedly.

Psst!!

A circle of purple waves rapidly spread from the center, and it was everything slowed down.

The trees instantly became shards, and the rocks also became powder. The snowy ground, the black soil, everything instantly shattered into pieces.

The waves moved extremely quickly, not giving anyone any time to react.

But someone was even faster than that!

Garen somersaulted a few times in the air, the black light formation appearing for only an instant underneath his feet so he could use the momentum to land steadily on a shard of tree bark nearby.

As soon as he steadied his footing, and intense vibration of soundwaves spread out with him at the center.

Roar!!!

It was the Dragon Roar!

Demetrius and the others, who were about to give chase, suddenly felt their eyes blur, and were instantly shocked to see Garen appear before their eyes.

Bang-bang-bang!!

Three dull sounds, and the three Elemental Generals were instantly hit. They were sent flying far, and no one knew if they were dead or alive.

Demetrius was extremely shocked, and started retreating rapidly. But she saw Garen’s face appear in front of her again.

"Blackhorn!!" She yelled out of instinct.

A Black-horned Unicorn rushed out from behind her, going through her as though an illusion, and crashed towards Garen mercilessly.

Squee-eee!!

The Unicorn’s cry mingled with the sound of Garen’s claw tearing through the air.

Boom!!

A huge tremor spread out, and the Black-horned Unicorn cried out tragically, instantly becoming dots of black light that scattered and vanished.

Demetrius watched in despair as the red claw reached for her brow.

"No!!" Antherella’s scream of terror came from nearby, but it still seemed so, so very far away.

"Save me… Big Sister…" Demetrius wanted to speak, but couldn’t make a sound. In that instant, it was as though time was stretched and stretched, infinitely.

Chapter 398: Ambush 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Hmm?"

While midair, God Cloud single handedly carried the unconscious hellfire, his eyes pointed toward the far end of the battlefield.

There was a hint of surprise within his eyes.

"Eight-headed Cloud Crow?"

He smirked at the corner of his lips, as he pointed with his right hand.

Fuuuuu!

A black chain suddenly flew out from his hands, and disappeared into a void.

*************************

The sharp claws touched Demetrius’ neck slightly.

Garen’s expression changed all of all of a sudden, and he retreated without hesitation.

Jii Jii Jii! With three successive evasions, he appeared several metres away in a flash, counterattacking with a palm strike

Bam!

The demonic blade clashed fiercely with the red claws, but it was not a frontal impact but a mere redirection, causing it to miss. Garen smirked, his free right hand cast a bolt of lightning.

Bam!

The Totem’s Light on Antharella’s abdomen shattered, she was pushed back lightly from the impact. Large volumes of blood spewed from her mouth, the skin on her abdomen quickly turned to a charred black with signs of burns, which smoking fumes with clear palm-shaped brand on her abdomen.

Swish!

At this moment, multiple black chains appeared suddenly, right under Garen’s Totem’s Light, which bound him tightly.

Ancelora tried her best to swing her blade.

"Kunta!!" She roared.

That tremendous horrid quake happened again. Its power was actually several times stronger than before!

Garen’s expression changed, this tremendous force was enough to threaten him.

"Die!!!" Antharella’s berserked blade fell upon Garen’s face. The vibration condensed and closed inwards, like a bent ray of purple light.

Bam!

In a loud thump, Garen’s head was shattered, splattering into a paste of blackish-red mixture of flesh and bones.

Purple rays of light scattered, releasing a bright flare in an instant, blinding everyone in the vicinity.

The black chains were also completely released due to the impact. Garen’s body exploded into smithereens, turning into a blackish-red pool of body parts, splattered across the snowy grounds.

Oddly, Garen’s silhouette appeared once again at the forest nearby. He seemed completely fine, backstepping quickly away.

In the air, countless dark clouds congregated and formed on God Cloud’s body.

He calmly looked at Garen from afar.

"Running, eh?"

He extended his arms and clenched his fists, multiple black chains instantly appeared from the void; shooting towards Garen with overwhelming density.

Hua huaaaa…..

In an instant, the entire sky was filled with the loud noise of clashing chains rubbing into each other.

A bit of fresh blood leaked from the mark between Garen’s brows, and he looked at God Cloud, who was far away in midair. Garen raised a pointed finger at him.

A giant scarlet silhouette appeared behind Garen. The attribute points that he had accumulated over a long period were all instantly added to Intelligence.

The Eight-headed Dragon roared ferociously, the growth on its back popped, and a golden colored dragon head shot out, ferociously rushing towards the chains.

Roar!!

The golden dragon head howled, the other eight dragon heads regained their vitality and simultaneously flew towards the sky-filling chains.

In that instant, the Nine-Headed Dragon clashed ferociously with the countless chains. Numerous dragon roars and the clashing of chains filled the air around them.

A loud thump echoed throughout the snowy mountain cap.

The large snow cap exploded, bringing down large volumes of snow, crushed boulders and uprooted trees.

From afar, it seemed as though the white mountain top was sliced by an unfathomable force; it's broken upper half exploded into countless bits of debris.

A giant red nine-headed dragon was entrenched in the mountain top, its nine heads howled all at once. Countless chains were bound onto it, much like a trapped demon dragon from the folklores!

In an instant, the demon dragon secreted a translucent liquid akin to blood plasma. These plasma flowed along the chains, completely dyeing them red.

Pa! Pa! Pa pa!!

The chains broke one by one, as though the plasma corroded them loose.

Roar!!!

The Nine-Headed Demon Dragon roared once again, Badum!!

With a humongous bang, the Demon Dragon turned into extremely luminous crimson rays, so bright they outshined the sun itself for an instant, casting the entire mountain valley in a shade of red.

Garen’s silhouette was moving quickly towards the right side of the mountain, and vanished from the horizon.

"As expected from Commander God Cloud! I will repay your kindness in the future!" A cold voice reverberated from the top of the mountain.

God Cloud could not help but to cover his eyes as he waited for the rays to disappear. The snow peak was in an incorrigible mess, with the opponent nowhere to be found.

As he observed the ranks of Antharella’s men dropping like flies, God Cloud extended his arm, recalling the demonic blade Kuna, which flew up and landed in his hand.

"From here on, in this vast land, comes another formidable opponent …" As he looked towards the direction which Garen fled, his eyes filled with lament.

Without a sound, God Cloud vanished into intangible dark clouds, along with his demonic blade.

********

In a dark cavern, deep within a vast desert far away.

Innumerable chains extended from a dark void, binding a man in the center like prey within a spider’s web.

There were two holes pierced into his shoulders, but there was no blood flowing out at all.

Just as God Cloud’s body vanished, this man slowly opened his eyes.

"Orders."

"Here." A silver lady appeared from within the darkness, much like a statue carved from white silver. Oddly, the lady does not have a face, instead only having a slab.

"To everyone from Obscuro Society, once you encounter Nine-Headed Demon Dragon Garen, report back to headquarters immediately, I will personally create a clone to deal with him."

"Yes sir. General, must we pay such close attention to a single person?" The lady could not comprehend the attention this man warranted.

"His abilities in and of itself are comparable to my clones. This person has embarked on similar paths as we. Unfortunately, the totems that he chose were not considered strong; its potential has been maximized. Otherwise, we might find ourselves with another commander-class character."

The lady did not ask further, but bowed and went off.

******************

On the snowy peak was Antharella, lying on the snow covered ground. Demeritus squatted beside her, slowly smothering a green medicinal cream onto her abdomen.

The burned palm mark was recessed in her abdomen, like carvings on rock.

"Sister…" Demeritus looked at the wound on Antharella’s belly, completely clueless as to how to handle it.

Even with the strongest Elemental General’s Totem’s Light was only capable of mitigating most of the damage caused by Garen, the little bit of power left that penetrated Antharella’s Totem’s Light and hit her had actually caused such devastating damage.

Garen’s speed was too fast. Even if Antharella had many tricks up her sleeve, in that instance of close quarters combat, the only thing that could defend her was the Totem Light. She hadn't even managed to spiritualize, yet she already had her totem’s light shattered by one palm strike, sending all of her totems into a state of heavy damage and injury.

Even the demonic blade Kunta was unable to hurt Garen with its strongest, non-blade tip attack; concussion.

Demeritus had chills to her bones as she recalled the scene just now.

Immense speed, strength, phantom-like movements. He could even revive after being slashed by the demonic blade.

"Rumour says he has eight heads, according to the analysis by the Grand Obscuro, he should have 8 chances of revival. Now that he has nine heads, we need to kill him another eight times, only then can we destroy the monster once and for all!" Antharella said with a defeated look. "My attack previously should have denied one life from him"

"Killing him another eight times…" Demeritus looked around, out of the five elemental general mobilized, only two were missing in action, likely to have fled. The remaining three who launched frontal attacks on Garen were thrown off the peak after having their totem lights shattered. They were likely dead as well.

The totem users of the outer ring had sustained major injuries due to the knockback from the broken tactical array. Adding onto the damage sustained from being within the blast radius of the explosion, it’s unlikely that they will survive.

"Just to kill him once, we had to give up so much….. Eight more times….." Demeritus didn't know how to go about this problem.

Her face wore the expression of shock as she stared at her elder sister Antharella. From her eye sockets emerged streams of warm, red blood.

"Sis….Sister…"

"I’m fine, don’t worry, I’ll recover after a while" Antharella smiled in a comforting manner, then she felt that her face was wet.

She reached out to touch her eyes, her hand suddenly turned bloody red.

"No….no… No way! What is happening!!!??" Antharella got frightened, both her hands tried to wipe her bloodied tears dry, but her eyes just kept tearing with more blood.

She felt her eyes bulging, getting dryer, as though there was something stuck inside her eyes. She rubbed her eyes vigorously with her hand.

She put down her hands, but her eyes bulged even more instead.

The bloodied tears flowed more and more, eventually….

Bam!

With a muffled explosions happening simultaneously, Antharella’s eyeballs exploded. She remained stiff, and did not move.

With a bang, she looked up, then fell again.

"Sis...sister..!!??" Demeritus covered her mouth, and took two steps back in fright. She saw that within her sister’s bloodied eye socket was some reddish-white grey matter!

"No!!!"

*********

The battle of the snow peak had spread across the entire East Continent’s forces without any form of reconnaissance within just two days.

The obscuro society mobilized seven generals, two Ultimate Heirlooms, two sets of tactical arrays. General God Cloud’s clone was mobilized, ambushing the Royal Alliance at the peak of the snowy mountains.

The master of the Geometry Service, Hellfire is missing, his status unconfirmed. Secret Service Eight Headed Cloud Crow, who walked into a heavy ambush, actually killed the leader of the ambush against Royal Alliance.

The evolved Nine-Headed Dragon totem had a single clash with God Cloud’s clone, and managed to retreat after breaking free from the chains.

Indeed, The Eight-Headed Cloud Crow shook the East Continent, and the order which came from God Cloud within the Dark Maze had also been spread far and wide. The pocket watch belonging to Eight-Headed Cloud Crow was broken, The announcement from God Cloud indicated that the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon is obviously more indicative of Garen’s totem characteristics.

At this moment, Garen’s nickname changed once again. The Nine-Headed Demon Dragon shook the world.

On the third day after the battle at the snowy peak, Black Prince arrived at Kovitan’s capital, officially meeting Emperor Avic.

Chapter 399: Notice 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Several thousand metres away from the Snowy Peak, on top of the dark green sea-like forest, a cloud of thick black mist shrouded a speeding blonde silhouette. .

After some distance, the black mist slowly dissipated, becoming thinner and thinner.

Finally; all the black mist disappeared into nothing.

The black pocket watch in Garen’s hand let out a crackling sound, and a crack revealed the watch within..

He suddenly lost the lift he had had from the black mist and began freefalling to the ground. The black light array lit up beneath his feet, and Garen used it as a platform to somersault in the air, steadily landing on the branch of a large tree within the forest.

Among the rustling sounds of the leaves, squirrels and birds scurried away, frightened.

Garen couldn’t care less about those animals, he was instead feeling sentimental about the pocket watch in his hands.

"Too bad, the Cloud Crow Array was really nice to use. Now it’s broken." He recalled the previous battle’s scenarios; it was probably damaged by God Cloud’s chain binding.

Those kinds of chains were very strong, which conversely meant that his body was strong enough to resist that kind of binding. If it was any other totem user; they would have probably been turned into minced meat.

Garen waved his hand, and three-dotted marks between his brows turned red. The status of the Nine-Headed Dragon was reflected into his consciousness directly.

He lightly touched the left side of the mark, which seemed to have dimmed a little following his main body’s death.

Within his consciousness, the Nine-Headed Dragon was lying quietly in a pitch black space, the one on the far left seemed to be dying without any signs of vitality left in it.

"Looks like this three-dotted marks are not simply a representation of the changes in the body." Garen thought, he recalled in the Secret Techniques world’s top invincible Holy Fist Palosa. One of his ultimates technique was the 99 Acute Airholes, which meant he needs to be killed 99 times before one could truly win him.

The Nine-Headed Dragon’s body containing nine lives are akin to the 99 Acute Airholes in its mechanisms.

"If it wasn’t for the continuous hunt for strong totem users on the snowy peak and gaining large amounts of potential points, this battle would have resulted in some significant damage."

He originally thought that there was more he needed to do before he could maximise his Intelligence, but during the hunt on the snowy peak, a large portion of his opponents were strong totem users, which made it adequate to maximise his Intelligence and then some.

The gang up by Obscuro Society was within his expectations, but the fight God Cloud’s clone had eluded Garen’s predictions..

God Cloud’s body was obviously immaterial, even at first glance. It was without a doubt a clone condensed from tiny particles, but nonetheless, a mere clone could reach such levels of power. Not to mention the odd Demon Blade Kunta.

If it was just a clone, Garen was confident that he himself would not lose in a frontal fight, but with that blade… he also wasn’t sure if God Cloud had more tricks up his sleeve.

As one of the few strongest in existence within Obscuro, the level at which God Cloud was was definitely something Garen had not been able to reach. Naturally, his gamut of strong moves wasn’t lacking.

That’s why he made the decisive move to run away.

As he inspected the status of the dying dragon head, he found it to be very close to death; it breathed in short, raspy breaths that were increasingly frequent and short.

Garen focused onto his own ability’s Attribute Pane. After researching multiple totem theories and experimentations, according to his on Nine-Headed Dragon’s genetic model, he should be able to mitigate the problem with his ability.

Indeed, the nine lives of the Nine-Headed Dragon are absolute!

Which means, these nine lives were not transferable; Garen has to die a total of nine times before he would perish for good.

But back then when the dual-headed salamander was able to evolve into the Nine-Headed Dragon, it was actually because he depended on his abilities to force an evolution. All these depended on abilities to evolve all the way to the absolute genetic limits.

Originally, the dual-headed salamander did not qualify to evolve up to this point, the Nine-Headed Dragon genetic pieces in its DNA was too little, only in literal shards. However, with a push from his abilities, he could fully explore its potential, and freely unravel all the possibilities that laid in the bits and pieces of genetic material, hence the nine heads.

"According to the derivator, since the abilities can evolve a Dual-Headed Salamander into a Nine-Headed Dragon, the loss of that severed head should have been permanent, but this could be fixed using my potential points." Even though Garen was quite sure this was the case, he still felt nervous when it came to the moment of truth. This was the pivotal point, where he would ascertain whether his deduction was correct or not.

He looked at his own stats.

"Strength 12, Dexterity 10. Vitality 10. Intelligence 10. Potential 3218%. Possess the qualities of a Luminarist."

Jumping across his dense Skill Panes and other totems, Garen eventually shifted his focus directly upon the core totem.

"Core totem - Nine-headed dragon: Evolved creature from the ancient creature Eight-Headed Dragon, perfect genetic organism. Theoretical Form 4 creature, ultimate form not upgradeable.

Information on Ancient Genetics: In the Luminarists’ records, the Nine Headed Dragon is one of the organisms with the strongest survivability in the ancient era. They possess 8 extremely vicious sub-heads and one main head. Each dragon head has differing abilities, although they were mostly related to poison. Each of the dragon heads has a different poison ability, and ruled over the ancient era for tens of thousands of years. However, due to the extinction of the Nine-Headed Dragon’s food sources, the Nine-Headed Dragons fell into decline, and was evicted from the position as the apex predator of the food chain.

This terrifying menace possesses strong poison. It was ugly, but extremely possessive towards objects that are aesthetically pleasing. They are attracted towards beautiful things; whether it be beautiful flora, fauna, or serene environments and its creatures. They would normally inhabit the side of a lake on a bed of gems. Even though they are distant relatives of the multi-headed salamanders that dug out underground mazes, as the top-dogs of the food chain, they never had the need to hide in a cavern underground, instead preferring to bask under the sunlight, cleaning its dragon scales. According to the Luminarists’ research and deduction, this kind of apex predator should turn out to be extremely narcissistic.

Abilities: Void Whirlpool (extends the dragon head, bringing it greater reach and tearing down prey. In the Nine-Headed Dragon’s eyes, enemies mean food! This ability allowed for its prey to be slaughtered and devoured straight away.)

Nine Lives (Must be killed nine times before it completely perishes, each time requiring the opponent to slice off all nine heads at one go, otherwise the heads will continuously regenerate; a nightmare for any opponent.)

Dragon Skin

Berserker’s Howl (After the inducing concussion, temporarily increases all dragon heads’ abilities for 155 seconds, attack and speed increases by 30% at the same time)

Vitality Tear

Rotting Poison Mist (A blood red, potent poison that can break down and decompose most of the organisms in the world.)

Virus Parasitism (The Nine-headed Dragon does not possess the parasitizing abilities like the salamanders living underground; it hates everything filthy and ugly, but.had another type of extremely horrid parasitizing ability, which allowed it to inject live bacterium into the enemy’s body, continuously absorb the enemy’s life force, ultimately transforming it from the inside out into an aesthetically pleasing - the dragon minion)

Looking through all the information, Garen knew these messages were sorted and collected by the ability within his memories, which meant that he had known some of the facts partially; while the rest were derived by the ability itself.

In reality, the Nine-headed Dragon’s strength is not completely known to its full extent. For instance, for its final ability, Virus Parasitism, the exact product of what was named dragon minion, even Garen didn’t know, the ability also hadn't managed to detail it properly.

He looked at the end of Nine-Headed Dragon’s Nine Lives abilities, and there was an additional blood red symbol which looks like an icon of the eight-headed dragon: it was a status icon.

‘Nine Lives’ Status: Eight Lives.’

Garen tried focusing on this ability.

In five whole seconds, the Nine Lives ability actually had some movement. The eight lives symbol slowly got blurry.

His potential points also slowly decreased.

Garen’s heart flustered, he knew it was working.

The potential points kept dropping for 20 whole points before it finally stopped. In the end, the eight lives symbol lit up again, but instead eight dragon heads, there were nine.

In his consciousness, the dragon head on the far left was slowly turning normal, becoming lively, like all the other heads again.

Garen exhaled in relaxation.

"Twenty points to recharge one life, this is really worth it. Unfortunately the heirloom was nowhere to be found, probably was taken away by people from the Geometry Service amidst the chaos. Who would’ve known that the Obscuro’s attempt to steal the heirloom was faked, whereas the ambush of the Three Departments was bona fide. It looks like this will turn into a full-blown war."

After finishing his checks, Garen jumped off the branch. He glanced at his own torn attire; the full black body armor was entirely destroyed, as well as the magic mirror that Windling made. It didn’t manage to reflect anything, and it had already been shattered into pieces due to the chains. The shards even got embedded into his own skin, as though they inserted into the muscles itself.

Garen’s body shuddered, and painfully extracted the shards.

"Big Brother… Big Brother…" Unexpectedly, the shards of magic mirror actually transmitted faint voices.

"Windling?" Garen asked in an explorative manner.

"Big Brother you’re alright! I knew it, how was it? Are you amazed by my noble techniques? It was still usable even though it shattered into pieces! This is not something any ordinary elite is capable of accomplishing!" Windling snickered.

"You’re okay?" Garen filtered out the nonsense.

" I had to hide further away to be able to observe Big Brother’s stalwart heroism." Windling said cheesily. Nine dragon heads!! Pshh, indeed, it’s not your ordinary strong creature, even God Cloud’s clone got beaten till it fled!"

Garen was speechless.

"I’m preparing to head back to Kovitan’s Capital, are you coming?"

"I…." Windling had a rare instance of not joking around, instead he quieted down. "I wanna go check on my kid."

"Where to?"

"Maryland, a small country near Daniela. Thanks to you, I have gotten a tonne of great materials, killing people and looting is indeed the fastest way to grind."

"Then, take care" Garen replied coldly. For Windling, he couldn’t say it was vengeance, but instead felt oddly like a friend. This fellow seemed like the type of happy-go-lucky person, walking around with a carefree look, but inside, he carried a lot of weight on his shoulders.

"So this is it, I’ll meet you next time, who knows if I’ll be looking for you." Windling snickered again.

"Sure, I’ll probably be in Kovitan this year, you can come directly to me."

"Big brother…"

"What’s up?"

".. Actually, you’re a good guy…"

With that, WIndling disappeared. Garen speechlessly put down the shard.

Chapter 400: Notice 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Blood Tower, if it were you, would you be able to escape safely from this harsh environment?"

Within a tall black tower somewhere in East Continent, in a room on one of the middle floors.

Two regal looking young men stood in front of a large sand basin, where one of them was manipulating the geography and settings of the sand within with his right hand.

The contents of the sand basin were black and white, and it appeared to represent the snowy peak on which Garen and Hellfire were under siege. Each little black dot represented an Obscuro Society member, while the two red dots represented Hellfire and Eight Headed Cloud Crow.

The other young man frowned. His face appeared ordinary, the kind that would go unnoticed if you passed him on the streets. At this time, he was watching the sand basin closely with a stoic expression.

Both of them did not look like they were past thirty years old, but the calmness in their eyes was something that one in their thirties could never accomplish.

"General God Cloud is one of the two strongest commanders, hence he was put in charge of the strongest military in East Continent. I wouldn’t know how much power he had allocated to a single clone of his" Blood Tower thought for a moment before he answered carefully.

"How much power was allocated?" the man before him laughed. His skin was slightly tanned and he had bright blue eyes. His face was marked with a black tattoo of the number "4", and his soft white hair glowed in the light.

"I acknowledge that God Cloud is stronger than I am, but you don’t have to rub it in right? In the 30 years I’ve guarded the Secret Services, I’ve clashed with him several times, and each time ended with me in a losing spot. He was one of the three strongest people within Obscuro Academy, after all."

His eyes fell on the sand basin once again.

"You may be unconvinced this time, but God Cloud has definitely unleashed his full power."

Blood Tower did not say anything, awaiting his rebuttal.

"His clone had even brought the demon blade Kunta, how much effort was put into this? Even so, he wasn’t able to restrain the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon." The white haired man said softly.

"If I were against him, I could retreat safely too." Blood Tower replied seriously.

"Even after you’ve been affected by the mixed poison?"

"Er…" Blood Tower was unsure of how to reply to him.

"God Cloud’s power have realistically reached the pinnacle of Form 5. This Garen being able to fight his clone on an equal level means he should at least be a normal Form 5. After all, the difference between each stage of Form 5 is extremely huge, like between the Leader and I." The white-haired youngster explained calmly.

"But Form 5 is already the top. It is then decided by the strength of the heirloom, as well as the comprehension and delivery of power. We are already in unison with the totem and have reached realms previously unimagined. This realm may be the pinnacle, but it is also a shackle. Each Form 5 is searching for a way to break through."

The young white-haired man turned around and walked towards the window, and he gazed towards the golden boundless desert outside.

"Such a pity… I guess God Cloud cracked his head researching on this topic. Even though I cannot beat him, someone else managed to."

A small smile quirked his lips for a moment.

"Heed my order!"

"Yes!" Blood Tower rushed forward.

" By the order of the chief minister, send an announcement to Secret Services: Once spotting the location of God Cloud's clone, he shall personally destroy his clone!"

Blood Tower’s pupils constricted, but it immediately recovered.

"Additionally, summon my personal messenger, tell God Cloud." The white-haired man once had a warm expression again. "Have you lost your bloody mind?"

Blood Tower’s face paled; he then knew the Deputy Minister’s old habits occurred again.

********************************

A few days later…

By the borders of Kovitan, at the upstreams of Red River --- Snowy Mountain Nebulus.

An otherwise quiet and serene snowy mountain had an unimaginably large black bird gliding around it.

This giant bird had some semblance to the Dragonhawk, with similar long, sharp beaks. Its wingspan extended a hundred metres, encompassing the area beneath it within an enormous shadow.

Under the shadow of the giant bird, a knight in black armor was riding a large black horse through the air, as though the sky was solid ground.

The black knight was circled by copious amounts of black smoke, which was diffusing in and out of the crevices of the armor, as though it was alive.

Jii!

The large horse exhaled two streams of white air strongly, before it stopped midair.

The black knight gazed into the distance towards the snowy mountain, raised his hand, and pointed at it.

Jii!!!

In an instant, the weather changed. Countless black clouds swirled from behind him as the sky immediately dimmed, while the land was blanketed by an enormous shadow.

Those were black dragonhawks!

Black dragonhawks that numbered more than thousands! Each had a wingspan of at least twenty metres, and they were cloaked within the black smoke, forming a large area of pitch black cloud. They flocked towards the snowy mountain.

"That… That is the Snowy Mountain branch of Obscuro Society! Blackfield Dragonhawk King…. Has he lost his mind?!"

"Sir?" A few white-clothed subordinates ran over, gasping for air as they questioned the white-robed man. They did not know what was happening, and they could only look at their leader in confusion.

"That is the place where a clone of God Cloud was stationed.." The white-robed man recalled, he looked at the situation at the sky with equal amounts of shock and confusion. " Is Blackfield trying to wage an all-out war with Obscuro?"

In the sky, the black knight upon his giant horse galloped forth. The heavy clip-clop of the horse could be heard from the patrol tower, despite being several hundred kilometres away.

The black knight accelerated, to the point where he appeared to become a streak of black lightning, heading straight for the snowy mountain’s peak.

On the peak of the snowy mountain, a single man bearing chains on both his shoulders slowly appeared. Both men faced each other.

"Dragonhawk King! Are you courting death?!"

The black knight pulled out the giant sword sheathed behind him with a clank. The black smoke surrounding him was concentrated on the black sword.

"In this world, there are things that I must do." His voice echoed from within the helmet.

Gachak!!

A lightning strike rent the sky, illuminating the two men’s imposing figures.

A few hours later…..

Bam!

In a loud strike, the Nebulus Mountain was split into two. The seemingly endless snow tumbled down as an avalanche, morphing into a white tide that swept away everything in its path, levelling the forest.

The black knight was adorned with a full suit of rent armor as he slowly flew off. Countless black dragonhawks twirled in the sky, announcing the victor of the battle.

"Blackfield announcing to the world: Garen, just because you didn’t mention some things doesn’t mean that they’ll be forgotten."

***************

After the Nine-headed Demon Dragon’s earthshaking incident, the royal Three Departments’ Geometry Service was furious, sending out personnel to negotiate for Hellfire’s release and the surrender of the heirloom.

But this wasn’t the big news.

The shocking one involved the Secret Services.

On the third day of the announcement concerning God Cloud, the chief minister of the Secret Service announced that he would personally create a clone to purge any sighting of God Cloud and his location.

The announcement and God Cloud’s content clashed, with neither of them giving in!

On hindsight, everything made sense; the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon was on a mission on behalf of Secret Services, and even though it wasn’t successful, Obscuro actually took the Three Departments lightly, publicly sending out the announcement to get his own clone to kill Garen. This made the elites within the Secret Services extremely aggravated.

When had it ever been others’ turn to hunt one of their own?!

Since the ancient times, it has always been them hunting down people. Now they actually dared to turn around and attack them?

In a series of forces’ influence, the incident involved both the Three Departments’ honor and the elites’ sense of belonging. The chief minister then announced to the world to launch attacks targeted at God Cloud.

The message was clear: You broke the rules first, and if you make a move, we will not hesitate to erase you!

Following that, another huge incident occurred.

Possibly in response to God Cloud’s announcement, the King of Blackfield, Blackfield Dragonhawk King Goth actually made a public appearance at one of the important Obscuro branches, fought hard with God Cloud’s clone,and at the price of a serious injury, he successfully destroyed a strong branch that had a God Cloud clone stationed there. The incident was earth shaking too, as at the same time he announced a similar content involving the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon Garen.

Two incidents, which were supposed to revolve around the Ultimate Heirloom had changed into a bloodbath.

By the time he received the news, he was already on the way to the capital.

He heard about this from the Secret Service member who escorted him, who also happen to be from the Crimson Team.

***********************************************

As Garen sat on the back of a large pale grey rhino-like creature, he carefully studied the latest intel.

These white rhinos that he sat on were the latest creatures bred by the kingdom, which had extreme stamina, being able to last over a fortnight with just one meal, and its speed was pretty decent.

The rhino was only second to the Yellow-eyed Crow, which were hailed as one of the best transportations.

For the aforementioned crow, although it wasn’t considered large by any measure, its wingspan was too eye-catching. With the current train of events, travelling on the crow would make him an easy target for elites, and reinforcements would not be much help either. It was better to move on land where it was covert and safe.

On the right side of Garen’s rhino was Kid’s rhino. This fellow was humming an unknown song, and hadn’t changed much from before.

By reasons unknown to him, Kid always had an odd aura about him which made people pay less attention to him, but they still feel felt his slight eccentricity when they paid closer attention.

After Crimson Team rendezvoused with Garen, everyone except Kid treated Garen with a mixture of fear and respect. Only Kid had the usual attitude as before.

Garen faintly understood some eccentric traits of Kid and he didn’t mind it, what he was most concerned about was the intel brought by Crimson Team.

As he quietly rolled up the intel sheet, he used some force and kneaded the paper, disintegrating it to be carried away by the wind.

"Goth you brat… you’re nothing like before…. And Chief Minister, with these two incidents, it may seem dangerous, but it’s already overwhelmingly safe."

Thinking back to the scenarios that happened in Iron Tank City, and the quartet he’d been in back then, its members had gone missing, been scattered, and had been killed in combat.

But the biggest influencing factor was not these, but the fact that Blackfield attacked Obscuro, which meant that the entire Blackfield had declared war against Obscuro.

There had already been ongoing subjugation missions against Obscuro led by Blackfield. Both sides had their respective wins and losses, though back then it had not escalated to this point. Blackfield Dragonhawk and God Cloud both had some restraint.

Unexpectedly, for Garen’s sake, he’d revealed all his cards.

Chapter 401: Encounter 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As he sat on the white rhino, Garen intermittently recalled memories from Iron Tank City, and there was an inexplicable emotion within his heart.

He’d thought that Goth would keep blaming him, angry at him. That the two of them would possibly remain at this state of misunderstanding. Who would’ve known….

From the announcement, he can see that Goth still held grudges towards him, but carried a similarly complicated emotion.

"Team Leader. There’s something that awaits your decision." Old Man slowed down at the front, and as Garen closed the distance between them, he held out a map, a soil-colored yellow scroll.

Garen took it from him and listened.

"We picked two routes on the map which were safer, but we couldn’t decide on which route to take. Both routes has its pros and cons." Old Man explained. "Please have a look."

Garen nodded, then opened up and scanned the map.

On the map, there was a winding mountain range from the middle leading to the top of the map, as though a black centipede had laid down upon the paper. The route they were currently taking was the way along the mountain range.

Two red lines clearly illustrated the two possible routes.

The destination of both routes was Kovitan Kingdom, but the one on the left was winding, it was significantly longer with a detour. Plus, there were many markings of sightings of strong creatures.

The route on the right was more straightforward, but they would have to go through three troublesome locations.

Garen frowned slightly.

"How long would the shorter route take?"

"Assuming that we do not stop, it will take about 7 days." Old man continued. "The troublesome sections have been marked out. Of course, there will be hordes of weaker creatures, but as there’s no markings, it is safe to ignore.

Garen nodded.

"The longer route will require us to brave through 4 clusters of at least form 3 monsters’ territories, and we may not necessarily be able to avoid confrontations. Some of them are more troublesome, the terrains are also more complex, and the swamps are not ideal for the white rhinos’ movement. We should choose the shorter route."

"But the shorter route passes by Blood Queen’s territory…" Kitten interrupted, and the remaining members shuddered. Except Red Umbrella, who was asleep on his white rhino’s back.

"Blood Queen Earnest? What’s the issue?" Garen raised his brows in confusion.

"One of the members of Secret Service caused a huge amount of losses in her territory Avision City, and now both sides are in a tense situation. Queen Earnest herself has Daniela’s support, and there are also strong subordinates under her wings. There was an announcement about a month ago which states that members of the Secret Services are all unwelcome in the city.

Garen was slightly shocked.

"Does the Secret Service have such a strong member? To be able to wreck havoc at Avision City?" Garen was interested

"Who would've known, that person from the Green team, who really wasn’t eye-catching by any means, actually could cause such a huge loss." Old Man forced a smile.

"What kind of losses?" Garen got more curious.

Old Man shook his head. "He absorbed the Blood Queen’s blood essence. It was an accident that nobody anticipated."

"Blood essence?" Garen was stunned. As one of the Three Heroes, even though she was not abnormally strong; probably on Goth’s level,she was not a character that one should offend. Blood essence was a form of essence gem that was extracted from her flesh and blood. This was the core of her largest tactics within Avision City, there were only four of them present in the entire city, and they powered all the tactical arrays.

An ordinary totem user would melt instantaneously as soon as they approached the blood essence, let alone absorb it. Who would have known that it would have been absorbed by some outsider totem user.

Old Man shook his head slightly.

"Now the Secret Service is in an awkward situation with Avision City. At times like this, It is best that a totem user of your calibre maintain your distance from Avision City to avoid any further conflicts."

"What about that person? That fella from Green Team?" Garen was more interested in that man than the tense situation. To be able to do what others could not, he must be special.

"Still hiding in Avision City. With the entire Avision City out for his blood, trying to capture him. It’s also hard for us in the Secret Service to step forward. After all, we were at fault for absorbing their important resource."

"Then let’s take the short route, just so I can see what this Blood Queen is like." Garen laughed. "Spread this news through the communication device. If that person is smart, he’ll take this opportunity to leave Avision City."

"Um...alright." Old Man grimaced.

********************************************

Two days later…..

The sky was ashen and heavy with mist.

Yellow weeds waved gently in the breeze upon the pale yellow plantation soil. Surrounding the area was a ring of shrubs.

Those murky yellow shrubs grew in uneven patches, but among them was a green passage..

Broken fences littered the area about the passage, the surface of the passage was covered in dense layers of leaves and moss.

Upon the passage were five greyish-white rhinos slowly marching forward. These rhinos were about three metres high, their bodies were round and huge, and every step they took was very stable. They could barely move along the passage, and sometimes they would bump into the fences on the side.

On the thick skins of the rhinos were concealed scars, giving them a rugged appearance.

There were even a bunch of oddly-dressed people riding on their backs. As they were donning black armors and hoods, their faces were hard to see. The exception was the golden iris embedded on their necklines.

Evidently, they were members of the Royal Alliance.

Deep within the plantation field, several pairs of white eyes were observing the passing rhinos, while carefully gauging the auras of the humans on the rhinos’ backs.

Woooo.....

A deep howl like a dog’s howl was heard from both sides of the plantation.

The rhinos started feeling alarmed and refused to move forward.

Suddenly, white shadows lunged from both sides of the passage; there were no sounds, just the light rustling of the weeds as they were brushed aside.

Most of them were rushing towards the white rhinos, while some of them targeted the people on top of the rhinos’ backs.

"Let me do it!" A girl’s voice was heard from the top of the rhino’s back. "I was looking for some potential points to upgrade my equipment!" he voice was clear, and a red ray flashed as she swung her hand.

Bam!

A giant red tiger was formed midair, with a long, whip-like tail fiercely sweeping.

Bang bang bang!!...

After a series of impact noises, large amounts of white shadows were battered back into the plantations. They tumbled upon the ground several times and no longer moved.

The group then saw the true identity of those white shadows; they were all white stray dogs, except they had two tails instead of one, which was odd.

"That’s the Dual-tailed White Dog, just a Form 1 monster pack." a man on top of the Rhino’s back said calmly, it was Old Man’s voice. "But they usually inhabit areas near the Red Unihorn Lizards. Everybody be more aware."

"Check me out!" Kitten commanded the giant red tiger to start killing recklessly around the plantation, with each swipe and lunge killing off two or three white dogs.

After a while, endless whines were heard as the scent of blood spread across. The pack that originally rushed towards the rhinos were now scrambling away.

"This dual-tailed white dogs have excellent breeding capabilities and are able to give birth to more than ten pups in a month. It’s also the reason why they are almost always in state of starvation and are constantly on the hunt for food." Old Man explained. "Coincidentally, they make great prey for higher leveled, evolved creatures too."

Before he’d finished speaking, the sky was suddenly abuzz with a horde of red unihorn lizards flying over them.

They had a black unihorn and red bat wings; much like a winged version of a lizard. These lizards were making some odd sounds as they flapped their wings towards the group. Behind them was a large white bat.

"Is that a white bat?" a man looked up from the back of a rhino in the middle of the formation. A sliver of golden hair was visible from the hood, the man had three scarlet markings between his brows, which look like a birthmark.

This person was actually Garen, who was rushing towards Kovitan Kingdom.

Watching the white bat swinging its chains as it rushed at him, Garen couldn’t help but recall the early days of Iron Tank City, where he first met a white bat. At that time he’d been extremely weak and had to resort to fight tactics just to go up against a white bat. But now…

Roar!!

The Giant red tiger roared in fury as it leaped upwards powerfully and pounced onto the bat. Its limbs had ignited in crimson flames, and as its mouth opened wide, a fireball was fired.

Bam!

The sky turned into a sea of fiery explosions, and the bat disappeared into a giant fireball, dyeing its surroundings red.

"Yay!!" Kitten happily withdrew Red TIger, and surveyed at the messy battlefield. " Successfully cleared!" She puffed out her chest and sneakily glanced at Red Umbrella, but noticing that he was fast asleep, so she pouted.

"Let’s go." Garen said coldly.

Kitten then obediently shut up and continued the journey.

After that time where she was frightened by Garen, she didn’t dare cause a ruckus in front of him anymore. She could clearly feel that Garen at that point of time had seriously been planning to kill her. It was unlike any other enemy that she’d faced before, where they would have second thoughts due to her attractive appearance and body figure, which would allow her more time to drag it out. But with Garen, she felt that he was looking at her like a corpse, and with just a single misstep, nobody would be able to stop him from killing her. The others may not have realized it, but she’d felt it. Even Red Umbrella, who was most sensitive to killing intent, thought of it as a joke. Kitten had almost wetted herself at that time.

She truly didn’t misunderstand that feeling. Garen at that time was really thinking about killing her, and had she been unaware of the affairs, Garen would have better control on the team after removing the "volatile" parts of the team. She did not expect this man to be so capricious.

The six rhinos continued walking past the plantation after a moment of settling and calming them.

After an unknown period of time, the fields in front slowly changed to golden-yellow, as though the harvest season of autumn was coming; golden wheat fields surrounded the passage.

"So pretty…" Kid beside him couldn’t help but comment. He gazed at the sky on his left, as though there was something even more mesmerizing there.

The group looked towards the direction in which he gazed but there was only a layer of grey clouds in the sky, nothing else.

"And so it’s happened again…." Kitten pouted as she lowered her head, continued playing with her toy which looked like a rubik's cube.

Fox also lowered his head to continue reading

Old man shook his head, and went back to sleep like Red Umbrella.

Only Garen, curiously studying Kid, realized that he was incomparably innocent.

He looked up to the sky, there was indeed nothing there.

He then shuddered suddenly.

An odd situation happened.

Garen actually noticed a little hint of gold in Kid’s eyes.

His heart shivered. The sky was still covered in dense layers of clouds and there were no sun to be seen,where did he see the golden thing?

A sudden thought flashed through his mind.

He recalled that he’d received an augmentation tactic previously, which was the war shackle he received when he joined the war guild: Eye of Isaiah.

The Eye of Isaiah was activated through his thoughts.

As he gazed towards the sky again, a blurry gold image faintly appeared from within the clouds.

Garen’s heart skipped a beat, and he looked closer after suppressing his surprise. With his current improved vision, he couldn’t see any clearly, but he could roughly make out a golden, human silhouette.

Chapter 402: Encounter 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Kid, what did you see? Can you tell me?" Garen used a Secret Technique to telepathically transmit his voice by bundling it into a string and transmit it to Kid’s ears.

"Something extremely beautiful nice." Kid looked at Garen and naughtily winked his eyes. This exchange was also silent, without a sound. Just by that glance, he made Garen aware of his message.

Garen pressed his chest to control himself.

"Can you tell me what exactly?"

"I don’t want to…. Even if i did, you wouldn’t believe me, you’d call me an idiot, crazy. I’m not crazy." Kid decisively declined.

"I actually could see a little bit, just not clearly as you."

"I don’t believe you." Kid pouted.

Garen laughed as he saw Kid’s insistence, so he changed the approach. "Then, can you tell me….what is that golden-colored thing?"

"Golden?" Kid had a suspicious expression, "did..you really see the.."

"Just a little bit." Garen nodded.

The two of them, one used his Secret Techniques to transmit his voice, while the other used his glances and expressions to return the message, could actually communicate at a level that even Old Man, though he was closest to them, was unaware.

Kid scratched his head, and showed a frustrated look. " I also don’t know what that was. I saw them often anyway, in the clouds, only when the land was covered in golden fields, only then can we see them."

Garen had a clue.

"Is that thing a human?"

Kid only shook his head

"They? Does that mean there’re a lot of them?"

Subsequently, no matter how Garen asked, Kid would only respond by shaking his head, and refused to comment further.

"If i said more, even I would become slowly become unable to see them. You have to be careful too, these are the rules; their rules." Kid got anxious from the bombardment of questions, so he answered this final sentence, then stopped replying altogether.

Garen also didn’t want to press on too much, obviously Kid had already told him as much as he could. Looking at Kid’s attitude towards him, it almost felt warmer than how he was with Old Man. Almost as though he thought of Garen as the same species.

Normally, only Old Man had the patience to listen to him spill out his secrets, but he understood that Old Man just wanted him to cooperate in the squad’s movements and operations, and therefore had to be patient. He wasn’t actually interested in what Kid said, neither did he believe him.

Kid was not actually stupid, he was well aware of all these.

Although Garen’s persistent questioning was somewhat annoying, Kid knew that Garen was genuinely inquisitive, which made him really happy.

As he observed Kid’s change in attitude, Garen knew that he didn’t have to rush the discussion; there would be many more chances to interact with Kid anyway, perhaps those would lead to unexpected outcomes.

Riding on the white rhino, he once again activated the eye of Isaiah and gazed upon the sky, but that sliver of gold had disappeared.

He then looked at Kid again to realise he had long lowered his head and started humming to that unknown tune again. In his hands were some strands of wheat that Garen’s didn’t know the origin of, weaving something that looked like a garland.

"This is getting more incomprehensible…" Garen sighed and deactivated the eye of Isaiah.

*************

At night

The white rhinos were tied to a few aging trees, and laid beside in the fields to rest.

Six people were seen surrounding a bonfire, the yellow light from the flame illuminated everyone’s faces in a shade of red.

"Do we have anything entertaining to do?" Kitten asked as she yawned.

"Cards?" Red Umbrella answered first.

"I don’t want to, Fox always wins." Kitten rejected decisively.

"Then, chess? The three of you come at me; I’ll take out two of my pieces." Old Man smiled as he stroked his beard.

"Sure! But you have to take out 3!" Kitten acted demandingly.

"Alright alright." Old Man shook his head.

Garen fiddled with the bonfire as he looked at the remaining 4 people setting up the chess board and preparing themselves for the chess games. He politely declined their invitation, instead spending time sitting with Kid, who was alone on the side, quietly listening to Kid humming to the unknown tunes.

"Kid, can you tell me your real name?" He asked as he picked up some firewood to be placed on the fire pit.

"Real name?" Kid took a twig and drew on the ground. "Isn’t my real name Kid?"

"Kid is just a nickname in our group, a real name is the name you had before joining in." Garen explained.

He observed that Kid was drawing a human on the ground, and he began drawing the next one.

"About that…" Kid thought, "I think it’s Mason? I don’t really remember…."

"Don’t you have any relatives?" Garen frowned slightly.

"Relatives? I’m not sure." Kid was drawing something attentively as he was answering. "I grew up in Pumpkin Farm. There weren’t any other people there.. The strawberries there were good, I always ate those when i grew up"

"Those strawberries?" Garen wanted to ask further, but suddenly he squinted his eyes and stood up.

"Who’s there!"

The four people playing chess got slightly shocked and stood up. They looked towards the direction that Garen was gazing on.

From within the dark fields, a slender silhouette gradually walked out from within the shadows.

This person had a well-balanced body figure, and was donning a light green robe, under the robes was a white shirt and long straight black hair reaching his waist.

The most eye-catching, however, was the long thin green sword sheathed on his waist.

His appearance was handsome, his eyes amber-green, his face was devoid of any expression of coldness, but he let out a chilly and unsettling vibe.

At Garen’s first glance on this person, if it weren’t for the opponent’s long silver-patterned boots, he would have thought an Eastern Warrior from his previous life have appeared.

"Green Dragon Swordsman?" Old Man reacted first, a hint of wariness was shown in his eyes.

"Green Dragon Swordsman?" Garen realized. Green Dragon Swordsman was rumoured to be Blood Queen’s strongest subordinate, and had been playmates with the queen since they were kids, a man who followed Jean Earnest to the end.

Soon, rustling sounds from the quick footsteps sounded around the Crimson Team, squads upon squads of veiled swordsmen in green heavily surrounded the team of six as they walked through the field.

"Green Dragon Swordsman Darkla. What is this supposed to mean?" Garen glanced around the people around him.

"It was rumoured that the Nine-headed Demon Dragon had exceptional abilities during the battle at the snowy peak, the one who could retreat without harm in such a harsh environment. I wouldn’t expect such an expert to be appearing during my night patrols so easily." Green Dragon Swordsman said very calmly; it seemed that he is someone with strong self-control.

"You mean, you wanna see if I’m the real deal?" Garen looked at Darkla coldly, realizing that the opponent’s right arm was slowly reaching for the sword sheathed by his waist.

Aside from being famous for all the weird plant-type totems, Blood Queen’s Avision City was most known for Instantaneous movement totems like Green Dragon Swordsman’s totem.

If it wasn’t because Garen had seen a history of the futures before, he may have been surprised by this man’s attack.

Green Dragon Swordsman’s totem was not an independent attacker after release, instead it is completely controlled by the totem user. His sword was the storage device of the totem, and in that instance of unsheathing of the sword, the totem will be released for attack, and when he sheathed it, it would be when the totem returns to him.

The stronger the stored totem, the stronger the sword. Naturally the swordsman himself would be stronger.

Green Dragon Swordsman’s title came from the sword on his hand. It was also his core totem -- The Green Dragon!

By the looks of it, the people around him were all elites that uses the instantaneous movement totems.

Garen suddenly recalled the Demon Blade Kunta that he encountered at the snowy peak . That blade...might have the similar structure as the Green Dragon Sword It should most likely be totem storage device.

"Since you came to our Avision City, we haven’t been able to give you a good tour around, and Her Highness and I a chance to treat you generously." Green Dragon Swordsman was extending these invitations of courtesy, yet his face showed zero hospitality, instead giving people a stone cold look.

"This is unfortunate, but I am rushing for an errand at the capital. Maybe next time, I’ll personally visit Avision City once I have the chance. It’d be great to see the rumoured Green Dragon Sword and Blood Queen’s powers." Garen answered with a half-smile.

"No need to delay, let’s go now!"

Before the word "now" ended, Green Dragon Swordsman instantaneously pulled out his sword.

Clang !!

Kong !!

The thing that was pulled out from the sheath was not a sword, but instead a green ray!

It was a giant green dragon, just like the Eastern Dragon. The green dragon flew towards Garen, its roar flattening the surrounding wheat field away from the direction of the shockwave produced.

Waves of green light completely illuminated the surrounding, blinding everyone with the bright green.

A green light path was formed by the green dragon midair, the dragon head which spanned over a meter in height opened its jaw and shot straight for Garen.

The dragon left a powerful wake as it rushed forwards, deafening everyone around it.

Bam!

The green dragon’s head fiercely crashed onto thin air in front of Garen, a transparent spiral-shaped whirlpool appeared, definitively blocking the dragon’s path. The force dissipated into incessant ripple-like waves away from the impact.

Garem smiled lightly, extended his index finger, and softly tapped on the dragon’s head.

Instantly, the green light shattered. Everything in front his index finger in front of the index finger, broke into a million pieces, including the dragon’s head, turning into innumerable light shards,returning into the long sword on Green Dragon Swordsman’s hand like water to its source.

Clang!

The thin sword was sheathed again.

"So it is indeed Sir Garen, I thought it was someone impersonating you, hence I decided to test the waters a bit, surely you won’t hold it against me?" Darkla’s face remained emotionless.

"Of course not." Garen smiled. He then put his index finger down. " I had the chance to ascertain your identity too."

"I heard that Sir is hurrying back to Kovitan Kingdom, I shall not delay you then, hope to see you again."

"Likewise" Garen looked at the opponent’s right hand, and then smiled again. "Let’s go"

He turned around and left first. The remaining Crimson Team members warily followed suit. Although, they weren’t clear of who won or lost that exchange within that instant. However, the leader had given his orders, so they naturally had no need to question.

Garen and his troupe slowly disappeared into the darkness in the distance.

The Green Dragon Swordsman Darkla slowly let go of the sword in his hand. He flicked a drop of blood away, and it shot into the darkness without a sound.

"Let’s go, fall back." he stuffed his right hand into his pocket, then turned around and left.

"Squad Leader?" A female swordsman asked him out of concern.

"I’m fine." Darkla shrugged the female’s support away. "What a strong Nine-Headed Demon Dragon! He is not an ordinary Form 2 anymore, I originally though our difference was small." His face showed a sliver of apprehension.

"Notify all swordsmen within Avision City along with the Queen and I immediately at the sight of Nine-Headed Dragon. This man cannot be fought head-on."

"Is he that strong?..." The female swordsman was stunned.

"Stronger than you can ever imagine." Darkla picked up his speed, and disappeared into the darkness among the escort of swordsmen.

Chapter 403: Hot Spring 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen and the others got on top of the white rhinoceros again, and followed the trail in a specific direction towards their destination.

During the night, their surroundings were filled with the howls of wolves and other strange roars that echoed from far away throughout the open distance. It almost seemed as if they had returned to the ancient behemoth era for a moment.

"Leader? Why do we need to rush even at night? Haven't you won already?" asked Old Man quietly as he stood beside Garen.

Garen shook his head. "I am indeed stronger than the Green Dragon, but his strength was sufficient to bind me for a while. After that, the following territories belong to the Blood Queen, and I've heard that there are many fighters under her influence. Once the conflict rises, the situation may be even worse than the earlier fight at the snow peak. Moreover, God Cloud and the others misjudged my strength, thus allowing me to kill their general suddenly.

"Does this also mean that the Green Dragon's late but sudden appearance here, actually means that some frightening things are in store for you, Leader?" replied Old Man immediately.

"You could put it that way," said Garen, smiling. He thought of something suddenly.

"That's right, do you know Beckstone from the Terraflor Society, Old Man?"

"Beckstone?" Old Man pondered thoughtfully. "Seems like I heard that name two days ago from Marquess Black Snake."

"Marquess Black Snake?"

"Yes, a veteran master of the Geometry Service who made a name for himself about ten years ago. Our relationship is alright, and we used to be partners when we were younger. We used to travel around the world, but went our separate ways because we expanded differently," explained Old Man, "Before this quest, I used to practice playing chess with him, and that guy's skills were slightly better than mine. One time while we were playing chess together, someone came over with a message, and that was the first time I heard of Beckstone's name and found out that he was a representative of the Terraflor Society."

"Black Snake, Black Snake…" Garen thought of something suddenly. "Didn't he have a Precious Heirloom called the 'Rose Snake Crown'?"

A slightly surprised expression appeared on Old Man's face suddenly, before he glanced at Garen.

"How did you know? He and I were the only people who knew about that Precious Heirloom…"

"It doesn't matter how I found out about it. Just pass a message to him from me, and tell him to be careful of Beckstone. That's right, what is Marquess Black Snake's power like?" Garen questioned continuously.

"Stronger than me, but I haven't seen him in action for many years. However, he has two generals under him; two female twins, who both possess form three spiritualized powers and are extremely formidable as a team. He also has two strange beasts that he has been nurturing for many years, and no one knows about the changes they've undergone," answered Old Man simply, "As a veteran marquess who is also a high-class aristocrat, his family's territories are extremely vast. It shrunk after the turmoil, but the size of a province as of now still remains as their territory."

"Oh?" Garen was slightly surprised. According to the original historical timeline, it was now unsurprising that Marquess Black Snake had shown such formidable strength when he encountered Beckstone, because of the powerful domains that were apparently behind him.

Marquess Black Snake himself was incredibly powerful, but Beckstone was an unworthy opponent, causing him to be killed in an extremely humiliating manner. When he was killed this time, the escort masters from the Terraflor Society were suppressed by the masters of the Royal Alliance of Luminarists. After this period of hardship, a series of accidental events were the key in the path that allowed Beckstone to finally gain the trust of Marquess Black Snake's twins. In his final moments, the Marquess was ambushed and seriously injured by the twins, allowing them to steal his Precious Heirlooms in an extremely unjust situation. This was something that no one could have predicted.

In the end, the Ultimate Precious Heirloom, the Rose Snake Crown had already fallen into Beckstone's hands. He obtained a great increase in strength after his hardships, and finally achieved the fourth form. At this stage, he had finally secured his position, and if the powerful organizations wanted to move him, they needed to use even more powerful means. However, the specialized characteristics of the Rose Snake Crown made it impossible for even certain high-end powers to trap him. Therefore, when the powers finally balanced out and the manpower of the strong organizations finally decreased, Beckstone's latent powers began to show themselves, and the other organizations had no choice but to let him go.

Garen thought of this period of history, and remembered that during this key period in Beckstone's life, Marquess Black Snake had already become a very important individual.

"This person, Beckstone, was essentially a specialized seed that the Terraflor Society was cultivating. He has great potential, so you should tell Marquess Black Snake to be more careful."

"I know, I'll pass the message soon," nodded Old Man determinedly. He knew that if even Garen said that Beckstone would be troublesome, he would truly be a menace.

*******************

In a dark forest far away

A line of night walkers walked through the mysterious dark woods. The person in front held a torch as its fiery red flames illuminated their surroundings. The crunching sound of footsteps echoed throughout the area continuously, accompanied by the occasional sound of snapping tree branches.

Among these night walkers, the one leading the way was dressed from head to toe in a long white robe, with his cuffs and hems torn off for easier walking. Both of his eyes were different from everyone else's, as they were blinking with dim silver light.

Among the people behind him, there was an old man, a child, and a beautiful young lady in red clothes.

"Stone, are we there yet?" asked the young lady in red softly.

"Soon, just hold on for a little while longer. This is the Barr giant's territory, we must pass through it slowly. If we move too quickly, the giant will be provoked," Beckstone said seriously.

"Do you know if Marquess Black Snake's people have caught up?" said the young lady in red in a slightly worried tone.

"It won't be so soon. Even if the formations were insufficient to hold them down for long, they would surely cause even greater problems assuming that they were unaware of the current circumstances. They might move too quickly through the Barr giant's territory, " said Beckstone with a calm expression on his face.

Ah woo, ah woo..!!!

Suddenly, the sound of wild men's cries began to echo from a far distance behind them.

Instantly, similar cries could be heard one after another, as they echoed throughout all four directions and began to increase in frequency.

"Look, the giants have gone to greet their visitors," Beckstone said with the glimmer of a smile in his eyes.

"Indeed, it is probably that person's disciple. To think that he even knew about a secret message like this," lamented Emin, who was part of the group.

"You're being too humble. We'll be out of this dark forest soon enough, but this is the furthest I can see you off. One of the Terraflor Society's bases are in front, and you can go there before you make your way to the Headquarters," replied Beckstone politely to Emin.

"You've been a great help to me." From his appearance, Emin seemed much more youthful, as the white hair on his head had become mostly black again, while the color of his beard was also becoming darker.

"As a senior of the Terraflor Society, and a schoolmate who was taught under the same teacher as myself, this little bit of help is insignificant. What's more important are the messages that you gave me, as those are enough to make up for everything." Beckstone's eyes showed that he was sincerely grateful. "You guarded this piece of information in a remote village for more than ten years, and for the Terraflor Society to have a senior like you, is something that gives me a lot of pride," he said before he bowed to Emin respectfully.

"That's unnecessary. I should be doing that." Emin shook his head, before bowing in return immediately.

"Alright, let's go." He pulled his disciple away before glancing at the other members of his team. This journey gave him mixed feelings. When Garen first showed signs of his extraordinary talents, he saw unmistakable loneliness in Garen's eyes, and fearlessness and strength that surpassed the average person. With his talents, perseverance and persistence, such power would arrive sooner or later.

He never expected that this day would arrive so soon.

When Beckstone first tasted defeat at the hands of Garen, his hatred did not spill over towards his own teacher, showing that his heart had become more humble. If only the hatred between the both of them could be absolved…

When this idea appeared in his head, Emin thought of the hatred between the both of them immediately. He exhaled at once. This was probably impossible.

Dragging his obedient disciple along, Emin walked forward and exited the dark forest. On the glossy black grass in front of them, a few people were standing there and waiting already.

"Emin, after all these years, it must have been hard for you." A figure stepped forward in the moonlight, and an old woman with white hair appeared.

"Liz…" Emin looked at this woman who was once his close friend, and felt his throat tighten suddenly, making him unable to speak. He shut himself away from the world for the sake of that piece of information from the Terraflor Society, and even allowed his wife to die, while his final research caused him to be hated by his childhood best friend and made them both enemies. Everything was done for this moment, when he finally received his returns.

"Then… I can finally…?"

"You have the right to restore your school, but only a branch of it," nodded the old woman sincerely.

"This is enough," said Emin as a satisfied expression appeared on his face. He turned around and glanced at Beckstone and the others who were still standing in the woods. "Let's go. I haven't returned for so many years, I don't know whether everyone has changed or not."

"They've changed… Everyone's hair is white now…" The old woman's eyelids began to shut, before her words suddenly disappeared into silence.

*****************

Garen pulled at the black box communicator at his collar and knitted his brows closely together. He tried to hear the sounds that were coming from the inside.

They walked in single file and slowly passed through the white stone mounds. The white rhinoceros walked through the uneven rocky grounds, and when its steps failed to find flat surfaces, its body would rock violently.

The sun was high up in the sky and shining down on them, the fiery sunlight burning the black clothes on the backs of the six people, causing their body temperatures to increase constantly. The surface of their black armor would constantly reflect the black rays, making the armor seem like it was made of layers of silver plated metal.

"So hot…"

Kitten could not help but pull at his collar. She looked around at her surroundings and noticed that there was not a single green plant in this expanse of white stone mounds. There were only a few black, wilted vines that were lying on a large stone that they passed by, which looked like it had died of thirst for a long time.

"What kind of hellish place is this?! The sun in the sky is already too hot, so why is steam still coming out of the ground?" complained Kitten suddenly in a loud and impatient tone.

Old Man glanced past her impatiently, before looking at Garen, who remained indifferent, and Red Umbrella, who looked drowsy.

"These changes probably occurred after the turmoil. The stone mounds were originally filled with steam, and when I was a lecturer at the Ender Kingdom University, I once brought students here to observe them. The ground here is filled with steam, and has extremely high temperatures, but apparently desert type phenomena have yet to appear here, a sign that there is an abundance of underground water beneath. So…"

"So, there's definitely a hot spring here?!" said Kitten excitedly suddenly. She could feel that her whole body was sticky and full of sweat. The natural temperature balancing effects of the black clothes were completely useless against the frighteningly high temperatures. The terrifying temperature here had already reached forty to fifty degrees. She could only occasionally use some of her Totem Light to deflect some of the strong heat.

Old Man nodded his head surely.

"Hot spring? Taking a dip inside and sleeping will surely make me feel much more comfortable!" An expectant look appeared on Red Umbrella's face as well, showing signs that he had regained some of his energy too.

Kid widened both of his big eyes as well, as he looked around at his surroundings.

Meanwhile, Garen pondered thoughtfully.

"Old Man, you used to be a Forger, so you should know about the War Guild's War Chain right?"

Chapter 404: Hot Spring 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Of course. That was the basis of the War Guild, and the other forces had no way of reproducing it whatsoever. I researched it for a period of time as well and attempted to reproduce it, but unfortunately, I failed," Old Man nodded in reply.

"This place has an abundance of geothermal heat. Could you help me reform a War Chain? I want to upgrade the level of the Chain because this thing can be used for Solidifying and Permanent Tactics to covertly increase the powers of the members of the Chain. It's quite useful," Garen said immediately.

"Just upgrading it should be no problem, but retrieving some of the required materials will be quite troublesome. The War Guild constantly monopolizes these rare materials, making it difficult for outside forgers to obtain." Old Man shook his head to say that they had no choice. "Leader, if you want to upgrade the level of the Chain, you must upgrade it at the War Guild. There's a branch in the Kovitan Kingdom."

"Alright…" Frankly, Garen did not harbor any expectations and was merely asking around, but received the expected answer straight from Old Man's lips. Core items like these were definitely firmly controlled by the War Guild themselves.

Currently, the Nine-Headed Dragon's potential points were exhausted, and since there was no way to upgrade it, he had to think of other ways to upgrade his own strength.

Other than the effects of the War Chain's Solidifying Tactics, there were also Precious Heirlooms. Of course, if he were any other person, he would only be able to depend on these two paths to find a solution. The potential of his Core Totem was exhausted, and there was no way he could upgrade it, unless he switched the core. However, an Ultimate Totem that had reached its form 4 peak was not easy to cultivate, and he had undergone a lot of tribulations and misfortune in between.

After all, there were no tricks to get through this road easily. In the end, Core Totems needed to combine with their Totem Users, as this was one of the characteristics that were embodied during Spiritualization. If the Core Totem was not grown and cultivated with its Totem User since its low level stages, it would be impossible for them to merge.

If a strong individual gave a high level Totem to a low level Totem User directly, this high level Totem would not be able to adapt to the Totem User, and would cause the required Totem Strength consumption to increase rapidly in a short span of time. This would make it undergo terrifying changes that had the potential to suck the life out of a low level Totem User.

A Totem User needed to cultivate their Totems to ensure that the Totems would feed the Totem User themselves during the process, so that their respective natures would be able to match with one another gradually. This was in order to reach the final combination stage in the end.

Natures that were not matched, regardless of the level of the Totem, would only be burdens and encumbrances to the Totem User, and would not be of any support at all.

Thus, carelessly changing Core Totems was something that only low level Totem Users would attempt, because once they reached higher levels, only a handful of individuals would be willing to pay such a hefty price. After all, changing one's Core Totem and cultivating it from the start again would require a painstaking amount of time and effort.

Most people, even the talented ones, needed at least ten years or more. Every high level Totem that they cultivated required sources of astronomical proportions.

However, Garen was different because of his regenerative abilities. Although he had to cultivate his Totems, his Totems themselves would also feed his circulatory system, which was caused by his regenerative abilities that increased the speed of his terrifying evolution.

The time taken for him to cultivate his Totems were much faster compared to the other Totem Users. As long as his Potential Points were sufficient, he could increase his efficiency to a terrifying degree.

Garen was still pleased with the abilities of the Nine-Headed Dragon. Nine lives that could constantly be refilled through his regenerative powers easily made it a perfect match with his abilities! Perhaps it would be stronger if he changed it to a different Totem, but it would not necessarily have the same kind of powerful skills and abilities.

Next, he had to consider how to strengthen the Nine Headed Dragon.

God Cloud and the other Marshalls all had Form 5 Totems, while the Nine Headed Dragon was Garen's only Form 4 peak Totem. If he did not coordinate it with the strength of his physical body, it would be impossible for him to defeat something that was Form 5. However, his strength was only a rough guess, as actual combat would depend on his creativity, Precious Heirlooms and other means. The difference between their basic skills, however, would always be an existing factor. His other means were merely add-ons, and did not mean that his nature belonged to the Form 5 level.

Garen sat on the white rhinoceros while his ideas became clearer.

He looked at his current Attribute Pane immediately.

'Strength 14. Agility 10. Vitality 10. Intelligence 10. Potential 2218%. Obtained Luminarist qualifications.

Secret Technique -- Myriad Water Jasper Technique, Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills.'

He skipped the rest.

The blood-red symbols in his Skill Pane represented his skills and their respective explanations. Garen himself was unclear of the number of skills that he had achieved, but since his Skill Pane was filled with symbols, he knew that he had obtained at least ten different types. Some of them were even accumulated from the Secret Technique world.

His attention was immediately turned towards the relationship between his Secret Techniques and Core Totem.

"The Secret Techniques are currently at the first level of the Myriad Water Jasper Technique."

It appeared on the Skill Pane clearly.

'Myriad Water Jasper Technique: Level one (Five levels in total, One of Neptune's top level ancient martial arts, used to increase the adaptability of one's body to water, and can be used to control a large amount of liquid flow."

Garen was unsure about this exceptional Secret Technique, as it was just something that he had traded with Celine for the Divine Statue Technique earlier.

That sly little fox Celine thought that she had been taken advantage of. She did not expect that the Divine Statue Technique was an Ultimate Secret Technique that only existed in theory, as the average person would not be able to adapt to it. All of this was only possible because of the Potential Points that Garen used to achieve this result. Once that cheat had been given to someone else, there was no way they could train themselves to use it.

Now that the Divine Statue Technique was gone, Garen had lost his immense physical strength and regenerative abilities in exchange for the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, and from the look of it, this new skill was not especially powerful.

He looked at his remaining Potential Points, and realized that there were only 22 points left.

He attempted to focus his gaze on the Myriad Water Jasper Technique to stop it.

There were no changes at all… Everything was still the same as it was earlier.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows. All this while he had been thinking about how he only needed ten or more points to upgrade his Secret Techniques in the past, whereas new issues had occurred now.

"It's very likely that my Potential Points are insufficient," he said as the guess appeared in his mind.

Right now, he was about to combine with the Nine Headed Dragon. The Nine Headed Dragon possessed a huge body, entirely filled with terrifyingly powerful spirits. Moreover, it also had nine lives!

A huge physical body foundation such as this was completely unlike his initial human body, and the difference was enormous.

These changes were probably caused by its difference in foundation.

A weak human body required a small amount of energy to be transformed, thus the large Nine Headed Dragon naturally did not undergo a large transformation as well.

For example, if the foundation was 1, the transformation would only need a single digit to easily undergo a large change. If the foundation was 10000, the changes of the new digits would not be substantial, and would not affect it at all.

Once he realized this point, Garen decided to attempt to accumulate a large amount of Potential Points. At the same time, he wanted to go to the War Guild in the Kingdom to upgrade his War Chain. He also wanted to see another one of the Chain's members, Angel.

She was the woman that he had once worked with in Iron Tank City, but now he was unsure of the progress of her and her group. Initially, she was already an elite Form 2 Totem User. Right now, he did not know whether or not she had entered Form 3.

Returning to his senses, he realized that his line of people had gradually entered a rocky area that was shrouded in mist. Their surroundings were still filled with the same jagged stones, except that muddy, slightly white colored flowing water had appeared in the stone cracks.

The flowing water formed large and small potholes that were all filled with hot steam that floated around endlessly.

Old Man stood in front of the line and led the way.

"It's not often that I drop by here, so I don't know if the hot spring in front still exists, but we should go there and clean our bodies."

"We can rest properly here for a day. This road is much faster than the one we took to get here. Thanks to Leader!" fawned Kitten as she smiled at Garen, before noticing that the latter was closing his eyes and concentrating, without looking at her at all.

"Hmmph!" Kitten pouted angrily.

"Is there anything good to eat here?" Meanwhile, Kid was busy thinking about food.

"There used to be whitebait here that tasted alright, and were good when roasted or made into soup. It's also full of nourishment to top it off. I don't know whether they're still here or not," replied Old Man, smiling.

"I don't think we should waste time here, so we can return to the Kingdom faster. If you want to bathe just do it quickly," said Garen absently.

"Leader, don't you need to rest? After running around for such a long time with such a dirty body… Can I ask you something, when was the last time you bathed?" Kitten retorted impatiently.

"Huh?" Garen's gaze drifted over.

The latter jumped off the rhinoceros suddenly, and hid behind Red Umbrella immediately as she had been frightened to the point where she was too afraid to come out.

"Lea… L-leader, I know that someone as kind hearted as yourself would not be offended by the little joke that I just made!" Kitten hid behind Red Umbrella's back and shouted loudly, speaking in one breath without stopping to breathe.

The others could not help but laugh softly. Before Garen's arrival, Kitten had always been the uncontrollable one in the group with a fiery mouth, and Red Umbrella who was the only one who could control her and was therefore unbothered.

No one expected that Garen's arrival would cause her to act like a mouse that had just seen a cat, thus keeping her in check at the same time.

"Men's bath times and women's ages have something in common, they are both things that you cannot ask. Understood?" said Garen coldly as he glared at Kitten who was still hiding behind Red Umbrella's back.

"Un… Understood!" Kitten nodded seriously, her whole face ghostly pale. Red Umbrella, the white rhinoceros below them, and Kitten herself had all been frightened until their entire bodies were frozen.

"That's good." Satisfied, Garen returned his gaze.

The two people and the animal breathed a sigh of relief simultaneously.

After going through this period of teasing, the atmosphere of the group had become slightly livelier.

Soon, bigger stones appeared in front of them, and the potholes in the middle of the rocks increased as well, and became bigger. Some of the potholes had become the size of little ponds with grey colored water that flowed out endlessly and constantly.

Shh…

In one of the stone cracks in front, white water mist was spraying outwards like a high pressured water gun. The water mist sprayed outwards for a little while and then stopped, as if it was accumulating power before every gush.

The air was filled with water vapor, and every few meters it became difficult to see the others, and was occasionally so blurry that only black figures could be seen.

"A little further in front and you'll see the hot springs. Be careful, everyone. I haven't been here after the turmoil and I don't know whether any monsters are entrenched here," said Old Man loudly.

But the surprising part was that although the crowd had reached the large hot spring pool that Old Man led them to, there was not a single monster in sight.

Garen began to think that a stronger monster had designated this area as its territory. Thus, once they had reached their confirmed location, he began to survey the area. However, he soon realized that there were still no monsters to be seen, causing him to feel slightly confused.

These rocky areas were shrouded in white smoke. The surrounding temperatures reached over thirty degrees, while the core temperatures were up to fifty, sixty degrees. The highest temperatures of the hot springs were had almost reached a hundred degrees.

Large clouds of hot steam floated upwards, and formed a thick layer of black clouds in the sky.

He was unsure whether it was an illusion or not, but when Garen arched his head upwards, he noticed that the black cloud was changing its shape, and twisting and turning slightly.

Chapter 405: Hot Spring 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It felt as though the black cloud itself was alive.

Garen narrowed his eyes slightly and felt a tremble in his heart, as he activated the Eye of Isaiah and looked towards the black cloud.

The black cloud continued to move along normally, except that it had slowed down slightly, with no other signs of abnormalities.

He returned his gaze and took a look around his surroundings. He did not notice anything suspicious.

Returning via his initial route, he passed through a few stone forests filled with large rocks and noticed a medium sized, oval shaped hot spring pool in front of him.

Large clouds of steam rose up as the air suddenly became humid and damp. Garen felt as though his skin had been covered in a sticky layer.

He heard vague laughing noises coming from the direction of the hot spring which sounded like female voices.

The exterior of the hot spring pools was barricaded by a circle of large stone pillars, an obvious sign that people had moved them over as blockades.

Near one of the outer stone pillars, Red Umbrella and Old Man sat cross-legged on the floor while chatting about an unknown topic. Kid was drawing on the surface of one of the stone pillars with his fingers to amuse himself.

When he saw Garen walking over, Old Man waved the jerky in his hands.

"We were planning to use the water here to cook some meat soup. Would you like some, Leader?"

"Have you found the whitebait fish?" Garen asked immediately, as he walked over to sit cross-legged on the floor with the others.

Old Man shook his head as a hesitant expression appeared on his face. "It’s strange, I easily got a net full of whitebait the last time I fished here, but now it seems like I can’t even see one. It would be an unlikely assumption to say that a monster had dived underwater and eaten all of the whitebait. We used our Totems to dive deep into the water, but we couldn’t find traces of any creatures even when we reached the bottom."

"We didn’t find anything in the surroundings either," said Garen, shaking his head. "This place seems kind of strange. We’ll let them finish bathing first and then we’ll leave at once. I wouldn’t want to wait around here."

"That’s fine," Old Man nodded his head.

"Don’t, I still want to soak… It’s been three months without bathing…" Red Umbrella groaned suddenly.

"Three months…" Garen and Old Man were speechless now.

"Every time I’ve thought of bathing before I sleep, but every time I just fall asleep first…" Red Umbrella was beginning to feel embarrassed now, and laughed it off.

"Just go and rest for now, while we still have time." Garen glanced at Kid and noticed that the usually strange Kid was now acting normally, a sign that this place was not entirely problematic.

He crossed his legs and closed his eyes, before sitting on the rock and meditating slowly.

He had planned to investigate his surroundings earlier to see if there were any monsters that he could use to obtain Potential Points, but unfortunately there was not a single monster to be seen.

Garen adjusted his state of mind properly, before he slowly immersed himself in the state of practicing his Secret Techniques like he did in the previous world.

Practicing Secret Techniques in a world where Totems were mainly used, occasionally allowed him to reminisce on his past mistakes.

He calmed his heart as he focused his attention towards the core of his vital energy.

Unlike the Divine Statue Technique, the vital energy and blood roadmap of the Myriad Water Jasper Technique were extremely complicated, and required the flow of all of his bloodlines, regardless of whether they were large or small, main blood vessels or capillaries.

This Secret Technique was an ancient martial art passed down to him from Neptune Fist, and Garen knew the uses of some of the roadmaps, but was unclear of the uses of a large number of roadmaps.

While practicing the Divine Statue Technique, his control of his physical body reached an unprecedented degree, and bloodline flow roadmaps that he himself did not understand appeared as well.

He followed the instructions of the Secret Techniques.

The first level of the Myriad Water Jasper Technique resulted in the effect of being able to control the flow of vital energy from a one meter radius. This type of control overlapped between the categories of humans and nonhumans, and would affect all living things that had blood flowing through their veins.

The second level was used to enhance the range, while the third level was used to enhance strength and to control power.

However, he was unclear regarding the following levels, as Celine had only trained until the third level, while the fourth level could only be achieved successfully by professionals from Neptune Fist. He was unclear about its exact abilities.

The Myriad Water Jasper Technique was one of the hardest main Secret Techniques to be learnt from Neptune Fist. Some said that other than the creator, no one else had managed to achieve such a high level.

Once Garen had closed his eyes, he concentrated and began to adjust the flow of the vital energy in his body to circulate towards a specific roadmap. There were far too many blood vessels that he had to operate, and even if his energies were stronger, one large circulation required at least two hours.

Moreover, this type of flowing movement was extremely difficult because the movement of vital energy required a fixed speed, and the slightest change would result in a huge setback.

An illusion began to form in Garen’s mind, telling him that if he wanted to combine with the Nine Headed Dragon, he would need to pass through this Secret Technique Roadmap as well.

The noises in his surrounding began to echo as though from a distance, as time continued to tick pass. His consciousness slowly drifted towards the stage where he had forgotten himself.

*****************

Old Man and Red Umbrella sat beside Garen. One of them closed his eyes and held a black box in their hands, listening to an unknown sound, while the other remained in his old ways, yawning constantly and dozing off to sleep.

Meanwhile, Kid lay on his back on the floor, unbothered by the heat of the ground, as he stared upwards at the white gas. Occasionally, he would glanced at Garen who was doing cross-legged exercises.

The noises surrounding the hot spring pools changed from excited comfortable sounds to soft voices, as sounds of people getting out of the water could be heard as well. It seemed like Kitten and Fox had finished bathing, and were getting ready to get out.

Old Man, who was listening to the black box, opened his eyes suddenly.

"After this quest is over, do you have any plans, Red Umbrella?"

"Plans?" Red Umbrella covered his mouth and yawned a few times. "Going home to sleep properly for a few days… No I can’t, it’s too difficult."

"With Leader around, don’t you plan on doing any level upgrading quests?" Old Man wiggled his eyebrows.

"Won’t you guys still be around?"

Old Man remained silent as he looked at Kid who was standing on the sidelines.

"Kid, after this quest is over, do you have any plans?"

"Going back to the farm," said Kid in a crisp, abrupt manner.

"Do you want to stay with us in the Kingdom?"

"Why?" Kid asked hesitantly.

"There’s nothing wrong if you choose to stay on the outskirts alone. The current situation has almost calmed down by now. The monster lairs in most places have mostly already been confirmed as dangerous zones, and the activity areas have been clearly stated on the maps. Hence, as long as we don’t loiter around, we won’t be in serious danger. The situations in most countries have calmed down, and the defense lines have also been solidified. Without exterior threats, orderly rebuildings of new societies will come next. This kind of order is still being tested out, but under these circumstances, we as part of the armed forces will receive much greater benefits than before if we stay in the Kingdom, unlike during the tumultuous period when the armed forces was the department that had the highest casualty rates."

Old Man paused for a moment.

"Our Kovitan, Daniela, and Ender built the West Farm defense together. After that we built the three major areas. As well as a few small organizations that survived in the secure catch. In this era, one cannot live on without power, and thus, those that control powerful abilities like ourselves will benefit greatly."

"Old Man, you’re thinking of becoming a solicitor for the princess, right? I remember you putting yourself under her command last year?" Red Umbrella brought up lazily.

"Since you already knew about that, that’s why I brought it up," nodded Old Man. "It’s true that I’m working for the princess. Although His Majesty Avic has great talents and strong forces, he is still dispirited sometimes, and thus under all circumstances, the princess is naturally the best choice. After my family pledged our services to Her Majesty the Princess, we received great care, and thus this was the obvious decision."

"That’s your problem. I don’t want to hang around someone else and do their work. Remaining in the Secret Service is fine by me. The benefits are good, the treatment is good, the positions are high, plus it’s also relaxing," said Red Umbrella, as he smiled with both of his hands behind his head.

"What about you, Kid?" Old Man looked towards the little guy on the side.

A similarly bored expression appeared on Kid’s face.

"I’ll go with Leader."

"What if Leader joins me as one of Her Majesty the Princess’ subordinates?" Old man smiled suddenly.

"I’ll just go with Leader," nodded Kid confidently.

"That’s good. Look, Leader will surely join us as well," smiled Old Man as he patted Kid’s head.

Soon, Fox and Kitten who had just changed into a new set of clothes walked towards them after getting out of the hot spring. Both of them had changed into white clothes that resembled figure-hugging swordsman’s uniforms, except that there were short cloaks hanging off their backs, which made them look exceptionally cool. Both of them were exposing their beautiful, pale legs.

Unfortunately, not a single person there was giving them a second glance.

Kid did not understand anything, while Old Man had a lot of past experience, as shown on his calm expression. Red Umbrella was busy dozing off.

All that was left was their sane male leader Garen, who was still closing his eyes and resting, as if he were meditating.

Kitten twitched her lip regretfully and glanced at Fox, as she began to feel like it was a wrong decision to hang around in this group.

Fox continued to cover her face, making it impossible to read her expression.

Old Man explained Leader’s actions to them, before Kitten and Fox expressed their understanding.

Garen opened his eyes slowly at this moment as well.

He glanced at the sky and noticed that the dark clouds were still the same.

After hesitating for a while, he realized that he had not bathed for a long time.

Although he could prevent dust and dirt from sticking on his body as a Totem User, he could not do the same for the sweat that his body released. He used his Secret Technique to control his body, allowing his secreted sweat to be released out of his body through other methods. However, the others did not have this ability.

Looking at Kid and Red Umbrella’s pleading expressions, he felt that he had been slightly cruel towards them. Allowing someone who had gone three months without bathing to not be able to enter a hot spring…

"Okay, okay. Since we’re here, we might as well bathe," sighed Garen. "I’ll go soak for a bit as well."

"We’ll guard the door!" Kitten exclaimed immediately.

"Wise Leader!!" Red Umbrella was the first one to jump up, before he ran to the white rhinoceros that was not far away and quickly found four black towels, which he gave to each of the men. After that he brought a little bottle of shower gel that had dark red flower petals floating inside. There were filament like red flower petals.

Garen and the other men each took a towel and walked into the man-made hot spring in the stone forest.

There was an oval shaped pool inside that was steaming with clouds of hot air, while there were stone pillars of different lengths that surrounded the pool in a circle, forming only one entry point.

The four men took off their clothes quickly, exposing their once hidden body shapes.

The white mist made it hard to see clearly, but Garen could still see the faces of the three other people.

Old Man had a kindly, elderly face and wore a pair of silver-rimmed spectacles, and was currently using a white cloth to wipe the glass. If he was seen at a library or a similar place, people would assume that he was a university researcher or scholar. However, there were rumours that he was actually once a scholar.

Red Umbrella had short red hair, a pair of slanting, flyaway eyebrows, and unusually handsome features. Coupled with his red eyes and porcelain skin, he definitely looked like a well-bred aristocratic prince.

Kid removed his clothes, and exposed his bony slender body that lacked flesh. His skin was dry and it was obvious that he was underdeveloped. His eyes were also sunken, his dark brown hair was coarse and messy, and there were freckles on the tip of his nose.

But none of these were important. The strangest thing was that Kid’s skin completely lacked the colour of blood. He was terribly pale.

Garen glanced at him a few more times unconsciously.

Only then did he remove his clothes and throw them onto the stone by the side of the pool carelessly.

Garen walked into the water and sat down, allowing his golden, shoulder-length hair to float on the surface of the water. He immersed his entire body into the water, exposing the parts above his chin only.

The temperature of the water was just right, at almost forty degrees.

Garen closed his eyes, and finally let go of the tight nerves that he had been holding on for so long.

Excluding the moments when he was in the outskirts such as this, Garen could never let go of his nerves completely. He always needed to keep his guard up in case a strange phenomena occurred, or in case a strong monster decided to attack out of the blue.

However, his own team mates were keeping guard now, and some of them were even soaking with him, which allowed him to not worry about issues regarding his safety for awhile.

Unconsciously, Garen drifted into a half asleep state.

Before he’d upgraded the Myriad Water Jasper Technique, this scene had appeared once, and now, it was appearing a second time.

Chapter 406: Hot Spring 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Amidst the blurriness, he saw the large, ten metres tall metal door again.

The borders of the door were filled with dark red rust marks that left faint patterns, as though fine, complex and gorgeous lines had once been engraved there.

Hungry…

So hungry…

Garen realised that he had turned into that pitiful, little Dual Headed Salamander again.

His entire body was covered in dirty scales, and he was only slightly more than three meters long. A strong sensation of hunger rumbled throughout his belly continuously.

Too hungry…

Garen unconsciously hit one of its heads against the large door violently.

Bang!

A loud noise echoed from the metal door as a slit revealed itself when it was pushed open.

Bang bang bang!! Bang bang bang!!

The sound of loud footsteps echoed from behind the door suddenly as if a large creature was pacing back and forth with heavy rhythmic stomping noises, that walked and stopped continuously.

The little Dual Headed Salamander could not suppress its hunger any longer. It was starving and it followed its instincts by attempting to push the large door open, before crawling inside slowly.

Garen hid inside its body and looked out quietly while experiencing everything, as if he was the Dual Headed Salamander.

Behind the door was a large black wasteland that was surrounded by broken and damaged walls.

A rotting stench permeated the air.

The little Dual Headed Salamander crawled inside clumsily before noticing that right in front of it, stood a tall, large black church.

The church was sturdy and well-built, but the sound of the heavy footsteps from earlier had echoed from within it.

Bang bang!!

The loud footsteps rang from the church once again.

The little salamander raised its head and looked towards the sky.

The sky was filled with large grey clouds that gave off a heavy feeling of hopelessness. It looked like someone had used a pencil to scrawl on a sheet of white paper, staining it with grey blotches that gave off an unclean sensation.

He did not know why, but Garen currently felt more awake than before.

He could vaguely feel that this little Dual Headed Salamander seemed to be a native ancestor from the ancient times, of the Nine Headed Dragon that he had evolved.

That was from an era when countless salamanders still existed, possibly more than ten thousand years ago in the Totem World.

In the history of humankind within the Totem World, there was only about six thousand years of history that up to the present day. This included the time periods from two different calendars; the current solar calendar that had spanned almost three thousand and five hundred years, and the ancient calendar from the past that spanned over two thousand years. When added together, there were almost six thousand years in total.

This was the journey of human civilization, from the wilderness to development.

Moreover, the period where the Dual Headed Salamander still existed was at least twenty million years away.

To think that during an era in which humankind had yet to plant the seed of civilization, a man-made building like this actually existed…

A sense of curiosity began to bubble up inside Garen suddenly.

For such a large door and an enormous church like this, how had it been built?

Perhaps everything would be revealed when the Dual Headed Salamander entered the church.

The little Dual Headed Salamander walked towards the large church clumsily.

The large black church resembled a tall black mountain that stood in front of it. It cast a large grey shadow.

As the Dual Headed Salamander got closer, the loud footsteps inside the church began to quieten down, and soon stopped completely. Everything was immersed in the silence of despair once again.

This whole world seemed to lack any signs of life; there were no green plants, no flying insects, and no chirping of birds.

Unable to see any of its brethren or any remaining living beings, the little salamander was all alone.

It stood in front of the enormous black copper door of the church and glanced at the remains of the door, which resembled the strange face of a bat. The little salamander suddenly hesitated.

Garen could feel the incomparable fear rising up in its heart. That strong sense of fear was caused by the incomparable terror that existed within the church. From the sound of its footsteps, he could tell that the bastard inside the church was at least fifty meters tall, and was definitely a humongous giant. One stomp was all it needed to crush the three meter tall salamander into meat sauce.

But the little salamander had been wandering the vicinity for far too long, and this place was the only area where it had found the existence of other living things.

The other places were all filled with silence and despair without any other life forms, not even plants. There was only wreckage, as if the whole world had been rent and destroyed. It felt as though it was currently walking towards its death.

To go in? Not to go in?

The little salamander’s brain was wrestling with itself violently right now.

In this world where the sun did nothing to warm the land, it had wandered for many years, eating roots and wet soil and barely surviving. Now that even the roots were beginning to wilt to death, it had no other options to turn to anymore.

Finally, the little salamander pressed its main head against the large door steadily, and began to push strongly.

Woo…

Garen opened his eyes suddenly and woke up.

His surroundings were still filled with white misty water vapor. He was still half-lying inside the hot spring pool.

His bright golden hair was spread out on the surface of the water, and he could see himself vaguely from the reflection in the water, before he noticed that the three red marks on his forehead were beginning to bleed suddenly.

He reached his hand out to touch it, before bringing his fingers downwards, and noticing that his fingertips were stained with fresh red blood.

"Is this an after effect?" Garen murmured to himself.

Obtaining strength quickly would always require one to give a designated trade-off in exchange. This was the biggest disadvantage of not acquiring the basics. Garen had always been worried about the after effects that would occur in himself.

Initially, he assumed that his heart might have undergone a rejection reaction, but now he found out that the most troublesome part was that he would have to relive the memories of the salamander’s ancestors that were encoded in its genes.

These memories were merely parts and pictures to a simple-minded salamander. However, to Garen, as a human, he could use them to find important information.

"Leader? Are you okay?" Red Umbrella was sitting a short distance away from Garen, and had noticed that his forehead was bleeding as well as the scent of blood.

"I’m fine, it’s just a minor issue," Garen answered lightly.

Red Umbrella saw from his expression that he did not want to say anything else, and thus he stopped asking.

He looked on as Leader’s handsome pale face began to sink into the water slowly, and noticed that the three dot marks on his forehead continued bleeding slightly. Leader’s face was completely expressionless, as if everything was normal.

Red Umbrella had always felt that Leader emitted a strange air throughout his entire body. It seemed as if this body he was approaching was not human, but a monstrous wild beast instead.

He glanced at Kid who was standing on the other side, and thought about how this child was no older than fourteen or fifteen years old, yet possessed terrifying powers and had managed to reach the peak of Form 3.

Meanwhile, his body was covered by deathly pale skin, without a single sign of blood.

Even after soaking in the hot spring for such a long time, in forty degrees water, not a tinge of red coloured his little face.

Kid seemed like a corpse when he immersed his whole body in the water like that.

These two people were stranger than others, and Red Umbrella felt that as a normal person, he should not come into too close proximity with them.

He inched away slowly and quietly to rest at the other end of the hot spring.

At this moment, Old Man approached Garen quietly.

"Leader, can we speak alone?"

"Speak alone?" Garen lifted his head out of the water and wiped the water off his face. The blood on his forehead dripped down his nose to the corner of his lips, and Garen stuck his tongue out to lick at it. He was unsure why his emotions were beginning to feel an inexplicable sense of irritability.

"What do you want to talk about?" He closed his eyes again and waited for Old Man’s next words.

Old Man tidied up his train of thought and looked at Garen’s calm face, before glancing at the other two people, before softening his voice.

"I don’t know whether you are aware that I’m actually a Totem User under the command of the princess?"

"Princess?" Garen had no impressions of this person. "I’m not that familiar with her, I’ve only heard that she is very competent. And she’s also a wise leader."

"During this quest, I was actually sent with the Princess’s sincerity. Not just for yourself, but also for the other members in the group, as her Majesty the Princess wishes for an opportunity to work with all of you," said Old Man with an honest look in his eyes.

"What do you mean? You want me to join you as one of the princess’s subordinates?" said Garen as a playful look appeared on his face suddenly. Him? A=He was a first class fighter that could even take on Obscuro Society’s Marshall God Cloud head on.

He still had a high level friend like Goth by his side, and he was also part of a loyalist family that had received Avic’s trust, giving him a high position in the interior of the empire. To think that this princess would not solicit him personally, but chose to ask Old Man to pass on the message instead.

"You’re not wrong about that," nodded Old Man. "The princess wants talented individuals, and prioritizes those who are strong and competent. If a strong individual like yourself joined our ranks, it would truly be a large blessing to our camp."

"So what kind of remunerations can you give me?" said Garen as a somewhat playful expression appeared on his face. "I’m treated like an Earl in the Secret Service, so what kind of promises can you grant me?"

Old Man did not say much, but withdrew a black scroll from his clothes beside the pond instead, pulled off the string, and opening it delicately.

This scroll was resistant to water, and had started to emit a faint black light in the midst of the mist. The rows of handwritten words on the scroll began to vibrate slightly.

Garen looked at the scroll and noticed that the writing was engraved in a secret language using Totem Light. It was written in a type of secret cryptography, and could only be read after it was decompiled.

"What is this?" Garen looked up at Old Man.

Old Man remained silent and outstretched his hand to point at the end of the scroll carefully.

Garen looked in the direction of his finger and noticed faint traces of a seal there.

He was slightly shaken when he realised that this was the special seal used by the royal family of the Kovitan Empire, which was also the emperor’s seal that only Avic possessed.

"This scroll was sent by His Majesty the Emperor?"

Old Man nodded.

"Do you still remember the incident where the king’s daughter was stabbed in the kingdom some time ago?"

Garen’s heart skipped a beat.

He’d assumed that the incident had occurred silently, and that he had destroyed all of the witnesses, he did not think that…

"What do you mean?" he asked quietly as he looked at Old Man.

"It’s very simple, now Avic has started to doubt you as well. Meanwhile, the ones that can truly help you within the entire kingdom, are only limited to us!" He said his last sentence in a louder tone, while a confident expression appeared on his face.

"Tell me the password." Garen’s expression had changed slightly.

If he wanted to beat God Cloud now, the battle at Snowy Peak would shake the world. However, the strength to face an entire empire was something that he still lacked right now.

It did not matter how much hidden strength Avic kept hidden, as the professionals on the surface of the empire were bad enough. The two Grand Dukes, defense minister Veska, and the three pillars of the empire were all extremely powerful strengths that were hard to understand. Once the stabbing incident was exposed, he would turn from a loyalist of the empire to a wanted convict immediately. It did not matter to him, but Big Sister Hathaway, Goth, and his other relatives would not be able to escape. They would all be involved.

After Old Man told Garen the password, he decoded the entire message carefully, as all of the contents of the scroll displayed themselves clearly.

‘Permission granted to examine the head of the Trejons household thoroughly, but it must be done in secret.’

Garen narrowed his eyes.

"This doesn’t mean anything, right?"

"Does it really not mean anything?" Old Man replied with a smile.

Garen grew silent for a moment.

"You aren’t worried that I hand this over to His Majesty?"

Old Man continued to smile but did not answer.

Garen knew that if this was real, even if he did hand it over to His Majesty, it would not benefit him at all.

Moreover, just like what he’d said earlier, the only one that could help him was the princess who was seated in a high position. With an important individual in the palace grasping the entire situation, his own control of his dangerous position would increase greatly as well.

Furthermore, for the other man to give this to him so confidently, it meant that he was not afraid that he would hand it over to His Majesty.

"His Majesty’s doubts are doubts. In the end, the stabbing of the king’s daughter was not something that I carried out, so I have nothing to worry about," smiled Garen, as he steadied his emotions.

Chapter 407: Princess 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"If you think of it that way, you’re making a huge mistake," said Old Man, shaking his head. "Although you’re an exceptionally powerful individual, His Majesty’s doubts are still doubts. We don’t know for sure if he contacted you just because of these uncertainties. He definitely has a more farsighted plan, of course? Your father’s contributions then were not done in vain, right?"

"We should stop our discussion here for now." Garen closed his eyes, unwilling to talk further.

The Black Prince had already arrived in the Kingdom, and Avic’s stabbing incident would be exposed, which would cause an uproar in the Kingdom. Then it wouldn’t matter if he wanted to seek refuge with her, the question of whether the princess would even be able to protect herself was already a problem.

Moreover, as to whether or not Avic knew that he had killed the daughter of a king, realistically the nature of the incident was already very severe. However, when he thought about it carefully, he realized that it was not an issue that was too serious.

He had powers equivalent to a Form 5 Totem User himself and was probably the strongest person in the entire Kingdom. The battle at Snowy Peak proved that he had achieved that level. To fall out with him merely for the sake of a king’s daughter, was beyond someone who was as wise as Avic.

The Trejons family of the past may have encountered terrible disasters because of this. However, now, it was different.

Before Garen could switch his status completely, he was already cornered by Old Man. When he thought back about this now, he realized that there was nothing serious to be worried about.

Old Man and the others only needed to look at Garen’s expression to know that this rationale was something that he could not refuse.

He did not bother to overthink it, this was not one of the key bargaining chips in the beginning anyway.

"Since we’ve come to this, just wait until we’ve arrived at the Kingdom so the princess can speak to you personally. Frankly, ever since you handed your household treasure over to His Majesty Avic, Her Majesty has wanted to speak to you. The problem was not that you didn’t have time to speak to her, rather, Her Majesty was the one who had no time."

"Then we’ll wait until we arrive at the Kingdom to continue discussing this matter," answered Garen simply.

Old Man shook his head and did not say another word.

From their perspective, Garen was a royal minder that would hold on stubbornly, and would never change his mind so quickly. Right now, he was only trying to create a sliver of doubt in Garen’s heart, to create uncertainties in his loyal heart towards Avic.

The tasks thereafter would require Her Majesty to speak to him personally.

Regarding the princess, Old Man had unshakeable confidence in her.

He moved away slowly and stopped bothering Garen, choosing instead to run towards Red Umbrella on the other side to speak to him.

Garen had actually seen through Old Man’s intentions.

However, he knew that future forces and the Obscuro Society were ready to stab the king, which would then throw the Kingdom into a state of turmoil. Before the situation cleared up, it was too early to be discussing these matters.

The steam in the hot spring continued to rise, and at once, Garen immersed himself in his thoughts again.

He did not know why there was an unknown irritability bubbling up inside his heart. He kept trying to think, but was unable to focus quietly.

Whoosh!!

Garen stood up from the water suddenly and used his Secret Techniques to dry off the steam on his body, before grabbing his clothes from the side of the pool and putting them on quickly.

"I’m going to take a walk first, you guys can take your time to soak."

"Okay, we’re almost done as well," answered Old Man hurriedly.

Red Umbrella made a sound of agreement as well.

Garen walked out of the hot spring with long strides and saw Fox outside using a dry towel to wipe her long hair, while Kitten sat on the side and laughed happily about something.

When both of them saw Garen come out, they frantically stood up cautiously.

"Leader."

"You’re done bathing, Leader?"

"Yes," answered Garen simply with a slightly impatient tone. He did not know why his heart had been filled with an uncomfortable irritating feeling since just now.

He was about to make a round around his surroundings before a loud angry yell echoed from the hot spring suddenly.

"Get lost!"

It sounded like Red Umbrella’s voice.

"I only had good intentions, Red Umbrella. Don’t you get the wrong idea!!" Old Man’s anger-filled voice could be heard as well.

"What’s going on?!"

Garen raised his voice and asked the people inside.

Instantly, the three people came out one after another, two of them fuming with anger. They seemed to have started fighting. Meanwhile, Kid walked behind them, clad in his brand new black skirted armor.

"It’s nothing, just a little quarrel. Leader, don’t worry about it," said Old Man, suppressing his anger determinedly.

"All my life I’ve hated it when others tried to threaten me!" Red Umbrella replied coldly from the side.

As he looked at both of their faces, Garen did not know why violent emotions started bubbling up inside his heart suddenly.

Could these weak pieces of trash give him some peace of mind?! Not only had he protected them throughout the journey, did he have to be responsible for their mental health as well? He was their leader, not their nanny!

The anger inside him grew stronger.

The air around him began to solidify gradually, and the atmosphere became more and more tense.

Suddenly, a shock quaked through Garen’s mind, and he began to feel like something was wrong.

As a fighter who had extreme control over his own abilities, he had always understood his physical changes like the back of his hand. Moreover, practicing his Secret Techniques had allowed him to repair some parts of himself as well.

But currently, Garen felt that something was not right.

Usually, he would not get upset at others so easily.

Furthermore, Old Man and Red Umbrella were usually mild tempered as well. How did they get mad so suddenly?

He glanced past Kitten and Fox.

Kitten’s brows were currently furrowed as she glared at Old Man angrily, as she was obviously furious at Old Man who had picked a fight with Red Umbrella.

Meanwhile, Fox had a cold expression on her face, a sign that she was somewhat upset as well.

"Is this place making us all like this?!" A thought flashed through Garen’s mind.

He glanced at the expressionless Kid again and noticed that the little guy had a sleepy look on his face, and seemed to be completely unconcerned about the emotions of his teammates.

Garen raised his head again and looked at the sky, noticing that the dark clouds had moved closer, while the sentient-like feeling became more obvious.

"Shut up!"

He yelled suddenly.

"Leader!"

"What’s happening?!"

Old Man and Red Umbrella rushed forward one after another and shouted back at Garen.

A red light flashed.

Roar!!

A hostile flash illuminated Garen’s forehead, as two dreamlike red dragon heads flashed in front of him suddenly.

Bang bang!!

After the two loud strikes sounded, Old Man and Red Umbrella were both sent flying before crashing into the stony ground on both sides and rolling far away.

"Garen! You dare touch me?!" Old Man attempted to get up, but his whole body was powerless, and he could not seem to move.

"Speak again and I’ll kill you!" Murderous rage flashed in Garen’s eyes suddenly.

Old Man was shocked and could not speak anymore.

On the other side, Red Umbrella seemed to have realized that something was wrong, as his power was now slightly stronger, and one hit had made him nauseous and unable to react properly.

Garen glanced at Fox and Kitten and noticed that both their eyes had become slightly more bloodshot, as they were temporarily suppressed by his strong powers, and it would not be long before he exploded.

"Hnngh!" Garen huffed coldly as two dragon heads flashed in front of his body again.

"Don’t fight back!"

The four dragon heads bit down one person each.

While the four of them were being bitten, even if they tried to retaliate, they were currently held down by its terrifying level of suppression which made it hard for them to breathe. Not only was it hard for them to fight back, but speaking required a lot of energy as well.

"Kid, follow me!" Garen glanced at Kid.

"Okay." Kid bore no sign of abnormalities and nodded his head sincerely.

On his own, Garen brought the four others out of the misty area and ran outside quickly.

Kid returned to the white rhinoceros and took everyone’s bundles from it, before following behind Garen closely.

The group of people rushed along for more than an hour before the white mist in front of them gradually became thinner.

The white rocks on the ground had also decreased, and the cracks between the rocks had stopped spraying water vapor.

The mysterious irritating feeling had also finally disappeared.

Once they reached a depression in one of the large rocks, only then did Garen throw the four people he had been biting on top of the rock.

He had regulated his own breathing slightly and began to feel as if his emotions were suddenly normal now. The irritating feeling from earlier was gone.

He looked at the others and their uncomfortable faces, that seemed to have realized the strange things that happened earlier.

"I knew there was something wrong when there were no monsters there. Who would think that there was something abnormal inside!" Old Man got up and shook his head.

"Everyone was almost done for." Red Umbrella forced a smile and got up as well. "It almost caused me to fall out with Leader and Old Man, really…"

"It seems like there aren’t any places without danger in this wilderness, so we have to keep our guard up at all times. Regardless if they’re strong or weak…" Garen nodded and said seriously. "Since I fell victim to it, you guys would be more likely to. No wonder there wasn’t a single monster in that area, I didn’t expect this effect to exist."

He stopped speaking and looked at Red Umbrella and the other man, before smiling slightly.

"You two are alright, right? I attacked you a bit harshly earlier. But I believe that you won’t blame me, yes?"

"It’s fine. Don’t worry, Leader." Red Umbrella stroked the left side of his face where a burning sensation could be felt, which meant that there was no way he was fine. But after looking at Leader’s fake concerned expression, if he even dared to say that something was wrong… He remembered Garen’s murderous rage from earlier, and a chill ran down his spine unconsciously.

"No… Nothing’s wrong. Leader, you did all this to save us, and we are inexplicably grateful. How could there be anything wrong? Ha… Haha…" Old Man held the swollen part of his face that had been hit and answered jokingly.

"That’s good." A happy look appeared on Garen’s face. "Since nothing’s wrong, we’ll continue our journey, because I don’t think we can get the things that were on the white rhinoceros’ back."

"I took all of our stuff." Kid dragged six suitcases along and stood beside them, taking credit for his contributions loudly.

"Well then, this time we owe you, Kid!" Garen laughed as he patted Kid’s head.

Kitten stood on the side and rejoiced in their misery. She was angry and speechless when Garen bullied her, but now that she realized another two people had joined her side, her heart was suddenly unbelievably joyful.

Fox, on the other hand, was still analyzing the abnormalities of the place.

"If I hadn’t guessed wrongly, the misty area earlier probably had characteristics that amplified the negative emotions of large creatures." Fox’s calm voice rang out amidst all the other people.

Garen was shocked. "Amplified negative emotions?" He pondered carefully and realized it was true.

He was worried that there would be no cure for his after effects, which caused the irritated and fretful feeling. Old Man and Red Umbrella had disagreed on only one matter, and while both sides would usually compromise, this time no one had expected them to be impatient to the extent of having outbursts.

Behind them, Red Umbrella had dared to yell at someone who was stronger than himself, which was an obvious sign that something was not right.

"I’ve observed Kid for a long time. Kid has never gotten angry. He was even happy. Regardless of how others treat him, he’s never troubled and always happy," explained Fox in a soft voice. "That’s why he was the only one among us who was completely fine and did not feel threatened at all. At the time, I heard the noises as well, and began to feel an inexplicable need to explode suddenly."

Garen turned around and looked at the direction they had rushed in from, and etched this place in his heart deeply.

"We’ll stop discussing this matter here then. Let’s just hurry up and head to the Kingdom."

The others had no objections. If they had not been convinced about Garen’s strength last time, they had experienced it first hand now, and finally realized that their Leader’s strength currently surpassed theirs greatly, and the difference between them was too large, and even his mere breath could make them terrified.

Chapter 408: Princess 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kovitan's Castle

The black city stretched over the mountain top. Red and yellow lights were flashing from within.

In the evening, the kingdom's mountain roads winded down in circles, passing through a sea of white clouds to the foot of the mountain.

Within the forest at the foot of the mountain, the black-roofed white-walled civilian houses were like fine white stones. They came in all sizes. In the middle of them were civilians passing by, as if they were ants.

Several carts were carrying heavy loads of goods as they headed towards the mountain road.

The faint moonlight shined on the surface of the mountains, coating the ground with a layer of silver.

Garen's black-robed group appeared before the road to the entrance of the civilian housing district.

At the entrance, two black stone towers stood tall. Sentries were on guard with a totem user on one of the towers.

This totem user was in white robes. As he saw Garen's group of six's appearance, his face instantly turned solemn. He rushed down from the tower, appearing from the exit at the bottom with a few silver-armored soldiers behind him.

As he took the initiative to meet Garen's group, the totem user bowed his head.

"I am the totem user on guard, Anlin. May I ask you to present your passes."

As he spoke, he was assessing the group in front of him. The six of them weren't like normal totem users or martial artists. The carved golden iris pattern on the collar of their black robes showed their noble status.

Looking at their dusty bodies, it was evident that they had come from a long journey. Being able to travel long distance and passing through the area where the monsters gathered, it can only mean two things. Either they were incredibly strong, reaching the third form level, or they had strong backgrounds with the support of precious heirlooms.

As they only had a small number of six people, the possibility of the former was the largest.

Anlin had met quite a few experts, but this group of people were on par with the masters of national authority. The smell of their bodies were obviously due to their countless killings.

Garen only nodded towards him. The old man beside him quickly walked forward with a black-golden pass and handed it over.

Normally, they always flew in and out. Rarely would they enter the kingdom through the main entrance. However, he was prepared and everything was proper.

After checking, Anlin volunteered and led the way towards the second tower.

Along the journey, Garen casually talked to the man.

"I heard that the black prince is visiting the kingdom to meet His Majesty. I wonder if he's arrived in the city?"

"Sir, the prince has arrived yesterday night. I heard that he has entered the Jade Pool. After freshening up, he should be officially meeting His Majesty tomorrow." Anlin replied respectfully.

"This time the Black Prince is really a big deal. He has more than a hundred totem users following him. Rumors have said that there are also third form totem users among them. Gee.."

Garen didn't care about third form totem users. In the eyes of this second form totem user, a third form user is an immensely powerful figure. Garen wouldn't be able to obtain any information about stronger forces from him.

"When the Black Prince arrived, who was the minister who went to meet him?" He asked again.

Anlin hesitated for a moment.

"I'm not very sure myself, but if I'm not mistaken, the Foreign Affairs Minister is usually the one who does the welcoming. His Majesty would wait until the other party washed up before officially meeting him. But the Black Prince is also the king of a country. The only thing is that he doesn't have an official title. So I think they would be meeting today."

Garen nodded and took out a golden Rumb.

"Tell us about other major happenings in the past ten days."

In the era of war, the Rumb has been heavily devalued as a commodity. However, to a second form totem user, a golden Rumb was not an amount that could be neglected.

After getting the small reward, Anlin instantly felt more relieved and continued speaking.

"There is another more important piece of information. The King has decided to hold an Aegis Ceremony for the First Concubine. The only thing is we do not know what the Aegis Ceremony is. In conjunction with the Black King's visit, His Majesty has decided to hold the ceremony next Monday."

"Aegis Ceremony?" The old man looked surprised and let out a low mutter. "It should be a ceremony of trust, awarding the rights to guard the precious heirlooms.." He explained softly through the black box.

The rest of them quickly understood and instantly let out a yearning expression. It was the strongest, legendary Original Heirloom! To be able to be protected by a heirloom of this level, would be a big thing for any totem user.

Naturally, Garen was the clearest on this matter. This meant that the First Concubine or the Obscuro Society's plot were coming to a head.

He continued asking Anlin about some other trivial matters until there was absolutely nothing. Only then did Garen stop asking.

The group of them did not talk much, and very quickly arrived at the second tower.

This time there were already men waiting outside the tower. It was clear that Anlin had informed them ahead.

"Let me excuse myself." Anlin bowed respectfully and left.

"Thanks for your efforts."

"My pleasure to be able to serve all of you."

As Garen and the rest went closer, they suddenly realized that the group of people welcoming them were dressed luxuriously. They were wearing thick cloaks used for concealing, and their faces couldn't be seen clearly.

"Your Excellency Garen Trejon, I wonder if Liv can have the privilege to have dinner with you?"

One of the black-cloaked figures lifted her mask, revealing her face beneath.

It was pure yet pitiful, beautiful girl's face.

Her fair and delicate skin was faintly glowing under the moonlight. Her blond hair was combed into a ponytail, winding down from her shoulders. Her lips were pink and delicate.

Her most prominent attribute was her eyes. They were clear like purple gemstones.

Although the girl had evidently no intention to beg, Garen still developed pity towards her.

It was like her gaze would unknowingly cause others to develop pity.

"Princess.." The old man honorably called out her name. He was evidently trying to point out her status.

"Princess?" Garen blinked and fixed his gaze on the legendary princess.

"I wonder if Your Excellency can agree to Liv's stubborn request?" The princess had a tiny figure, with her height only up to Garen's chin. They stood opposite each other. As the wind blew, it brought with it a faint fragrance. It wasn't a recognizable fragrance, but a girl's natural body fragrance.

"Since Your Majesty has invited, how would Garen dare to reject?" Garen smiled, assessing the legendary princess in front of him.

Being King Avic's most precious daughter, Princess Liv had astonishing beauty, a superhuman strategic mind and extraordinary courage. Unknowingly, she gathered large amounts of forces for King Avic.

Vast forces.

Being Avic's eldest daughter, Princess Liv definitely wasn't very young, but looking at the girl, there was a hint of doubt in Garen's heart.

The girl was at most sixteen years of age! It was impossible that she was the rumored thirty-year old princess!

"Are you suspicious?" The princess smiled. "In fact, there's no harm in telling you directly. This is my body's natural talent."

"Body's natural talent?"

"Yes. My body will never grow old, up till my death. This is my natural state." The princess smiled. "However, this is not the time to talk about this."

Suddenly her expression turned solemn.

"Your Excellency Garen, I'm sure you know about the upcoming Trust Ceremony?"

"What about it?"

"Let's start walking. We'll talk in detail during dinner."

Garen nodded and gave the rest of his group a glance.

"You guys head to the headquarters first. I will return later."

"Yes team leader." The old man and the rest of them stuck with Garen over these few days. In this chaos, only the strong ones had the highest possibility of assuring their own safety and benefits.

Together with the princess, Garen and the group went along the mountain path. Very quickly, they arrived at a secluded bungalow.

The bungalow was brightly lit. A banquet dinner was already ready in the hall.

Golden roast chicken, rich beef and vegetable soup, fragrant black caviar, red colored fruit platter and big pieces of black steak. There were also fine egg rolls with unknown fillings, and others.

The princess ordered everyone to leave, including the waiters. Then she put on a confident look.

Very quickly, she and Garen were the only two left in the hall.

She lifted a jade-green colored wine bottle and poured some wine for both of them. There was a pure smile on the princess' face.

"You might know this, but, the First Concubine Delouse is very possibly someone from the Obscuro Society?"

Garen furrowed his brows and nodded without uttering a word.

The princess glanced at him and continued. "But, you do not know her other identity."

"Oh? What identity?"

"I didn't plan to tell you this secret, but I did not expect….aih...Honestly,

"It was my father that requested me to wait at the tower for your return to the capital. This secret, was also told to you by my father's request. His intention is for you to not worry."

"These are King Avic's intentions?" Garen got more and more curious.

"This secret is simple." The princess smiled. "First Concubine Delouse is actually a spy that my father placed long ago in the Obscuro Society."

"Oh?!" Garen shuddered. At this point he finally understood why the Obscuro Society ignored him although they knew he might have found out about First Concubine Delouse's status. This was where the problem was.

Delouse was originally not of the Obscuro Society, but a spy that Avic placed in the Obscuro. If it weren't for the fact that he already knew this history, Garen couldn't have imagined that Delouse would give up her status as the First Concubine, and eventually choose to betray Avic.

"Why tell me such a big secret?" Garen asked without any expression. Now only he knew, the depth of the complications behind Avic's stabbing.

"Tomorrow, father will personally meet you. He will let you know then." The princess shook her head.

Garen looked at the innocent, beautiful girl in front of him.

She looked innocent, but in fact there was huge ambition hidden inside her. You can't judge these kinds of people by their appearance.

"Alright. I've completed my father's request. Next, it should be our own time." She pouted her lips signaling displeasure.

"I originally thought my father would stay away from you. Then I would have opportunity to grow close to you. I never imagined it would be like this. It's really disappointing."

She raised the wine and drank a big gulp. As she put down the glass, her face instantly blushed.

"You know, when I heard from the palace that you managed to escape from numerous ambushes in the battle of snow mountain, I was instantly excited." There was passion in her eyes. "Since young my body wasn't healthy. I did not have the qualifications to become a totem user. My body was weak. It would have been impossible for me to live to this age if it weren't for the herbs from the Royal Family. My greatest dream would be to be like the ancient heroes, surging through armies. Unstoppable! That would indeed be too… amazing!!" She could not find a word to adequately describe that feeling, as she formed a fist showing her passion.

"So at that point of time, I was thinking, if only I can meet the person that could carry my dreams…"

Without knowing why, Garen felt a surge of lust within him. Looking at the innocent and cute princess opposite him, he suddenly had an urge to rush over and press against her, tearing her clothes apart. There was a fierce rampaging impulse within him. He noticed her eyes of adoration as she looked at himself. Time to time, a small tongue protruded from her soft lips.

"I know I do not have a perfect body. But I only want to fulfill my my ambition...wonder if you would agree…" The princess bowed her head, letting out a shy expression. Her face and neck turned a rose-like pink.

"If you agree.whatever position…I will allow you. Even from behind..that's…fine too" The princess spoke softly.

Chapter 409: Countermeasures 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen's eyes drooped.

"Your Majesty, your dream is indeed precious, but I am not the person that you should pass it to."

He adjusted his body and closed the majority of his pores. Instantly, the heat all over his body reduced by a half. He glanced at the princess again, and he no longer was as impulsive as before.

The princess slowly stood up. Her pretty eyes looked like they were about to cry.

She slowly walked towards Garen's back.

"Am I really that unattractive? I only wanted to fulfill my dream. A small request…" She begged softly.

Garen leaned his head back slightly. He could feel that the bump on her breasts had already touched his face. The fragrance of a young girl was even clearer now.

He also stood up with a faint, absurd smile on his face.

After walking behind the princess, Garen slowly insert his hand through the princess' collar. He instantly felt a lump of soft flesh. It was extremely bouncy, like jelly.

"If that's the case." Garen whispered in the princess' ears. "Why did you drug the candles?"

"Well….that's just an alluring fragrance." The princess cuddled her body in Garen's arm. Her eyes blinked, revealing a gleam of joy.

"Do not have pity on me…" She placed her hands on Garen's chest.

Garen abruptly moved his hand and reached for the princess' bosom.

As his fingers were about to act, the sound of hurried footsteps came from the outside.

"Your Majesty, Your Majesty!!" A girl's hurried voice came from outside the door.

Garen's eyes smiled as if he had predicted it. He retrieved his hands and backed off.

The princess' face was blushing. Her whole body mildly released fragrant sweat, intensifying the fragrance of her body. She gave Garen a sad glance, and adjusted her clothes.

"Come in."

"Elaine is my bodyguard. She wouldn't take the initiative to look for me if there was nothing important." The princess looked apologetic.

Suddenly, Garen understood.

"Alright then. I shall excuse myself today. There is still time in the future." Garen smiled. His words seemed to carry another meaning.

"Send the Viscount." The princess shouted loudly. She then stepped forward. Her hand deliberately swept past Garen's lower body. "I will not forget about tonight.." She exhaled, walked towards Garen and gave him a light kiss on his chest.

Garen's slightly raised the corners of his mouth without speaking a word.

Very quickly, two white-armored guards entered. One of them held Garen's cloak, then both of helped Garen to put it on.

The three of them left the hall under the princess' bitter gaze.

As the exited the bungalow, the smile on Garen's face intensified.

The princess was playing hard to get. Although she said to let him do anything he wanted. However, if he really made his move and crossed the line, there would be someone who would rescue her in time. To a male, the best things are always the ones out of reach. Therefore, she could always stir up a man's desire.

The night air was a little cold. Garen took a deep breath. As he exhaled, there was a strong, fragrant vapour coming out of his mouth.

It was the faint fragrance that he inhaled in the hall. Because it was covered by the princess' body fragrance, he did not realize it, but now as he came out, he instantly forced the majority of it out.

"She is indeed a seductress." Garen recalled the previous scenes. His body was still heaty. "If I hadn't had insider information, he might still be under her seduction."

Unfortunately, whether it be the eldest princess or the other princesses, Avic wac already bored of most of the older princesses. Only the eldest princess' unique body assured her of Avic's enduring love.

Pulling off his cloak, Garen saw a black carriage with gold sides awaiting him. There was a white-armored lady guard beside the carriage.

This guard had an enchanting body. She wore an armored top but it was evidently not for protection. The armor was just like an undergarment. Her slender waist was revealed and her fair skin looked exceptionally fair under the moonlight.

She wore the same colored white dress on her lower body. Her long, round legs looked powerful.

As she saw Garen coming closer, the female guard turned over, revealing a pretty face. Her long, white hair draped over her shoulder, glowing in silver underneath the moonlight.

"May the duke board the carriage."

She uttered respectfully.

Then she bent down and crouched on the ground, allowing her back to become a step for Garen to step on.

Her hips were cocked up, forming a seductive arc. It shook from time to time as if it weren't steady.

"Indeed." Garen was clear that the princess used her beauty to control a large number of people. That was why she could gain Avic's love and at the same time gather such vast forces.

Served by the pretty guard, he simply nodded his head, then stepped on her back onto the carriage.

The white-haired guard slowly got up, bowed at the horse carriage, then retreated into the darkness.

The driver was also a pretty woman. She was dressed in green armor with short black hair. Her long legs looked long and curvy in her long boots.

This woman also had a seductive figure. She had a solid bust and a slender waist. As she straightened her body, her lower body armor was a little low, faintly revealing a ravine on her abdomen.

Garen closed his eyes. He felt his blood boiling.

There was also a downside in having a powerful body. Once the body was tempted, it was far more difficult to control compared to an average human.

A hint of fragrance wafted through the carriage. It was the princess' body fragrance.

Garen refocused and quickly adjusted the state of his body.

Under the rumbling wheels, the carriage continuously moved forward.

After sometime, Garen heard the voice of the driver coming from the front.

"Your Excellency. We have arrived."

"Yes." Garen opened his eyes and looked out from the left window. He had arrived at his manor, Blue Bay.

When he got off the carriage, a guard was standing straight at the gate with his head held high, indicating that he was energetic and alert.

"Welcome Your Excellency on your return!" The soldier shouted.

The door to the manor as already wide open. Lala, in her black tunic skirt was standing in front of the door, waiting silently. Evidently, there were also some new servants and guards.

"Welcome back, Your Excellency Garen." There was a relaxed smile on Lala's face.

"It's been a long trip." Garen also said. "I thought I would be back in around ten days."

He took off his overcoat and handed it to Lala, then walked into the manor surrounded by the others.

"During the time when I was away, did anything major happen at home?"

As he entered the hall, he went straight for the sofa. After finishing the tea prepared for him in one gulp, Garen asked.

"There are some things going on. There are some changes with the family assets. The businesses under your name received support from the government's policy. The shops in the capital have also reopened. There are many suppliers looking for us, hoping to supply stocks to us…"

"Shops?" Garen was surprised. He instantly recalled that he still had a totem repair shop. It was long closed due to lack of suppliers and raw materials.

"Yes. A totem shop." Lala nodded. "There's also an auction house given by the King. The contract documents were sent over earlier."

"Auction house? When?" Garen was surprised. "An auction house, ignoring its intrinsic value, even the land that it's on is worth quite a lot. His Majesty is indeed generous." Auction houses were commonly relatively large. A certain level of fame was also needed to run it. It wasn't something that anyone could build. Without sufficient power and fame, a built auction house would be equivalent to trash.

"His Majesty gave it on the second day after you left the capital. This wasn't the only thing. There are also twelve other unrenovated, empty shops. They were said to be your reward for being loyal to the kingdom."

"Twelve empty shops. His Majesty is willing to give them up. Are there any nobles who faced predicaments recently?" Garen smiled faintly.

"Yes. Earl Boliu who lived in the East district was suspected of colluding with the Obscuro Society, and had already been sentenced to death. The vast assets under his name were distributed among the other nobles. These shops and the auction house were also part of Earl Boliu's assets."

"What should we turn these shops into? What do you think?" Garen asked Lala plainly, "In fact, our family does not have a stable income source. His Majesty gave me these shops as a foundation to get back on my feet. What do you think can earn quick money?"

For Garen to be able to maintain the manor's operations and the salaries of the many servants, finding a stable income source is a must.

He couldn't always depend on rewards, or hunting monsters to sell materials right? Supporting so many people by himself was obviously unrealistic.

"Miss Angel is doing decently well in the War Guild and has also made some good friends. Her side could provide a relatively stable source for raw materials. With so many shops, we can convert all of them into chains of potions and consumables stores, selling medicine and ointments. We can also sell equipment produced from the monster's materials, or simple tools that totem users like." Lala, who seemed to have thought about it before, immediately spoke her mind.

"Besides, we can also purchase some rare items from totem users for auctions in the auction house. I've contacted some individual forgers to purchase their goods. If there are good items we can also use them for auctions. The other two auction houses in the capital also function this way."

"What will be our advantage? How do we ensure that we won't be squeezed out by the other two auction houses?" Garen asked with interest.

"You are our advantage, Lord Garen." Lala said. "You are incredibly strong. Among the other two auction houses, the Dawn Auction house is backed by a Grand Duke. The other one can't be compared with us at all. The difference is, their elites wouldn't simply go out and explore, but would choose to stay in and protect the family. However, only elites would be able to obtain the goods an average person wouldn't dream of obtaining. Hence, that is our competitive advantage."

"You have a point."

"The problem at hand, is insufficient manpower." Lala frowned as she said.

"Manpower. How about the transformed inmates?" Garen thought.

"Not possible. They have already created trouble a few times in the chamber. It was almost as if since they are no longer imprisoned, they would like to come out. These people have been underground for a long time. Their heart has gone a little wild." Lala whispered.

Garen nodded his head. After the inmates were transformed by him, and had been staying underground without any opportunity of contact with the outside world. They had no news about the outside world at all. Without the Crystal Derivator to imprison them, plus their incredibly strong transformed bodies, it was natural that they desired to get out.

"How many people are there now?"

"Five. The one that create trouble is one of the girl assassins." Lala answered simply, " If it wasn't for the two knight leaders who returned twice to suppress them, I wonder what other trouble they might have created."

"Understood." Garen nodded. "How are Maxilan and Edney doing?"

"They organized and trained all of the old family old survivors, and removed those who were unqualified or had lost focus. The remaining people are guarding the different shops respectively. These people are using quite a huge amount of resources daily. Our family wealth is depleting as we speak. We have to find a new income source immediately."

Garen was instantly ashamed. He only cared about his personal development and almost neglected the family business which was declining each day. There were so many people around him to support. It was his responsibility as the family head.

Chapter 410: Countermeasures 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"In the entire Trejon Household, there are twenty-three official subordinates.The eleven guards are assigned into two groups with the two knights, Maxilan and Edney, leading one each. The remaining twelve are elderly, handymen, maids, coachmen, and others. Myself included." Lala was incredibly familiar as she immediately reported all the information.

"We have three manors, twelve farms, thirteen shops and an auction house." Lala summarized. "The people who remained are those who have been raised by the family since young. They are living in the other two manors."

"Don’t we still have farms? How are the profits?"

"It looks like a lot. But recently, the farms were unable to find a preventive measure for mutated flies, which has severely affected the crops.." Lala shook her head. "The food produced is now sufficient only for their own survival, nevermind the family."

"What’s the status of the family’s totem users?" Garen asked further.

"Not good...Out of the 10 first form totem users, half of them already left. The remaining five have deep sentiments towards the family. Furthermore, you were out there for such a long time. There were rumors from the capital that you’d been killed by the Obscuro Society. It was then that the men left."

"It’s really bleak…" Garen shook his head. He himself had become stronger, but the entire Trejon Family was on the verge of disappearing. The assets left by his father were either gone or weakened. If it wasn’t for the King, who couldn’t bear to watch it happen and thus provided some assets in support, the entire Trejon Household would have been eradicated.

Even the old totem users that were raised by the family were disheartened. They were only left with five loyal first form totem users. If it wasn’t for the support of the two elders, Maxilan and Edner, the family guard would have long been extinguished.

Garen thought for a moment. Avic’s assassination was about to happen. Whether he should choose to help or be a bystander would be a major decision.

The Obscuro Society was his greatest enemy. Therefore, it would be a logical decision to help Avic and thwart their plans. However, Garen did not know of Avic’s perspective towards himself.

Moreover, the crucial detail was the palace was where Kovitan’s strongest was stationed at - that old monster. The elite from the Elder Council was not a laughing matter. The old guy was different from Garen himself, who was not a fifth form but managed to reach the level of a normal fifth form through unique methods.

The old guy in the palace was a genuine fifth form totem user. He might even be the top amongst them.

What methods did the Obscuro Society use to fight the old guy and successfully retreat from the capital?

According to history, after the Obscuro’s assassination had succeeded, all of them had quickly retreated from the capital. The old monster had not left the palace in pursuit. In fact, he hadn’t even been in Garen’s vision. After that, the whole of Kovitan had fallen into a state of discord. It led to internal struggles and eventually decline. The Black Prince was suspected to be a member of the Obscuro Society, and he left the capital injured.

"Let’s wait for a few more days. After the Aegis Ceremony, I will make arrangements for the matters of the family." Garen thought for a moment then murmured softly.

He wanted to wait until the incident had happened, then make his move based on the situation.

"The family resources can only last for two more months." Lala coldly reminded him.

"Don’t worry."

"Alright. Prepare some food and get some rest after dinner. We still have things to do tomorrow."

"Okay."

Now, Lala willingly followed Garen. Although she was now free from the control of the derivator, it was obvious that she had nowhere else to go. She was already used to taking care of the Trejon Family, hence she did not entertain other thoughts.

Garen knew that in his current state, it was necessary for him to help.

Since he would be pursued by both by the Obscuro Society and the Terraflor Society, he might as well help to preserve the power of the Royal Alliance, albeit earlier than before.

After dinner, he went to the secret chamber.

In the underground cave, the female assassin that had created trouble was the last female inmate that he’d transformed. She had a strong body and was already two meters tall. As she had muscles all over her body, she didn’t look much like a woman.

As Garen strode into the underground hall, the woman was boxing fiercely with two muscular men. Muted thuds sounded whenever one of them managed to land a blow on the others.

The three of them were engaged in a scuffle, much like a bunch of barbarians. Blood was splattering everywhere.

Two other men were clenching their fists as they stood beside to watch the commotion. Both of them had incredibly strong bodies, which were comparable to Hercules. They only wore black underwear and their heads were completely bald. They were all shaved including the female assassin.

Garen entered in his white pyjamas and coldly stared at them.

When the two bystanders saw Garen, it was like mice noticing a cat. The hairs all over their body stood upright. They quickly put down their hands and bowed their heads, looking like they were timid and obedient.

"Lord…" The two men softly greeted him one by one.

Garen walked over to them. He was 1.8 meters tall, yet was still obviously a head shorter as compared to the two men. His normally strong body was clearly not on their level.

The bodies of these men were swollen like Garen when he’d been practicing the Divine Statue Technique. The muscles on their bodies were incredibly tight as if they were about to explode.

The three people who were embroiled in the fight had not noticed Garen's entrance.

"Not bad. Now you know how to create trouble." Garen smacked his lips with a bloodthirsty stare. For whatever reason, he’d often felt his body burning recently. Only during a slaughter would he feel slightly soothed. This put him on his guard.

After not killing for a few weeks, he felt something stuck in his heart. He grew more and more uncomfortable.

The two men who stood in front of him were shivering due to this gaze.

"It's not us who created trouble. It's that b*tch!!" One of them pointed at the female assassin who was midfight. "It's all because of her! Her body grew stronger and stronger recently. After our transformation, our skin grew tougher and tougher. We can't even feel any pain from being beaten. The b*tch is especially strong!"

Garen’s gaze grew cold.

He turned his head towards the direction of the fight.

His gaze was almost tangible as it swept over the three of them.

Instantly, the three people shuddered and noticed Garen standing at the side.

At this point in time, one of the men behind Garen raised his hands quietly, flexed his tough, steel pillar-like arms and fiercely crushed Garen’s head.

"Die!!" The strong man cried with a vicious expression.

The female assassin let out a satisfied smile from afar.

According to their previous tests, with their strength, a punch on the wall would leave a deep hole. Other than the bodies of their companions, nothing could withstand their hits.

The last time Maxilan and Edney came, they only showed a third of their strength and acted like they were defeated by the two men. It was all a farce to conceal their strength for this moment.

They wanted to completely eradicate this man who’d made their life hell.

Out of the five, this was planned by three of them.

At that point in time, the other two were completely stunned.

One of them was Komodo, the one who’d previously trusted Garen the most. At this moment, he looked absolutely terrified. He rushed towards Garen in an attempt to save him.

He was immediately held back by the female assassin and another strong man.

Bang!!

Finally, the strong man’s two fists smashed into Garen’s temples on both sides of his head.

It did not even activate totem light.

Garen turned. There weren’t even red marks on his two temples.

"Are you helping me scratch an itch?" He smiled abruptly.

The man was sweating all over his body. He bowed and looked at Garen, realizing that he had done something incredibly stupid.

"He...hehe...Lord...It wasn’t on purpose.."

Crack!!

A red blur flashed by.

The man remained motionless. His whole upper body disappeared as though he had been bitten into two by something. Only his lower body was left on the ground, then it fell over with a thump.

His bloody intestines spilled onto the ground, releasing a thick fishy odor.

"I thought I was already merciful enough. Who knew that something like that could still happen."

As the rest of them witnessed the scene, their expressions were filled with terror. Especially Komodo, who saw with his own eyes how Garen had turned a monstrous, frightening beast into jerky. He couldn’t imagine that these idiots would dare to revolt against their Lord!

As he saw Garen’s glowing red eyes, he instantly felt like the sky was about to fall.

Crash!!

With another clear sound, the female assassin and another man were instantly left with only their lower bodies, and they toppled onto the ground.

Komodo and another man were the only ones left shivering. Their sweat trickled down their bodies onto the ground. Their faces were twisted in fear as they fell onto their knees.

"Lord! It had nothing to do with us! It’s that bitch! It’s her! We totally do not know anything!!" Komodo beseeched him.

The other man could only howl. He shook his head non-stop, begging for forgiveness.

At this point, Garen had slightly cooled down. He glanced at the three corpses.

"I know who has the heart and who doesn’t. Both of you really did not know anything. Go clean up the place. Follow me out tomorrow."

"Yes! Yes! Lord!!" Komodo immediately bowed repeatedly.

After Garen left the hall, the two of them trembled and fell to the ground. They looked at each other in relief, as if they’d received a second chance at life.

"Quick! Quickly, clean it up!" Komodo quickly reminded.

"Alright!" The other person immediately started moving as well.

***********

Garen left the hall. After killing the assassin in the secret chamber, he understood more about the people he transformed.

Although his initial experiments had been carried out to perfect the dragon heart transplant on himself, the results he’d obtained weren’t weak at all.

The transformed humans had the power and speed of a first form totem. Each of them were incredibly, silver totems in human form.

With this conclusion, he could actually use this technique to create a living army for the family. However, he would have to completely perfect the surgery before starting.

Due to the incredibly painful repelling process, the mortality rate was too high.

Out of the hundreds of inmates he’d experimented on, only five had succeeded.

Of course, this was a plan for the future, but he could actually bring out the two men to be members of the family guard.

As he left the chamber, Garen considered the information he’d received from various sides. He returned to his bedroom. After washing up under Lala’s service, he climbed onto the bed to rest.

He had to be revitalized. It was likely that tomorrow would be the day Avic called for him. It was imperative for him to gauge Avic’s attitude. After all Avic could not represent the Royal Alliance.

Even if he wanted to help, he had to think of a plan.

The First Concubine was Avic’s most trusted person. For him to suspect her based on Garen’s few words would be completely impossible. It might even get Garen himself into trouble.

Chapter 411: Poison 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The next day.

Avic’s edict arrived as expected.

Garen dressed neatly, and followed the herald to the palace to see His Majesty.

It was the same study as before; Avic was seated on the bench quietly, looking relaxed and at ease. As he saw Garen come in, a satisfied look flashed across his face.

He stood up and gently shook Garen’s hand.

"Trejons, you are finally here. This time you have truly salvaged the reputation of Kovitan’s royal family."The joy on Avic’s face was void of any pretense. Even his greetings were raised a notch higher.

"Your majesty, that is an exaggeration. This is what I am obliged to do." Garen answered humbly.

Both of them sat down on two separate golden chairs by the window.

"Coincidentally, I am holding an Aegis Ceremony a few days from now. Since you are back, do join us. Never expected that you would become a fourth form master; it is a rare sight in this country. It is perfect timing; I have already notified the rest of the fourth form totem users that you are back. Compared to the average person such as myself, you high form totem masters would definitely have more to talk about."The smile on Avic’s face was neutral. Perhaps he knew that Garen had killed one of the princesses, or perhaps not; either way, he didn’t look like he really minded.

Garen only smiled politely and listened as he continued on.

"Obscuro’s God Cloud – I have heard of his fame previously, and it is certainly distinguished. His experiences are similar to yours; Kovitan’s defense minister Veska had once faced off God Cloud, and I have called him here today so that both of you can interact with one another. "Avic calmly continued, "Both of you are the country’s top talents, and Kovitan needs your vital support to stand strong, have greater stability and to continuously increase in strength for years to come.

"I am undeserving of Your Majesty’s praises."Garen lowered his head in an act of humility.

Avic lightly shook his head. He appeared to be powerless against Garen’s humility.

"Alright. There are two main reasons for the edict. I hope you will be willing to help."

"Please continue, your Majesty."Garen nodded his head.

"Firstly Trejons, you have reached the level of the fourth form. According to the country’s standard procedure, every fourth form will be given the title of Earl, as well as a territory as an inheritance.

Secondly, this is my personal request; I hope you will be able to attend when I hold the ceremony."

"Your subject will be there without fail." Garen nodded his head. "Besides that, the first was a reward; how is that considered as a favor?"

Avic smiled, ready to explain. All of a sudden, a loud announcement was declared.

"The defense minister is here"

Both of them looked towards the entrance of the study at the same time.

Two knocks sounded at the door, and it was pushed open. A serious looking old man with a head of white hair came in.

Just as he walked in, he saw Garen who was humbly seated before Avic.

"Your majesty, it’s apparent that this is the new fourth form Garen?"His voice was composed and unshakable, and through it one could discern an unassailable spirit.

Garen stood up, and started weighing this old man carefully.

He seemed like a typical old pedant from the scholarly institutes; conscientious, without a trace of unkemptness in the way he carried himself. Even the smallest detail did not escape him. It was obvious this person was a serious and strict old man.

But the most obvious thing was not his appearance, but the subtle white glow hovering around this old man’s body.

That was a nearly liquefied totem light! Just glancing across with normal human eyes would evoke a realization that this old man’s entire being was filled with the breath of the abyss within the deep sea.

Garen could vaguely smell the salty scent of the ocean from him. Undoubtedly, his core totem was a water type.

"It’s good to see you, Your Excellency Elder Veska. " Garen politely bowed towards him.

Veska returned the bow.

At this time, a blue light flashed across the back Veska’s right hand.

An invisible force field crashed into Garen. This force field had no form or color; even the air was void of any movement or disturbance. It was as if it appeared abruptly in front of Garen and crashed towards him.

This rush of energy was not large, but it had an unstoppable, all conquering air to it.

In that moment, Garen seemed to hear the sound of crashing waves; a huge large blue wave appeared right in front of his eyes and was about to overwhelm him.

He quickly saw that a swirling blue-black whirlpool had formed behind Veska.

It was a whirlpool of immeasurable depth, like an invisible whirlpool sent from the depths of the ocean. Slow, extremely enormous; it was as if everything was in danger of being swallowed by it.

The side of Garen’s mouth slightly twitched up. Behind him, the nine-headed hydra’s red silhouette appeared.

Roarrrr!!!

An invisible force field was sent to the opponent in the same manner.

Boom!!

There was not a sound of collision in actuality, but the force of both powers colliding sent a loud sound reverberating in the hearts of the people watching.

This was purely just a competition between the totem powers. Without the exchange of totems, totem powers are powerless; incapable of changing the nature of matter. Only by changing it into totem light or by using it to manipulate totems will it affect the world of matter. It was similar to the nature of spirit power, as mentioned by Garen in his previous world.

Garen’s totem power was initially not strong, but after feeding on the nine-headed hydra’s totem light, it was not one that a normal totem user would be able to defend themselves from.

This time, two large forces collided.

The light rays between them appeared distorted. There seemed to be a layer of invisible crystal wall.

The light rays only distorted for a moment, and returned to normal quickly.

Garen’s face flushed slightly. This was due to an overwork of the mind, causing the momentary discomfort.

Veska had no expression to his face as usual, but his eyes betrayed a hint of astonishment.

" As expected of a fourth form! And of the highest level."Veska nodded his head,"I now believe you were capable of escaping from the hands of God Cloud."

"It seems it’s true that there is always a succession of talented people in the Kovitan Empire."Garen remained silent, focused on making adjustments to his body.

The defense minister was one of the strongest 3 in Kovitan. Besides the two grand dukes, he was the strongest and most loyal towards the royal family. Garen initially thought that facing off other powerful fourth forms with the nine-headed hydra would not be a difficult task.

Now there seemed to be more of a problem. No wonder God Cloud gave such an assessment.

During the battle just now, he was slightly weaker than the other party. The defense minister’s totem was a ginormous ocean whirlpool; when it came to how he managed to get produce that, Garen had absolutely no idea. Even the nine-headed hydra was far below in comparison.

Even though his totem was incapable of winning, Garen was not worried. His strength lay in his being and not his totem. The totem was only there as a complement to his being.

The ceremony of becoming an Earl was fairly simple; An edict was written by Avic and then passed on to Garen, together with a few prepared letters and documents.

The capital was in a highly complicated situation at the moment; Avic was obviously not in the mood to hold an official awarding ceremony. Those were not compulsory. The most important thing was to receive the tangible benefits.

And then the demarcation of territories.

The one given to Garen by Avic was a territory situated a distance from the capital, the surface area the size of a province. It was a broad prairie plateau named Pato, the name signifying the place of birth. It was initially a place in the capital where livestock grazed freely; now, a huge number of livestock have perished, leaving a numbered few to graze around and Pato subsequently being emptied of its prior purpose, vacant of civilization. All of these was passed on to Garen by Avic.

After leaving the palace, Garen carefully considered the implication behind Avic’s actions.

To summon the defense minister who proactively initiated a face-off was obviously meant as a warning for him to know his place a little, as the kingdom was completely capable of controlling its people. All along, they had turned a blind eye. As long as it was not too overboard; that will not turn out well.

And the broad prairie plateau was obviously a compensation after the blow.

Recalling the defense minister Veska’s capabilities, Garen made some rough estimations. Although he wasn’t sure how much of his capabilities was shown, he made guesses based on the performance earlier.

The opponent’s totem was indeed stronger than the nine headed hydra. If only totems were taken into consideration, he would be on the losing side.

Not only that, the opponent definitely possessed heirlooms. Each of the 3 masters, also known as the pillars of the Kovitan Empire, had a high-level heirloom.

If he really had to battle the opponent.

Garen estimated that if he did not use his own body, he would not be up to par. It was obvious the opponent would have a powerful card that was kept hidden. If they really had to battle for their lives, it was unknown who the actual winner would be.

As he left the palace, he headed towards the secret department.

On the way there, the streets near the kingdom’s palace were much cleaner; many villagers and business owners were putting up lights and decorations, they seemed to be in celebration of something.

A pair of newlyweds stood high on a wooden car with two huge white eagles pulling two ropes from the front; the eagles flapped their wings while propelling the car forward.

Surrounded by two rows of guards tasked to protect, many little kids were holding on to flower baskets and scattering rose petals.

The wooden car passed by Garen’s left side; Garen could see the happy smiles on the faces of the newlyweds.

"It’s a wedding?"Realization dawned upon Garen.

"Yes, master."Driver Josephine answered immediately,"These two people are Viscount Leliyah’s son and his wife. Viscount Leliyah had often helped the people and the businessmen, earning himself a good name in this part of the streets, so everyone is genuinely wishing them the best.

"Viscount Leliyah?" Garen tried to search his memory but came up with no recollection of this name. It was obvious that the man played a small role in the kingdom.

The people outside the carriage were extremely noisy, one noise topping the other.

Garen let down the window curtains.

"Wedding…Such a pity, this would be your last taste of happiness." He closed his eyes. Not long from now, the entire kingdom will enter a state of extreme chaos, leaving no trace of peace and stability behind.

In order to stop the killings, the biggest key laid in the hands of The First Concubine, Delouse. When it came to revealing her scheme in a way that was believable to Avic, it was a huge headache.

As the First Concubine had the identity of a double agent, to convince Avic of her rebellion would be extremely difficult.

Obscuro’s plans were almost bulletproof.

The information that was in Garen’s hands decreased. Thinking about it on the way, there seemed to be no clue.

Delouse was laying low at the moment. From what he’d heard, she’d completely cut off contact with the outside world, staying deep within the palace in preparation for the loyalty ceremony.

And as he entered the palace this time, Garen was indecisive on whether to save Avic.

The key to the fall of Kovitan was not on the death of Avic, but whether or not someone would be able to centralize power and take control of the big picture.

To prevent the assassination appeared to be too difficult. Even so, aiding the kingdom in centralizing the power after Obscuro left seemed to rank much lower in difficulty.

To be honest, Garen was not keen on being involved in this mess. The impression Avic left on him was not good, or at least, not to the extent where he would put his life on the line for him.

Moreover, the 3 major departments were the foundation of the royal family. As long as the 3 departments stayed in place, everything would slowly return to order.

As long as the original heirlooms were not taken away, Kavitan would eventually return to peace.

If his hypothesis was correct, Obscuro’s real goal was to obtain the original heirloom Caeserton, which was also an absolute sanctuary according to legend.

As he was in deep thought throughout the journey, the horse carriage arrived at the secret department without him realizing it – Wells castle.

A castle made of grey stone silently stood in the middle of grassy lands.

As Garen dismounted from the carriage, a few men and women covered entirely in black armor walked out; they had a blue emblem on their chest.

"Blue team?"Garen immediately recognized the meaning behind their emblem.

The secret service team, from the bottom to the top, were distinguished into 9 colours – red, orange, yellow, light green, dark green, blue, purple, white and silver. The higher the team was on the list, the stronger they were. Blue was amongst the top 4, also known as one of the top leveled teams.

Chapter 412: Poison 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The same few saw Garen dismounting the carriage. The member leading the team nodded slightly towards Garen. Without saying a word, they both passed each other.

As Garen made his way up the steps of the castle, he couldn’t help but take a second glance at the blue team.

These people were indeed powerful; each of their auras were ambiguous, unusual and deeply hidden. The weakest of them should be in the third form at least; while the strongest, even Garen was unable to decipher the aura.

It was highly possible they were in the fourth form just like him, but their auras were significantly weaker than Garen’s, which meant they had probably barely reached the fourth form.

Although so, it was already a huge accomplishment.

The blue team still had 3 tiers above them – purple, white and silver. Among them the silver remained the strongest; Garen had no idea what their members were capable of.

These were the 3 major services; strong users were as uncountable as the clouds. Even Obscuro did not dare face them in a straightforward manner and instead relied on the monsters and the contents of their nest.

Garen continued on into the castle. Right then, he saw a figure with a silver emblem walking out from the front door.

Both of them saw each other’s faces.

The person was a silver-haired woman with dark skin; she had thick, luscious lips, an average looking face, and a slightly bloated body. Her right and left hands were placed into their opposing sleeves. The section of clothing on her shoulders seemed to contain something moving; a living creature.

As Garen walked closer towards her, he smelled a pungent fragrance.

He furrowed his eyebrows. Taking a second glance at the moving shoulder, the incident with Obscuro's poison as well as the poisonous nature of the nine-headed hydra came to mind. He could immediately tell that the fragrance had an underlying poison that was extremely lethal.

"Crimson team?"This woman saw the red emblem on Garen’s chest and immediately blocked his way. "I heard that the head of your team is a master named Garen? The return to the capital this time around, he would join us right?"

Garen raised his eyebrows.

"Why do you want to see him?"

"I heard that he walked out completely unscathed after being poisoned twice with two types of poison by Obscuro. I’m just trying to figure out what he is made of."The dark skinned woman chuckled, "If you see him, let him come to my lab voluntarily, instead of having me issue a personal invitation."

Rage flickered in Garen’s eyes; the red glow in between his brows shone. Next to him, a gigantic dragon head leaped forward.

Bang!!!

A circle of red black light shattered into pieces right in between them.

A red dragon head close to 2 meters big crashed into a giant black snakehead. Both of them were similar in strength and backed away at the same time.

"You are knocking on death’s door !!"The dark skinned woman never thought Garen would retaliate this way. She was enraged "There are people in the administration who actually dare mess with me!!"She quickly took out a handful of black powder, disseminating it in front of her.

The black powder followed the wind and disappeared, melting into the air in just seconds.

Garen turned a deaf ear to her words, and then the remaining eight dragon heads appeared behind him. In moments, they pounced towards the dark-skinned woman from all directions.

Roar!!

The low rumble of the dragon’s roar shook the whole castle; circles of runes appeared on the walls one after another, these black runes preventing any damages inflicted by the rumbling of the dragon’s roars.

The wooden tables and chairs at the front door and the decorations made from bone on the wall turned into dust during the dragon’s roaring.

The ground, with Garen as the center, folded up like waves from all directions; large number of stone pieces flew all over the place. You could hear gasps coming from rest of the people in the living room inside.

"Fabulous timing. I have yet to kill anyone today, may you be that blood sacrifice!"Garen’s eyes had a killer gleam. His sequelae had started reacting again; he killed a few experiment subjects that were asking for it and felt himself calming down. He’d never thought he will meet another idiot with a stronger than thou attitude in the administration today.

The dark skinned woman laughed dryly and took two steps back hurriedly; Her long hair behind turned into countless black snakes, engulfing any empty space around the place from all directions, spreading out with piercing hisses. It looked like a huge blob of black lines pouncing towards 8 large red dragon heads.

Among them was the largest black snake head with three horns attached to it. Its eyes were green and fierce, heading towards the main golden dragon head.

"Enough!!" A voice thundered from the castle all of a sudden.

It was at that time a white figure slashed out like a whip, aiming for the space in between the dragon head and the black snake.

White billowy smoke burst out from the middle with a sizzling sound, separating Garen from the dark-skinned woman.

The black-skinned woman had a crazed sick look to her eyes, looking as if she found her new toy.

Garen’s eyes were even weirder; he looked at her as if she were food, licking his lips, ready to pounce on her any minute to devour her.

It was during this time figures in full black armors walked out slowly from the hall; these people were members of administration teams that had just returned recently. Most of them had orange and yellow emblems on their chest, which obviously meant that they were from the orange and purple teams, teams which had the most numbers.

"Black Nesat! If you want to butt heads with Nine Heads that’s your problem, but the purpose of calling you here is for you to cooperate with the investigation, not for you to create more trouble!" A middle-aged man in white robes walked out slowly. His gaze fell on the woman with dark skin, and felt his head throbbing.

He then looked towards Garen on the opposite side; his instincts told him that this guy was going to be another source of headache for him.

The way this dude was staring at Nesat looked as if he was seeing a spread of delicious treats, damn! Another pervert!

Was there no sane person among these top dogs?

He couldn’t help but curse in his heart.

"I would need a detailed explanation as to why your poison fell into the hands of Obscuro, which eventually led to its use on our men." The middle-aged man’s voice was similar to the voice of the administration director, which Garen had heard from the black box prior to this. Evidently, he should be Director McCain.

"My only concern is about mixing the poisons and selling them out; as to who uses them and on who, that is out of my reach."The dark skinned woman chuckled and looked towards Garen, her eyes darkening, sinister. "Although so, when it comes to who lived on after facing any poison of mine, I am extremely interested.

"Ahh…So it was your poison.." Garen recalled the unpleasant memory of the poison that brought him great annoyance, and anger flared up in him, "Good…very good…"

Both the orange and yellow team’s leaders were there. Both of them entered the service together as blood brothers; now they stood together, trying to avoid the 3 people at the door. They looked at the dark-skinned woman with extreme fear.

"It’s that crazy woman Black Nesat again! I thought she returned to Ender? Why did she pop out of nowhere!? Orange team’s leader Cohen locked her eyes on Nesat, hatred blazing across her eyes.

"She is merciless even towards her own people. I have long suspected that it was this woman who plotted against us from the beginning, causing the horrible death of Aqua and the others! Does she think that she is all that just because she is from the silver team? Sooner or later she will crash into a wall!"

Both of them had long held grudges towards Nesat from an earlier time. Now that they have seen her in a tough spot, they could not help but glow with satisfaction.

"Disperse! All dispersed. Brother Cohen, please bring your men out."The administration director McCain instructed the bustling crowd from a distance.

Hmmph!

Cohen made a sound signifying his dissatisfaction and dragged his brother, along with more than 10 people out of the door on the right.

Garen suppressed his inexplicable killer urges and looked towards McCain.

"Director, if there’s nothing else I will return to my team."

"This issue…sigh…" McCain did not know how to resolve this; Nesat was the sole poison specialist in Kovitan’s administration, and the only reason the administration was not afraid of any sort of poison attack from the enemy. This was the reason why even when she created huge problems, she would be let off with just a severe warning.

In the 3 main services, masters were as uncountable as the clouds; there were countless strong users. Even so, those who used poison were but a few; when it came to status and rarity, they were similar to that of a fifth form master.

"Sooner or later I will devour you." Garen glared at Nesat with bloodshot eyes.

"You will definitely lie on my laboratory table, hehe."Nesat laughed openly without restraint. She had initially wanted Garen’s cooperation on a few experiments without the intention of hurting him. She would never have thought he would be so gutsy, not easily complying the way the previous people did. Now, she really wanted to get rid of him permanently.

As for Garen’s previous battle record, she was also a fourth form master. Even the director and assistant director of the administration pegged her as a headache. God Cloud? He seemed to be only a fifth form master from Obscuro, how much does that count for?

"Enough! We are all from the same team! If you feel like killing, find someone else!" McCain felt his head throb yet again. "Nesat, let’s go. The others are still waiting for us." He was not only Kavitan’s administration director, but also the leader of the strongest team here – the silver team.

"Uh uh." Nesat placed her hands back into each opposite sleeve. "Such a tiny tiny pawn. Do not think you can go rampant just because the director protects you."

"You are looking to die!"

Garen’s urge to kill intensified. Out of his left hand shot a red lightning within seconds.

Clang!!! Baaam!!

McCain and Garen both retreated a step.

One of them held a knife while the other empty fists.

"Sorry, I was a little impulsive." Garen suppressed the growing urge to kill, and it showed in the raspiness of his voice.

McCain felt his heart thumping against his chest violently. Just now, he could not summon his totem in time and used only his totem light and instantaneous knife technique. He never thought that even his instantaneous knife technique which was used for the purpose of self-protection would almost falter.

Silence haunted the hall.

Two workers who had just walked out held their hands over their mouths, staring at the 3 people at the door. They did not dare make a sound.

Nesat gulped. A moment ago, she clearly felt the shadow of death.

That speed, that power; even the director was forced to take a step back. Director McCain! The man known as Silver Dagger, their top close range combat totem user!

Even among the fourth form totem masters, he was one of the elites – to the extent that Blood Tower was not a worthy opponent. He could be considered within the top 4 when it came to fourth form users.

It was unexpected that he would be on the same level with Nine Heads!

"So what, who cares that you’re stronger than me! Longing to kill me? I’ll poison you first!" Her heart was full of venom.

McCain shook his head, feeling as if Garen was a volcano waiting to erupt anytime. A moment ago, his one palm could affect even him.

He then looked towards Nesat. This idiot had finally decided to control herself.

Having a person to keep her under control sounded good; Garen was immune to poison anyways. He released a sigh; Nesat was really too much most of the time. Now that there was someone capable of restricting her, it acted as a method of control.

Garen bowed to the director slightly, suppressing his hunger and yearn to kill, and walked into the castle.

To the nine-headed hydra, any type of hostility signified food! The more riled up he got, the more he felt like eating the opponent.

The current Garen needed to kill periodically, using fresh blood as a way to settle his emotions. Now that he had been taunted by Black Nesat, a part of him exploded.

The sequelae caused by nine headed hydra was not one of the norm; when it was still eight-headed, Garen’s secret technique had been capable of keeping it under control. Now that it had nine heads, he was barely able to keep it in line.

Without a spirit realm that was strong enough, it was hard to overcome the urges and yearnings of the flesh.

"Don’t know if an upgrade in secret technique would help with a breakthrough in this area."Garen passed by two people and walked in the direction of the castle’s secret passageway.

When the time was right, he would devour that Black Nesat. As useful as a person could be, their value would plunge to zero when they were dead.

Chapter 413: Buffer 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The entrance of the secret passage was slowly raised.

Garen entered openly, and the members who were walking about inside distanced themselves away from him when they saw his emotionless face, hoping to avoid any unnecessary trouble.

Along the passage, there were transparent crystals glowing with blue light every few meters. This was a facility which was built underwater.

After walking for a while, Garen saw the fatty that he had come in contact with rushing towards him, as his upper body jiggled about freely.

"Oh! My dear Captain Nine Head! You’ve finally returned!!" The fatty exaggeratedly flung his arms open in an attempt to hug him.

Garen ignored and walked past him.

"Do you have anything you want from me?"

"Uhh…" Fatty Baidel’s face was filled with awkwardness as he put away his hands. "It’s Deputy Director Marquis, he wants to see you to talk about Red team’s completed mission."

He paused for a while before he continued. "Captain Nine Head. You have produced a very satisfactory results for this mission. With the addition of this special mission on Snowy Peak, perhaps Red Team is about to be promoted…"

"Promotion? What benefits would a promotion bring to me?" Garen asked as he walked on.

"Of course there is! A big one too!" The fatty started to pick up his pace to match with Garen’s and yet he was barely able to keep up to him. "If the Red Team were to be promoted to the upper class group, then the welfare and treatment of the team would naturally increase as well. The approval from the Headquarter would increase as well."

"What’re the overall benefits then?" Garen was considered the type where he wouldn’t stop asking until he could clearly see the benefits.

"Uhh… About this… The main increment aspects are authority and wealth." The Fatty Baidel took out a white handkerchief as he wiped at the sweat on his face. "The amount of wealth would be completely at your discretion and can be exchanged for with your mission points. It can be a Heirloom, a territory or resources of the highest level such as antidotes, poisons, weapons, equipment, etc. In terms of authority, you may be promoted to obtain more power and even the support from the other branches."

"It is quite beneficial." Garen nodded his head as he finally cooled down.

The number of people in the area had increased as they took a few turns. There were a lot of workers in grey shirts, who were meant to serve the members here. They milled about in the area as they pushed around boxes filled with food, drinks, and clothes.

There were even workers running out of the room with some sort of intel in their hands. Some even carried a wardrobe filled with uniforms as they passed through the passage with no clear intention.

There were even people standing in the middle of a forked road as they debated softly.

The Headquarter was clearly more active than when he’d first arrived.

Fatty Baidel noticed Garen’s confusion and decided to explain as they walked.

"Usually, most of the people here are out on their missions so the special teams would naturally rest. Now that most of the small teams have returned, it’s normal that the service teams are working their butts off. Whether it’s to service equipment, instruments, audit missions or announce reports and news, this is when the workflow is at its peak."

Garen nodded to indicate his understanding.

Baidel continued his explanation: "Our main sponsor at the Headquarter is currently the Kovitan Empire. Of course, we do have our own industry as well but there’s not a lot of it, hence we are currently assisting the Kovitan Empire. The Trust Ceremony is going to begin soon so we’re busy preparing as well. Five out of the nine teams have already returned to maintain the safety of this area."

Garen understood.

The two of them came across another forked road and went into a sealed pathway, where at the end of the road a silver, textured door gleamed. A guardian in a heavy white armor was guarding the gate.

Baidel walked towards the guardian and showed him a white name card.

The latter bowed his head down and stood beside the door.

The giant door opened automatically without making any noise.

Garen followed Baidel as they entered the room.

Inside, it was similarly structured to a meeting room. Everything was white and the ceiling was chiseled to resemble a silver flower. Four vivid, white stone Pegasi, each a man’s height, adorned each corner of the room.

There was a circle of black sofas in the middle and two people were already sitting there.

One of them was wearing black bordered spectacles and had mustache fully covering his lower jaw. He was wearing a neat black suit and gave off a vibe similar to that of an artist.

The other person was a man without a single strand of hair on his face. He had his dark golden hair combed towards the back neatly. He was a dreary looking middle-aged man with a smile on his face.

Both of them glanced at Garen who had just entered the room.

"Baidel, have you brought Captain Nine Head? What a rare occasion. It’s my first time seeing Nine Head Captain even though we’re both from Kovitan Empire. How embarrassing." The fair man stood up as he welcomed Garen by holding his hands and smiling.

"I am Senda Tungus. I believed His Majesty has already mentioned me to you right?"

Garen recalled that Avic did mention Earl Senda, who was the only one with substantial authority within Kovitan’s Secret Service, excluding the foreigners.

Garen started sizing this man who stood in front him. This man who had swollen eyes and pale face, he obviously didn’t look very healthy. He had a white emblem which resembled a white bonfire placed in front of his chest.

"Nice to meet you. My name is Garen and I suppose you already know that, right?" Since the opposing party had already told him his actual name, Garen did not have any intention to hide within the shadows as well.

"I’ve heard of you since a long time ago!" Senda shook Garen’s hand with tangible respect.

"Captain Nine Head, you’ve arrived at the right moment." The other person stood up. "Earl Senda had come here to request for my assistance. Since everyone knows about the condition within the capital, we can’t provide the proper amount of safety personnel, let alone extra people from other departments."

Garen glanced at the purple emblem placed in front of this person’s chest and immediately inferred that this man was Marquis Yawei, the Headquarter’s Deputy Director, the manager of the Nine Color Team and also the team leader of the Purple Team.

"Requesting assistance?" Garen was confused.

"Yes. As of now, the Kovitan’s Headquarter’s main support towards the kingdom is to clear off creature’s nests to recover back some territories and kill the rebels from the Black Sky at the same time. However, Earl’s Green Team has run into some troubles this time." Marquis Yawei said as he nodded. "Before you came back, the General Director had already held a meeting but due to the lack of manpower, we had no choice but to request the Green Team to endure for a little more."

"What actually happened?" Garen frowned.

"I’ll tell you more about it later. First, let me reward the Red Team." Marquis Yawei waved his hand as he walked towards the Pegasus Sculpture and took a small white crystal ball.

With the crystal ball in his hand, he walked back towards where everyone was.

"This is your reward for completing the high difficulty mission. It was offered by the General Director that you shall be promoted to the White level."

He gently tapped onto the white crystal ball.

Pew!

The crystal ball opened up like a flower petal as countless of white layers opened up, revealing a white diamond shaped gemstone.

This white gemstone was levitating as it rotated on its own axis as it gave off a faint white glow.

Baidel, who was standing beside Garen, explained softly to him.

"The reward is ranked by the nine colors, which is red, orange, yellow, light green, dark green, blue, purple, white and silver respectively. White color is the second highest next to the silver reward and this reward is determined by the difficulty of the mission!. A single white gemstone can be exchanged for 1000 mission points!"

Garen didn’t know how much would 1000 mission points amount to but a benefit was still a benefit. He carefully received the white gemstone from Yawei and placed it into his pocket.

"Furthermore, your Red Team had surpassed the quota. According to the overall strength assessment, do you want to increase your team’s rank?" Yawei continued.

"Isn’t it more troublesome to increase my rank?" Garen questioned back.

"Yes, as you will need to compete with the team above you. It is the test of overall strength."

"There’s no need to rush that for now." Garen shook his head.

"How about my problem…?" Earl Senda butted in from the side. He looked like he lacked quite an amount of blood and appeared to be recovering from a serious injury.

"It is indeed troublesome. We are currently in a decisive period and we can’t spare any men." Yawei replied with difficulty. "Perhaps you should go and ask Captain Nine Head?"

"Senda shook his head as hopelessness was written all over his face.

"We won’t have enough time if we were to gather people here and we don’t have much time even if captain Nine Head agrees to it. Whatever, I will go back and let the rest know that this mission is a failure."

"If you say so." Yawei smiled wryly. "I have already pulled the man out earlier from that area."

Senda pulled at his hair in distress as he acted in an un-noble manner. He then left the meeting room alone after bidding goodbye to Garen and Yawei.

Garen then listened to the explanations of the situation in detail from Marquis Yawei and Baidel.

The majority of Kovitan’s strength had been sent out to clear out the creature’s nests in order to recover back the stolen territories. However, as there were wins and loses with every battle that had been fought, the current situation had both sides locked in a stalemate. The higher rankings within the Secret Service would have continued eradicating the creature’s nests if not for this ceremony of trust.

The Three Departments, the National Service, Secret Service and Geometry Service were each in charge of different things and the most troublesome one was handled by the Kovitan Empire itself. They had pushed in about a third into the West Farm’s defense line and had recovered about half of the original land.

However, totem users were unable to maintain and service their totems as they were short of gemstones. Furthermore, the numbers of creatures outside were practically endless and didn’t seem to be decreasing at all.

It wasn’t just Kovitan that was in trouble; Daniela was in the same situation. Ender Kingdom was slightly better off as they had the Giant Divine Statue. However, rumor had it that they’d lost two Giant Divine Statues recently to a giant dragon which had three transparent Cicada wings. The Ender Kingdom was in full defense mode and was urgently gathering strong individuals to fight off this army of creatures.

It was the same reason why the poisonous hag from before wanted to go back to Ender Kingdom.

"In a nutshell, the Royal Alliance’s movement is grinding to a halt. The three major domains, which are the Dragon Domain, Rainbow Domain and Black Domain seem to have formed their own alliance as well. This is to be expected as they need to fend off the strong creatures. Under these circumstances, His Majesty plans to reevaluate each profession and revamp the country’s overall system, as a stronger army won’t be able to continue battling without the help of a practical profession."

It was natural that Marquis Yawei knew this much due to his social standing.

Chapter 414: Buffer 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"We Kovitan are lacking the supply of different kinds of gemstones and the same for our food stock. The disasters have been much worse recently and the Black Field, which the Black Prince is about to bridge us to, has the resources that we urgently require. The Dragon Field’s overall geographical structure is similar to of a basin. The inner region is a plains area with all sorts of crops and minerals. As their defense was good enough, they didn’t suffer a lot during the chaos. However, they are sorely lacking in powerful individuals and the only form four totem user is the Black Prince himself, and it’s not enough to protect the entire Dragon Field."

"I heard that the Black Prince is extremely gifted…" Garen butted in.

"It takes time to convert potential to actual strength. No matter how gifted you are, you’re still weak if you do not have strength." Yawei shook his head as he said. "Hence, no matter if it’s His Majesty or the Black Prince, we have to view them in high regards. If this two were to collaborate together, it would be beneficial to everyone."

"So the reason why so many powerful individuals have returned isn’t because of the trust ceremony but of the alliance between Kovitan and Dragon Field." Marquis Yawei summarised.

"I understand now. It felt weird that we would require so much security just to hold a trust ceremony. The main objective is to let the Black Prince witness our strength." Garen nodded.

"I’m glad you understand. To be frank Garen, you have already reached the upper class of form four so you’ll definitely have a notable influence in the Kingdom. I don’t need to tell you this but soon a lot of people will try and get closer to you. As an ally and a person who has been in your shoes, I suggest it’s best for you to befriend someone who can help you out. You don’t have to keep interacting with those inferior to you as it won’t be beneficial to you and you may even trap yourself with overconfidence." Marquis Yawei said.

As the leader of the Purple Team and a form four totem user, it was obvious that he was befriending Garen and planned to get closer to him.

"Thank you for your reminder. I have this in mind as well but unfortunately, I don’t know anyone." Garen shrugged his shoulders.

"That’s simple." Yawei smiled. "I have a friend from the Headquarter who is going to visit Kovitan and we decided to gather with a few friends of mine. We’re all of the same level and we talk to each other quite a lot."

"Someone from the Headquarter?" Garen squinted his eyes.

"Yea. The Headquarter’s structure is different from the Administration’s. Their main objective is to coordinate the relationship between each country’s Administration and most of the people inside are promoted from their respective country’s Administration. This good friend of mine was the General Director of the Kovitan’s Administration. Oh right, he is currently on the verge of becoming a form five and has been preparing himself for quite some time."

Garen was slightly stunned as he was currently at a loss of understanding about the Existing Mode of form five totems. His Nine-Headed Hydra was considered the pinnacle within the Animal series. He didn’t know what had been used for form five totems as its core as even the Nine Head Dragon was no match to their totem’s potential.

God Cloud’s comment towards the Nine-Head Dragon was that it had reached its limit. Garen couldn’t grasp the Existing Mode of the core totem at that level.

"Then… May I have the luxury of attending this gathering?" Garen asked directly.

"That’s naturally a yes. My friends have not been in good terms for a long time. They were from the same Academy and God Cloud was very arrogant and didn’t consider anyone superior to him there. Every one of us is very happy that you are able put him at a disadvantage. It is also because of this that this circle of friends has been wanting to talk to you directly. Do you think I would invite you if it’s only me with this intention? Marquis Yawei started laughing loudly.

"It is an honor." Garen smiled back with hope brimming in his eyes.

"To be frank, there are only ten or so form five users in the whole Eastern Continent including the Elder Parliament. It is too difficult to achieve that level…" Marquis Yawei sighed. "I encountered lots of hardships to reach the peak of form four and has been stagnating here for sixty years. It’s been sixty years and I’m still at this level."

He started to recall his memories as his voice slowed down.

"My daughter, granddaughter, and great-granddaughter have all grown up. Just a few days ago, I attended my daughter’s funeral… It’s funny, isn’t it? She was just a commoner who lived for eighty plus years and she went to the other world earlier than me…"

Garen could feel the sadness in his tone.

It’s rare for them to be able to talk to each other this easily, hence it took Garen about an hour or so before he left the meeting room.

They had decided the time and place for the gathering and Garen had obtained a lot of intel that he couldn’t obtain through Yawei.

As he got out of the room, he saw the members of Red Team had been waiting for him, as if they were waiting for something.

Garen smiled and took out the white gemstone from his pocket.

"White color!!" Kitten was the first one to shout but immediately covered her mouth. She almost jumped in joy as she hugged Fox who was standing beside her.

Old Man and Red Umbrella were laughing happily.

Kid cracked a smile as well.

Garen handed the diamond-shaped gemstone to Fox. They then went into the Red Team’s room where there was a machine for them to enter the white gemstone’s information into the Red Team’s mission point’s folder.

The system would automatically divide the mission points based on the performance.

It was a highly advanced technology.

"Everyone will have a month long holiday and will continue to rest if there are no mission afterwards. So it’s basically free activity from here on." Garen smiled as he announced the arrangement.

"Team leader is the best!" Kitten shouted.

The others smiled happily as well.

"Kid, you can follow me if you have nowhere else to go," Garen said softly to Kid as he smiled at him.

"Sure." Kid was the diverse type in the Red Team and couldn’t be promoted as he wasn’t strong enough. However, he was definitely unique or else the previous captain wouldn’t have paid attention to him at all.

Garen knew that there were mysterious people within each of the groups.

Garen left Well’s Castle with Kid and both of them had a quick lunch in a restaurant that they’d picked without much consideration.

It was totally different from the Kingdom he’d visited previously. A lot of the citizens had opened up restaurants and they didn’t have to squeeze with each other when they were purchasing items. It looked like society was starting to get back on track.

Occasionally, guardians in white armor would patrol the streets and the amount of homeless people had been reduced drastically. Avic’s policies appeared to be rather effective.

Kid and Garen were on the streets. Instead of using a horse carriage, they cut through an alley and soon arrived at the Kingdom’s War Guild division.

The division was built at a corner of a crossroads and was a grey stone door built into part of a chain building.

There was a brass copper name plate outside with ‘Milvus Tide’ engraved on it.

Occasionally, people in black cloaks would enter and exit the place.

Garen put his mask on and entered the Milvus Tide together with Kid.

Inside, it was peaceful, the silence broken by only the sound of a violin, which was soft and gentle, giving off a soothing vibe.

The Milvus Tide was a very quiet bar.

The seats were organized in double sofas for each unit and each unit would have one double sofa. The units were then separated by an opaque glass wall, forming a small semi-open studio.

It was rather dim inside as the only light source was the yellow light from the candles by the walls.

People were walking into and exiting from each unit constantly.

There was a rectangular bar on the left side of the entrance. There was a bartender insider preparing a drink for a woman in a red shirt. His hands moved so fast that only the after shadows could be seen.

Garen entered together with the curious Kid and a man in black shirt immediately came up to him.

"Sir, have you made any reservation?"

"No. I’m here to find a forger," Garen said coldly. As he was about to show his emblem, his hand stopped moving as he realized that his emblem had been destroyed by God Cloud’s chain at the Snowy Peak.

"Kindly show me your guild’s emblem so that we can arrange a forger for you based on your rank." The bouncer requested respectfully.

"Erm… I have accidentally lost my emblem." Garen said hopelessly.

"You can use mine." suddenly Kid’s voice came from beside him and handed over a black emblem to the bouncer with his fragile, small hand. The black emblem had circles of tread patterns on it.

"Honored customer, please follow me." It seemed that the emblem’s rank wasn’t low at all.

Garen patted Kid’s head as he thanked him.

Two of them followed the bouncer deep into the bar and settled down on a unit with a silver textured black sofa.

"Please wait for a moment." The bouncer left together with the emblem. After a short while, a white-bearded old man came rushing in with a crutch.

"I am the forger in this guild. May I ask what kind of service are you looking for? Excluding the highest rank, every services are half off."

"I wish to upgrade my war chain." Garen pulled up his sleeves and showed the diamond-shaped marking on his biceps.

"War Chain?" The forger studied the marks on Garen’s hand. "What grade do you wish to upgrade to? With the restriction of your emblem, we can increase it by five grades for you here. Every grade will give you a Solidifying Tactic Space. You’ll have a total of eight Tactic Spaces once you reached grade five."

"What is the cost for each upgrade?" Garen asked softly.

"You’ll need twenty thousand gold rumbs for each upgrade. Furthermore, we also have a few Solidifying Tactics for our customers to choose from." The old man’s attitude was very humble due to the black emblem.

One gold rumb was equal to a thousand Iron Tank City currency. Twenty thousand gold rumbs meant that it would be equal to twenty million, which was the same price as the War Chain Garen bought.

However, if the War Chain were to be nurtured, it would be rather effective as it would form a solid and strong team.

Chapter 415: Goodbye 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen pondered for a while, as he only had a few hundred gold rumbs with him at the moment. He couldn’t even upgrade for even a grade with the current amount he had. What’s worse was that this was considered a huge amount even for a noble.

He didn’t expect that an upgrade would be this expensive.

As Garen sighed, Kid beside him pulled his sleeves.

"Captain, I have some gold rumbs that should be enough for your upgrade. Do you want me to lend you some?"

"You do?" Garen was slightly surprised.

"Yeah. I typically trade the items I do not need for money after missions and I have nothing to spend them on." Kid laughed as he told the bouncer. "My emblem is directly linked to the Kingdom’s bank account. You can directly take the money out from my Emblem for the upgrade."

Garen was speechless.

"Never thought that I would depend on you all the way through."

"It’s fine. I don’t know how to spend all this money anyway and it’d be a waste if I were to hold onto them." Kid didn’t mind at the very least.

The bouncer looked at the white-bearded old man.

This old man nodded his head.

"Then, how many grades do you wish to upgrade by, dear customer?"

Garen didn’t pull back his punches at all.

"If you can upgrade it to the maximum, that would be great."

"That’s not a problem at all." The old man replied with confidence." However, it would require some time."

"How long do you need?"

"You may have to wait until night time. We need to first analyze the state of your chain and design the War Chain based on your compatibility. Within this period, you will have to pay the deposit and we will notify you when the time has arrived. You may entertain yourself here while you wait. Time will surely pass in a blink of an eye."

The bouncer then walked forward and introduced what they had here.

"Here we have casino, pleasure area, Sant Table Game and also battle gambling area. Two of you may freely choose which one you desire."

"There are a lot of well-trained men and women who can fulfill your desires in the pleasure zone. The Sant Table Game is one of our unique games here where the sand table is modeled by totem light and the customers can freely control the items on top of it to commence their battles. The battle gambling area is where customers sort their dilemma and is also a gambling activity as well."

Garen didn’t expect that there would be so many activities here as the environment looked similar to of a bar.

"It should be the underground of this place, right?’

"Yes." The bouncer replied immediately.

Garen pondered for a moment.

"I think we’re fine. I will come and retrieve it later tonight as I have things to attend to."

"That’s fine as well. We will always welcome the two of you." The bouncer responded with respect.

Garen left the bar with Kid and waiting for a normal horse carriage at the entrance.

"Go to Cloud Light District Tanning Street No. 128."

"Alright."

Garen threw a silver rumb over as he sat at the back of the carriage with Kid, and they watched the streets behind slowly disappearing from their sight.

"Where are we going now?" Kid asked.

"Since you have nowhere to go, you might as well just follow me." Garen smiled as he answered.

"Alright." Kid lowered his head and took out a piece of paper and pen from nowhere and started drawing.

The Kingdom was separated into three major districts.

The Palace District, Cloud Light District and Trading District.

The Cloud Light District was where the guardians and nobles gathered. The Palace District was where all the Royal members lived in and the Trading District was where all the common citizens resided and trading occurred.

Garen recalled the first time he appeared in this world, the first person he met. Everything was long in the past in a blink of an eye and he couldn’t stop himself from feeling emotional about it.

***************

Cloud Light District, on the street beside a three-story white building.

Hathaway still had a golden ponytail and was beautiful as ever. She also gave off a rather strict vibe.

She was kneeling on her single bed as she was trying to place a newly given order at the wall of her bed.

Her white undergarments highlighted her beautiful curves.

Hathaway pouted as she held it up, firmly pressed onto the glue and took a step back only to realize that it was slightly slanted. She then went back, pulled it down and attempted to place it nicely once more.

She had always been this serious when it came to doing anything. As long as it didn’t meet her standard, she would do it over and over again.

The afternoon light shimmered through the window and glowed on the wooden floor beside the bed, a faint yellow sheen reflecting off.

Since the incident in Vanderman’s manor, she’d returned to the Kingdom and continued her duty as the Lieutenant of the Royal Guards. She was not a totem user and wouldn’t be of any use during the war, so she could only maintain the basic order inside the Kingdom.

"Are you alright Sophie?"

A clear female voice came from outside of her room. "Isn’t it just a captain’s order? Even if you lose it you can get a new one at the Archives. Why do you have to be so vigilant about it?"

"It’s almost done," Hathaway replied loudly.

"Where’s your sister Dani?" The female asked.

"I think she went to the lake again. She and her friends had planned to relax there."

"Your family has very little relatives." The woman said softly.

Hathaway slightly smiled.

Compared to her cousin brother’s household, her relationship with her relatives were a level apart. In addition to her straight personality, which no one found likable, her relationship with her relatives had gradually died off.

She was currently living alone. The horrifying battle at the manor was more like a dream, as it became more and more unrealistic as days passed.

Her peaceful life seemed to be able to hold on until the day she died of old age.

"Perhaps this is better since this is the life of a commoner." She sighed as she was about to get up from her bed.

Knock knock knock.

Suddenly, someone knocked on the door rhythmically.

"Who is it?" Hathaway asked loudly as she pulled on her royal guard’s uniform and ran towards the main door at the living room.

"I’ll open it!"

The woman’s voice appeared once again and then the next thing was the sound of her footsteps.

Click.

The door on the first floor was opened.

West Virginia was stunned as she looked at the two people standing by the door and couldn’t grasp what the situation was at the time.

Two black-shirted men stood at the entrance. They had cloaks over their silky smooth uniforms as if it was a uniform of a certain department. Their collars were placed up high with a golden Iris flower sewn into its sides.

The two of them were very eye-catching.

A handsome face paired with fair skins and golden hair at shoulder length. In addition to that, he also had three red dots on his forehead which formed into a triangle and gave off a rather strange vibe. She could also see her own reflection through his pair of red irises.

"May I ask… who are you looking for?" West Virginia asked softly as she completely ignored Kid, who was beside Garen.

"This is where Sophie Hathaway live right?" The golden-haired man asked calmly.

"Yes."

"Then we’re good." He smiled as he looked at West Virginia’s redden face. "I am her cousin brother, Garen Trejons. I’m here to visit my cousin sister."

"Cousin brother?" West Virginia’s eyes were wide open as she heard Hathaway mentioning that she had a cousin brother in the past but she hadn’t mentioned about this person recently. As a colleague and a friend, she rarely heard about Hathaway talking about her household at all.

"Sophie! Your cousin brother is here! Quickly have a look." She immediately turned her head and shouted.

Garen looked at the woman in front of him.

"She seemed to be about twenty-two or three years old and had a grey-brown ponytail and was wearing the royal guard’s silver armor. This armor didn’t have any defense capability and was merely used for decoration purposes. It was placed tightly onto the woman’s body, revealing the woman’s body figure to its maximum. There were also delicate and detailed patterns on it and a few decorative white crystals lining.

It was obvious that this woman in front of him was his cousin sister’s colleague. The royal guard was separated into two sections, where one section was the honor guard where they were used for public relation to show the glory of the royal family and the other was an actual team where they would perform a royal guard’s duty.

It seemed that his cousin sister had been transferred to the Honor Guard team.

His cousin sister was an expert among the commoners who had gone through countless of dangerous missions and obtained the Astronomical Edict. However, commoners were not really of any use during the chaotic period and it might’ve been the reason she was transferred.

This woman in front of him was elegant. She wasn’t considered beautiful but her rating would be above average. Her beautiful long legs were very eye-catching as they were firm, long and it outlined her curves and tight hips. Although her skin wasn’t very fair and she didn’t really have any bust, she was giving off a realistic sexy vibe. Unlike Aquarius who was close to perfection, but somewhat unrealistic.

"May I know who you are?"

"Oh! My name is West Virginia. I’m Sophie’s colleague and friend! Since you are Sophie’s cousin brother, you should call me sister as well, right?" West Virginia turned around and smiled.

Garen and Kid walked into the living room and saw his cousin sister Sophie in the same silver armor coming down from upstairs.

"Cia!?" Sophie called out his previous name the moment she saw Garen. Her eyes were filled with worry. "What took you so long to visit me? Has something happened?" She was not a totem user and didn’t really have a good networking so she didn’t really know what happened in the world of a totem user. Naturally, she didn’t know that Garen was no longer her weak cousin brother.

"Sister Sophie, where’s Dani?" Garen went towards her and gave Sophie a hug.

Two of them sat down on the red sofa beside the wall and a green parrot could be seen chirping and hopping about inside the silver cage.

"Dani has gone out with her friends. You could have met her if you visited this morning. She’s been getting crazy lately and I couldn’t control her any longer."

Sophie Hathaway shook her head hopelessly.

As she stared at her cousin brother in front of her, her worry had finally settled down.

The Hathaway household was just a branch of the Trejons family from her generation onwards, hence her connections with the other relatives had distanced quite a bit. However, if not for the care his uncle had provided her since young, she wouldn’t have become a Lieutenant of the Royal Guard. With her unconditional love towards the only successor of the Trejons Household, she didn’t even consider the relationship changes towards her cousin brother.

Chapter 416: Goodbye 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I haven’t seen Dani for a long time. It’s unfortunate since I’m rarely free to be able to." Garen shook his head. "Whatever, the reason I came here today was to see how cousin sister is doing. Just voice out if you need any help."

Sophie looked at the person in front of him, once an immature kid. Cia was once a gambling addict who was kicked around all the time by a horrible woman named Aquarius. As time went by, that useless boy had matured and was able to sustain the Trejons Household all by himself.

"I don’t need any help here. Your life should be a mess since the situation in your household isn’t that well, right?"

"Eh…" Garen awkwardly rubbed his nose. His household’s situation was indeed dire, but he wasn’t the management type and had accidentally forgotten about the Household.

"I’m working on it." He said softly.

"I believe you can do it." Sophie Hathaway patted Garen’s shoulder. Two of them had decided to forget about the awkward ordeal of getting married.

"Let me introduce you a good friend of mine, West Virginia." Sophie Hathaway averted her attention towards West Virginia. "She’s slightly older than you so you’ll have to call her sister."

"Sister West Virginia." Garen put away his position as a captain and called out to her. Kid, who was beside him, had his mouth wide open as he saw a drastic difference in Garen’s personality. He couldn’t believe what he just witnessed.

"It’s definitely something to be Sophie’s cousin. You’re so handsome!" West Virginia openly got closer to Garen as she revolved around him to assess him. "Woah! You have a very good body! Your muscles are well built too." Without any hesitation, she reached out her hand and pinched Garen’s arm and the sensation of his muscles made her inhale loudly.

Sophie helplessly shook her head as she looked at Garen.

"Alright West Virginia, stop fooling around. This is my cousin brother Cia. Oh right, he’s changed his name. He’s called Garen now."

Garen was speechless as he looked at this woman with beautiful legs circle him and assessed him as if he were some sort of rare species.

"Alright alright. Didn’t you have other things to attend to? Go and do your stuff!" Sophie blocked her best friend who was getting out of control. "Quickly!"

"Hmm… Sophie, you don’t want your best friend anymore now that you have your cousin brother?" West Virginia acted in mock pity.

"Didn’t you have your part-time work to attend to?" Go!" Sophie gently hit West Virginia.

"Ouch! That hurts." West Virginia was sent out of the door by Sophie, and the living room finally quietened down.

She turned her head around, and only then did she realized that Garen had Kid, who was in the same black shirt as him, by his side. This black-shirted man’s existence was so low-key that she had completely neglected him.

"This is?"

"He’s my colleague. He’s currently working with me in the Kingdom." Garen simply introduced him and didn’t explain further. Kid’s history was mysterious and was most likely related to totem users. As a commoner, it would be disadvantageous for Sophie Hathaway to know more about him.

Hathaway didn’t pursue further as well. They sat down and started to talk about the past with Garen.

She originally planned to ask Garen about what happened in the past, but things got turned around, and she was the one being asked instead.

After coming back to the Kingdom, she returned to her old job as the royal guard. As she had just finished a mission recently, she had been promoted to First Lieutenant. Her lifestyle was simple. However, as she had to spend a lot of time at work lately, she had neglected Dani, she had been mixing in with the delinquents all day long.

"You have to help me with her. Dani doesn’t even listen to me anymore! We had an argument last night because I didn’t give her enough money allowance." Sophie frowned as she mentioned about Dani. "You guys got along in the past so maybe she will listen to you. I can’t do anything anymore."

"It’s alright, Dani is currently going through a rebellious phase, she’ll come to her after some time. Wasn’t I the same? I still have a lot of the poems I’ve written back in my place." Garen laughed.

Time passed as he talked with his cousin sister.

It was unfortunate that cousin sister didn’t have the attribute to become a totem user. The death rate was too high for any modification experiment, not to mention the intense pain she’d have to go through. Without an absolute control over the Secret Technique, her life would be meaningless even if she were to be modified.

It’s best for her to live the rest of her life as a commoner.

He listened to his cousin sister talked about her lifestyle, which was gentle and peaceful. There was no killing, no conspiracy, just a little bit of quarrel between relatives which would return to normal after a few days. After a hectic day, her wish was to have a good meal, take a good, relaxing bath and have a good sleep.

This kind of gentle lifestyle was so much better than his current one, where he could die at any moment.

As Garen listened to his cousin sister’s interesting stories, he unconsciously recalled the days he had on Earth. It was the same lifestyle as hers, simple and gentle.

"Sister Sophie, the reason I come here today is to tell you something important."

"Something important?" Sophie blinked.

"If, and only if, something major happens to the Kingdom, I want you to head to this address immediately." Garen gave her the paper that he had prepared earlier.

Sophie received it and had a look at it.

"White Phoenix Forest Academy?"

"Yes." Garen nodded his head. "Remember. If something happens, you have to go to this place with Dani immediately."

Sophie nodded as she understood the importance of this as she realized how serious Garen was. "I understand. I will."

The White Phoenix Forest was one of the rare places which would be unaffected when the Kingdom was in trouble. This was because the dean was one of the two Grand Dukes of the Kingdom, who was also Prynne’s grandfather. He was the third strongest individual in the Kovitan Empire.

If the assassination of Avic becomes a success, the place that would not be in any trouble would definitely be there.

The Kingdom had more than ten academies, and the White Phoenix Academy didn’t stand out because no one knew that the dean of the academy was one of the Grand Dukes. The performance of the academy had been rather low profile as well, so the Obscuro Society didn’t really pay attention to this place. No one would know that this academy had set up a powerful Tactical Alliance Formation.

Garen wouldn’t need to rush to save her if she were to seek refuge there when there was trouble.

This was the main reason he was here today.

The sky gradually became darker.

Sophie was busy making a sumptuous dinner to have a feast with Garen, who rarely visited.

She had cooked some expensive foie gras, bird’s breast and even boiled a big bowl of fresh fish soup. This was considered a delicacy in the Kingdom, who was in shorts of resources.

In addition, there even was chicken meat surrounded by a big bowl of vegetables.

"This is the new aberrated meat His Majesty just passed. It’s one of those meat only a selected few can get their hands on. Do you want to try some?" Sophie gave Garen a piece of golden meat. She then proceeded to dip some concentrated black salad sauce onto the chicken meat.

Garen took a bite. The taste was delicious, and the meat was very tender. However, the fragrance was too strong, giving off a slight stuffy feeling.

"Should we leave some for Dani?" He looked at Kid beside him. This guy’s stomach seemed like a black hole as he kept eating without any sign of slowing down at all. For some reason, Sophie didn’t seem to notice his existence. It was obvious that it was the mysterious power to mask his presence was in its full effect.

"I have left some out already. It’s fine." Sophie smiled.

The sky had become dark.

As the three of them were having their dinner, the first-floor door opened, and someone seemed to have entered the building.

"Sister! What’s with the aroma!?" A clear voice of a young girl came from below.

"It’s Dani, she has returned." Sophie frowned. "You have to help me out. I’m afraid she might go onto the wrong path if she continues like this."

"Alright, leave it to me. I haven’t seen her for a long time too." It was rare that Garen was able to enjoy such a peaceful lifestyle and he unknowingly put his guard down. He didn’t want to destroy this peaceful feeling.

Soon, a young teenager with shoulder-length black hair came upstairs. This young girl seemed to be eighteen or nineteen years old and was wearing a tight white shirt which revealed her tummy. She was also wearing ultra-short black leather shorts, revealing a pair of white, long legs.

The supposedly mildly sexy attire was nothing jarring. However, the entire vibe was changed entirely after some modifications made by Dani to her getup.

The long sleeve on the left of her shirt was completely cut off, revealing her white arm. She even had a tattoo of a rather complicated black tactic symbol on her arm. These symbols didn’t seem to have any totem light, which meant that it was obviously just an imitation.

The girl had thick makeup on her small face, which gave off a rather matured look. All of the five fingers on her right hand were filled with fake red gemstone rings, with imitated tactic symbols on them. In addition to that, there even were some strange, beautiful patterns that Garen had never even seen before carved onto the ring as well. It was obvious that the small merchants had designed it themselves to allow the ring to give off a more mysterious vibe.

With a small chest on her body, the lady rushed upstairs as she rushed over in a pair of black leather boots. She then noticed the additional two people sitting on the dining table. Kid’s existence was, of course, unnoticed by her, and her attention immediately landed on Garen.

"Acacia!!?"

"Call him brother!" Sophie’s mood suddenly changed for the worse.

"Why should I call him brother? Isn’t he just slightly older than me? Sister, I don’t have any money. I want more allowance to spend." Dani complained and reached her hand out as she walked towards Sophie.

"I don’t have any!" Sophie turned her head around and ignored her. "I just gave you fifty silver rumbs yesterday and you have already spent all of them?"

Fifty silver rumbs was equal to five hundred copper rumbs. With the current state of the Kingdom, A thousand silver rumbs would equal to about one gold rumb. It was considered a small amount to a totem user. However, fifty silver rumbs were enough to sustain a family of three commoners for a month.

Garen calculated in his mind and found out that it was about five hundred to eight hundred dollars on Earth. It was considered a big amount for a child to be able to spend all of it within a day. No wonder his cousin sister, who was considered a highly paid commoner, was angry about it.

"Isn’t it just a small amount of money? Rafier could easily spend three hundred silver rumbs per week." Dani was getting impatient. "Are you going to give it to me or not?"

"I’m not giving them to you!" Sophie replied coldly. "If you dare to steal and sell off the things in my house again. I will break your leg!" She immediately raised her voice.

"I would like to see you try!" Dani had no intention of backing down at all.

"Alright alright. It’s just a small amount of money. There’s no need for you two sisters to argue."

He gently placed a hundred silver rumbs onto Dani’s hand.

Garen smiled as he butted in.

"Wow!" Dani whistled. "You’re amazing Cia. Have you become rich in the time we hadn’t seen each other?" She flicked the paper money with an elated heart.

Sophie was about to voice out but she saw Garen looking at her with the intention of telling her that he would handle it.

Feeling helpless, she didn’t say anything further.

"I think it’s about time. I still have some stuff to handle. I will visit sister Sophie again." Garen stood up and said gently.

"Alright. You may come any time you want, the door will always be open." Sophie nodded and stood up.

Garen and Kid were seen out by Sophie downstairs. As they were about to leave the place, Dani Hathaway unexpectedly followed along.

Dani’s eyes were moving about as if she had some brilliant idea.

"I’ll send them off!"

Sophie was stunned as she didn’t know that her sister would common courtesy. As she was about to speak up, she saw Dani was running towards Garen.

Suddenly, Sophie understood what Dani had in mind.

This fellow definitely was thinking of seducing Garen’s money.

Furious, she wanted to catch up to her but then she recalled Garen’s gaze and believed that he must have had some kind of plan in mind.

"Whatever. Let’s see what Cia can do."

Chapter 417: Surprise Guess 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen and Kid were walking down the dimly lit street. As they were about to board a horse carriage, they heard a paced footsteps coming from behind.

Dani Hathaway was chasing up to them. As she reached them, she bent down and tried to catch her breath.

"We haven’t met for so long Cia, and you wanted to leave already? Why don’t we go and play?" She asked with a welcoming face after catching her breath.

Her everyday life was rather boring, and it was rare that her past playmate would appear. To top it off, he seemed to be rich as well. She guessed that she could easily get some money out of him as long as she tried, since she was tight on money lately. She wouldn’t let go of such an opportunity since she had been quarreling with her sister lately.

Ever since the chaos started, she vaguely heard about what happened in Vanderman’s manor from her sister. However, she didn’t feel anything from it as she didn’t really interact with her uncle, and it was her sister who interacted with him often. She only had some memories of her playing with Acacia when they were young, and even these memories were soon placed at the back of her head.

The Kingdom was very safe and the number of refugees had increased due to the chaos. However, it was still peaceful.

Dani had heard how strong and fierce the creatures were outside the Kingdom, and anyone would be ripped apart if they went out. However, she had never seen these creatures in her life.

Garen, who came from outside the Kingdom, had gained her interest when she met him.

Garen glanced at Dani and turned around to Kid.

"You can go ahead first. I’ll find you later in the War Guild."

"Alright. I’m hungry anyway." Kid replied honestly.

After paying the fair for the horse carriage, the carriage gradually disappeared into the misty night.

Garen then turned towards Dani.

"Alright. I have things to attend to later so I can only accompany you for a bit."

"I understand." Dani grabbed hold of Garen’s arm. "Let me bring you somewhere interesting."

"What kind of place is it?" Garen had promised to teach Dani a lesson.

"Just follow me," Dani called for a horse carriage as she held onto Garen.

Two of them went to the border between the Cloud Light District and Trading District.

************

Within the noisy music, two women in blood red attire were dancing wildly on the stage. There was a huge crowd at the bottom, shouting wildly with their hands up high, occasionally throwing paper flowers onto the stage.

This was a bar.

As it was located between the Trading District and Cloud Light District, it consisted a huge area and most of the customers were all teenagers. Furthermore, all of them were wildly dressed.

A band composed of non-mainstream smart costume themed players were playing all sorts of instruments at one corner to the side.

There was a three-legged oval bar counter at the side of the entrance, and all the bartenders were young and beautiful. They were putting up a show for their customers as they mixed alcohol.

Garen swayed at the deepest corner of the bar counter as he looked at the wild crowd inside the dance floor.

Initially, he was worried that people would recognize him from his uniform. However, he hadn’t expected that everyone here would be wearing things much more eye-catching than his attire.

There were royal guards uniforms, royal special guards, army general attires, totem forger attires and so on. They were all deliberately designed costumes. The clothings were all made from common materials, and Garen would have thought that everyone here was the real deal if not for the absence of totem light.

As he looked closer, he found out that all of these uniforms were fakes.

Although the bar was very crowded, it was obvious that it had no class. The number of young totem users in the Kingdom was not a small amount, but their place of entertainment was definitely not of this level.

Garen could stare at the crowd for the whole day and would only see a single digit amount of totem users inside. They were the elites among their crowds, and no matter if they were male or female, they were always surrounded by a group of people. They formed one user at best.

It was rather clear that the majority of the customers here did not come from wealthy backgrounds, and this was just a place for all the commoners to vent out their emotions.

During this chaotic era, where commoners were completely useless and their social status hit rock bottom while the authority of totem users had increased, anyone would find the need to vent out their frustrations in this kind of environment. Hence, these kinds of places were born from this frustration, and everyone dressed up themselves to satisfy their ego. This was also the reason why everyone had heavy make up on so that no one would recognize them.

It was the first time Garen had attended this kind of activity in this world.

No matter if it was Acacia in the past or the current Garen, they all started as this world’s elites and had high social standing. Their place of entertainment would always be booked out beforehand.

As the son of a Viscount and a noble of a territory, Acacia’s social standing was equal to the Huaxia’s Governor’s son on Earth, and it wasn’t something a commoner could hope to match. The merchants and small nobles who tried to befriend him were as big as the ocean. This made it impossible for him to come to this kind of places.

Now, Garen was at the peak of the form four totem users and his actual battle strength was equal to of a common form five totem user.

Within the whole Kingdom, he was considered a person of major influence. Only the top brass from Kovitan Empire and the Three Departments were on equal footing with him. If this was Earth, his influence was similar to that of a prime minister.

However, due to his unique identity, he could only hide in the dark away from public knowledge.

As he leaned on the white bar stage, Garen lazily drank the purple liquor in his hand. The liquor even had bubbles foaming out of it endlessly.

In this kind of place, Garen’s unique face didn’t raise any suspicion to anyone, as everyone had some sort of glowing tattoo on them. There were even four or five of them that had strange earrings hanging on their ears, and the majority of them had white silver decorations on their eyelids.

However, there was a very little amount of people who didn’t have any makeup on, like him.

Garen was dragged to this place by Dani, who had mixed into the moshpit, enjoying the night with her friends.

"Hey, handsome guy? Are you alone?" A beautiful woman with golden hair and purple-red eyeshadow leaned towards him and looked at him in the eyes as she holds a transparent liquor in her hand.

She was just a commoner. Garen glanced at her and immediately lost interest.

"I’m sorry. I already have a partner." He politely responded.

The woman was stunned and she didn’t expect to be rejected and walked away in disappointment.

If it weren’t for Dani, Garen wouldn’t be wasting his time here.

No matter how fresh he felt from experience the life of a commoner, it was still not enough. With his identity and authority, it would be bad for him and the commoners.

As he looked at Dani moving her body wildly in the moshpit, he was relieved to see that she knew how to protect herself from people touching her body as she danced among the girls.

Or else Garen wouldn’t know how to face Sophie.

He drank the liquor in his hands as he quietly waited for Dani.

************

"Dani, is that guy really loaded with money?" A purple short haired girl asked Dani softly.

"Of course, didn’t you see what his shirt is made of? I’m telling you, that shirt alone costs this amount of digits!" Dani showed four fingers to her.

"Four hundred silver rumbs?!" The young girl was fourteen years old at best, but her face was filled with white powder and her eyebags were painted black, which made her look like a panda. She was quite satisfied with her own creativity, but she was covering her mouth to conceal her surprise.

"Four hundred!? I’m talking about four thousand!" Dani was smiling in delight.

The people in the vicinity were all shocked.

"Four thousand? Oh my god. No one would even ask for that much if someone were to sell me off!"

"Four thousand silver rumbs is enough for me to spend for an entire year!"

"Where did you find this rich handsome man?"

"Dani, I’m so envious of you!! Isn’t he richer than my cousin?"

Her friends were all envious of her and this made Dani felt very proud and satisfied. She secretly glanced at Garen who was far away. She had to admit that, within such a messy environment, Garen gave off a peaceful vibe as he lazily drank the purple liquor. His shoulder-length golden hair waved freely by the bar, paired with his handsome figure and firm muscles had separated him from the environment.

"My cousin said it! He said that he will be covering our expenses for the night!" Dani gestured her small hands happily.

"Oh yeah!!" A group of youngster suddenly shouted in joy.

Dani felt guilty as she looked at Garen and noticed that he was observing the beautiful liquid in the glass.

Garen noticed that he was being watched so he placed down the cup and smiled at her.

Dani felt even more guilty.

************

At the corner of the bar, there were two women who didn’t seem to fit into the environment.

They were sitting inside a unit separated by a glass wall. The sound isolation wasn’t bad and the mirror wall was a one way, where they could see everything from the inside.

One of them was in a black mini skirt, revealing her sexy body figure. She looked attractive, and could be considered a beautiful woman.

The other one was drunk, in white jeans and was hugging her legs tightly, revealing her perfect streamline body. She wore a black camisole and had her head placed on the table with her hair spread wildly, revealing two golden earrings on her ears.

"Oh… My head hurts…" The black haired girl moaned.

"Who told you to drink this much?"

These two often came to the bar. Although the environment was rather loud, their standards in bartending were high and were leagues away from the other bars. They initially came here to protect their sisters in the dark, but eventually grew accustomed to this place and knew each other quite well.

Whenever both of them were stressed, they would gather here and release it as best they could.

"But… it tastes good…" The black haired girl replied with her eyes closed.

"Whatever, take care of yourself because these kids are starting to become noisy again." The black skirted girl shook her head as she looked at the dancing pool. Dani, the panda girl, and another black skirted girl were moving their waists here and there. They seemed to have drank quite a bit as their faces were completely red.

"Dani seemed to have come here with her relative. Nini, do you want to go and say hi to him?" The black skirted girl asked softly.

"Sure." The black haired girl slowly got up from the table with her head swaying about freely. "If we can’t come here anymore in the future, at least we can tell him to help us out in taking care of these wild people."

Two of them got up, and the so-called Nini woman went to wash her face to freshen up a bit, before they walked to Garen, passing by the dancing pool.

As the duo arrived at where Garen was, another girl who thought she was relatively attractive was again rejected by Garen and was leaving the area angrily. Within this short amount of time, he had already rejected five ‘beautiful’ girls.

"If you’re here to hit on me, please turn right." Garen’s cold voice could be heard.

Two of them were stunned as the opposing party rejected them before they could say anything.

"I’m sorry, we’re not here to hit on you." Nini tidied up her long hair. "You’re Dani’s guardian, right? We are relatives of Dani’s friends, and we’re here for the same reason as you. We’re here to guard our kids."

After that, Garen looked at them straight in the eyes.

"I’m sorry, I’ve mistaken both of your intentions." He felt apologetic and reached out his hands and shook their hands.

"I’m Nini, Shaer’s sister. She’s the youngest among the group. This is Dilan, sister of the panda-eyed girl." Nini introduced herself.

"It’s a pleasure to meet the both of you." Garen smiled. "I’m Garen, Dani’s cousin."

"Pleasure to meet you."

The three of them sat down and ordered their favorite drinks from the bartender. They started talking to each other as they took a look out at their family members.

Chapter 418: Surprise Guess 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen also found out from his conversations with the two of them that they work at the Tax Department and Irrigation Department respectively.

The Irrigation Department, where Nini was from, was located on the street opposite the palace. Most of their casual conversation involved the nobles and officials moving in and out of the palace.

"Speaking of which, this morning I saw the First Concubine’s carriage leave the main hall and head towards the side hall. Last time I could still the Concubine’s flower-watching guards from afar, but now I haven’t seen them for a long time," Nini said casually.

Garen frowned slightly. "The First Concubine left the main hall today, but it’s Saturday, isn’t the ceremony the day after tomorrow?"

"So you know too." Nini looked at Garen in surprise, he had just said he worked at the capital, but that his job was secretive and he couldn’t speak about it. She didn’t think he would know about these details.

"Normally, any preparations for large-scale ceremonies would only end at least the day before the ceremony itself, but something must have happened. The First Concubine is in charge of many systems, she has a lot of things to handle." Nini said nonchalantly. "If it wasn’t for the fact that I noticed how regular the First Concubine’s guards are, I might not have noticed anything different either."

"Speaking of which, I heard someone mention, it seems that the First Concubine has indeed left the main hall early." The other person, Dilan, added on.

Garen didn’t think much of it at first, but once Dilan mentioned that term, a possibility occurred to him.

If the Aegis Ceremony was so important, would Avic possibly go ahead with it secretly? In order to prevent outside intervention?

In that case, he would just need to put on a show during the official ceremony, and it would be enough. The ceremony had already been completed beforehand, there was no need to worry it would be disturbed.

The more he thought about it, the likelier it seemed to Garen.

If this possibility really existed, then… Obscuro’s assassination attempt would probably also be brought ahead!

His heart grew slightly cold. Although he wasn’t particularly fond of Avic, he didn’t dislike him either. The main thing was if the ceremony and even the assassination were brought forward, it would be highly disadvantageous to his hold on the situation, as Obscuro would be one step ahead, and constantly ahead.

As he thought that, he began to grow restless.

Glancing at Dani and the others in the distance, he stood up slowly.

"Sorry, I suddenly remembered something urgent."

"It’s okay, go ahead." The two of them paused for a moment but didn’t really care, politely indicating that they would take care of Dani and the others.

After paying the bill for Dani and the others, Garen walked out of the bar and looked at its name: Dewdrop Bar.

Calling a carriage immediately, he hurried towards the War Guild. He needed a couple more days of understanding and contact to teach Dani, but this matter couldn’t wait.

He needed to make the preparations as soon as possible.

*****************

War Guild

It was still that Milvus Tide Bar.

As soon as Garen walked through the door, an attendant in black came up to lead the way.

The two of them went through the corridors and many sofa rooms, walking into a small corridor. The corridor had many lines of single rooms.

After knocking on a single room in the center, they found a child dressed in black sitting inside, together with two other people.

One was a pretty woman with blonde hair, who dressed extremely sexily, her shirt white skirt almost all the way up to the top of her thighs, but right now she was being totally ignored by Kid, her expression unbelievably awkward.

The other was that old forger from back then, holding a black box and frowning, thinking about goodness knows what.

"You’re here." Kid watched Garen come in, smiling slightly.

"Yeah, is everything ready?" Garen looked at the black box in the old man’s hand.

"Of course! With two masters personally on the case, there’s no way anything would go wrong!" Old Man touched his beard with a smile, standing up and giving the black box to Garen. "Just press it against the chain seal you had before."

Garen nodded and opened the box. Inside was a diamond-shaped white-silver ornament, carved hollow.

Vaguely, he could hear the sound of dense approaching footsteps from outside the room, evidently the people here to protect this transaction. This was such a valuable item worth millions, even the War Guild had to take it seriously. Unlike Iron Tank City, this place wasn’t lacking in manpower.

He picked up the ornament, and held up his sleeves lightly, pressing it determinedly against the seal of the War Chain from earlier.

Something strange happened.

The ornament actually liquidized quickly, slowly melting into Garen’s skin, melting in the War Chain seal that was already on his arm.

Garen glanced at his attribute pane, and saw the minute changes as expected.

‘War Chain:

Effect 1 -- Eye of Isaiah. Effect 2 -- None. Effect 3 -- None. Effect 4 -- None. Effect 5 -- None. Effect 6 -- None. Effect 7 -- None. Effect 8 -- None.

Collaborator -- Angel.’

"Eight tactic spaces in total, are you satisfied, sir?" Old Man asked with a smile.

"Satisfied, very satisfied!" Garen nodded. "You should have some Solidifying Tactics for sale here, right? May I choose some?"

"Of course, please come with me." Old Man nodded, his expression telling of how good his mood was just then. It was rare for someone to want to upgrade a War Chain so much at once, and to buy Solidifying Tactics too, that would invariably be a huge profit for the man himself.

Garen and Kid followed Old Man out of the private room, heading deep down a corridor, protected by a host of totem users in black until they finally reach the wall at the end of the tunnel.

Old Man reached out and patted the wall once, white light glowing on his palm.

The wall instantly rippled, and actually disappeared before everyone's eyes.

Garen's expression didn't change as he and Kid followed Old Man into the hall behind the wall.

It was a large and dark brown hall shaped in a circle, the walls lined with a circle of round glass display cases, and with a cylindrical display in the center of the room as well.

In these glass display cases, there were many strangely-shaped items scattered sparsely, none of them very big. Some were like little boxes, some were like live specimens of unnatural living organisms, and some looked utterly normal, like a mineral stone.

There was also a smattering of people in the hall, standing in three groups. They looked to be like Garen and co, Guild customers brought here to choose Solidifying Tactics by the people from the Guild.

"This is the display hall for Solidifying Tactics, please go ahead and point out anything you two might like to me." Old Man explained with a smile, "I can provide you two with the highest discount of 20%."

"Then I'll thank you for that." Garen smiled slightly. "Kid, you have money on your side?"

"No problem." Kid replied nonchalantly.

"Then please assume I'm borrowing it from you first, I'll return it to you in a bit." This time he was grateful to Kid, otherwise the War Chain's upgrading would prove to be a problem."

"It's okay, I don't know how to use the money anyway." Kid evidently really didn't care.

Garen nodded and didn't hold back anymore.

He walked to the counter and looked at them carefully, one by one.

As expected of the large kingdom capital's guild, it wasn't like Iron Tank City, where there were only a few choices of Solidifying Tactics. Here, they actually displayed them openly for everyone to choose, and a glance showed that there were no fewer than thirty items.

Garen followed the counter, checking them individually.

The Solidifying Tactics here were divided into three categories in total.

Self-strengthening types, Totem-strengthening types, and Special types.

Self-strengthening types meant they strengthened the totem user themselves, and this strengthening could affect the speed a Totem user can release a tactic, its powers, or how nimbly they can control a totem in battle and so on.

And totem-strengthening meant that the single totem would then be temporarily strengthened.

There were the most types in the last Special category, such as healing, scoping, night vision, underwater breathing, levitation, disguise, ice sealing and whatnot. These were all extra abilities for a totem.

Garen looked around him in a circle, but couldn't find the tactic he wanted. Although he knew the Eye of Isaiah that he had found was no ordinary tactic, but all these Solidifying Tactics didn't even come close, so Garen couldn't help but be a little disappointed.

Looking at the prices tags, these Solidifying Tactics were each worth ten thousand golden rumbs, which was equivalent to at least ten million copper rumbs, two or three of them were enough to buy a basic Level One War Chain.

As though seeing the look of disappointment on Gardens face, Old Man mused for a moment.

"How about this, other than the Solidifying Tactics our War Guild has, there are still some Solidifying Tactics we had planned to put up for auction, you can have an early look at them. See if there's anything you might want."

"Sure." Garen nodded.

Kid told him briefly how much he had in his own savings through the black box at his collar, he still had about twenty thousand golden rumbs. Added to the eighty thousand golden rumbs he had used earlier to upgrade to Level Four, he would have used a whole hundred thousand golden rumbs. That was a huge fee, even if the Trejons family sold off everything they had right now, they would only have at most forty or fifty thousand golden rumbs. This was including all of their solid assets and the land His Majesty the Emperor gave them, all of it added together.

Using so much of Kid's money this time, Garen felt a little ashamed, but now was the most crucial time, so he couldn't afford such concerns. There would be plenty of chances for him to return the favor later.

After waiting for a moment in the hall, Old Man sent someone to bring a catalog that he gave to Garen.

The catalog had the detailed information regarding five Solidifying Tactics, and was evidently the information for the auctions.

The first of these Solidifying Tactics was the Hand of Vandala.

It looked like a necklace pendant shaped like a golden palm. There weren't any special patterns on it.

It had a very simple effect. Aurification, it used a certain amount of Totem Light or totem power to turn a certain amount of a material into gold.

Although gold wasn't as precious as white silver here in this world, it was still a precious metal second only to white silver.

There were surely many totem users who would like this thing, but that definitely did not include Garen.

The second was called the Navy Blue Chain.

It also looked like a necklace, and was completely navy blue, with an irregular white stone suspended in the middle.

The effect of the Navy Blue Chain was Water-style Mist Territory, it could form a mist territory with a radius of twelve meters upon release, blocking the enemy's vision. The thickness of the mist depended on the strength of the totem user.

The third was called the Dematerialisation Badge.

Looking at this one, Garen's interest was slightly piqued.

It was just a picture that looked like a black flame.

Its effects were self-strengthening: upon activation, it could elementalize part of the totem user’s body, if the totem user was strong enough, they could totally use it to avoid a fatal blow, and they could use it to transmit across long distances as well. Of course, if it was a low-level totem user, it'd be impressive for them to elementalize even one fingernail.

The fourth and the fifth were both tactics used to strengthen totems. Garen gave them a glance, one was very effective with healing, the other could add the element of ice to the totem, allowing the enemy totem to take ice damage. Compared to regular strengthening tactics however, its effectiveness was a lot more overstated.

"How about this Dematerialisation Badge?" Garen pointed at the third Solidifying Tactic and asked.

"You have great taste, sir!" Old Man gave him a thumbs up. "This Dematerialisation Badge was found by one of the Guild’s great fighters in a monster's lair, they snatched it from the hands of Obscuro. In order to obtain this Badge, two of our elite Form Two totem users were grievously injured. Although elementalization was a necessary route to success for high-level totem users, wouldn't it be an extra level of insurance to first have access to this technique using a Solidifying Tactic?"

"Cut the crap, and just tell me, how much does it cost?" Garen was lazy to listen to his preamble.

"This much." Old Man held up four fingers. "And this is after I gave you two a special eighty percent discount."

"Forty thousand golden rumbs?!" Garen raised an eyebrow. He wanted to buy this mainly because he was interested in the elementalization, elementalization was something true totem users could use temporarily when Spiritualized. But the path Garen was pursuing didn't have anything to do with elementalization at all.

Although the Nine-Headed Hydra was powerful, in term of elementalization, and especially when.It came to the elementalization of the main body, it had no clue whatsoever. With this thing, perhaps he could peek at the secret high level totem users had for elementalization.

Chapter 419: Trace 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kid only had twenty thousand rumbs left, so it probably wasn't enough to buy this thing.

Garen mused over it for a while.

"Then forget for now, I'll come back when I get enough money."

Although elementalization items were interesting, that didn't mean this was the only place he could find them.

Garen was mostly worried that after the assassination began, the Kingdom would fall into chaos, and if the War Guild was caught in the conflict as well and couldn't provide upgrading services for the War Chain anymore, then that would be a problem.

Old Man was slightly disappointed too, but he didn't show it at all on his face."That's okay. Since the customer doesn't have enough funds, you can still buy it again later. We have a steady long-term supply of these Dematerialisation Badges, so I’m sure we won't disappoint you."

"Oh? Is it forgeable?" Garen's eyes lit up.

Old Man smiled but didn't reply.

"In that case, we'll take our leave now." Garen thought about it and decided to leave.

"Allow me to see the customer out."

************

Deep in the palace

Delouse wore along figure-fitting dark red dress, sitting quietly on the Concubine’s throne, one hand on her chin as her eyes wandered, thinking about something, goodness knows what.

The palace was dim and dark, with no lights and only black shadows flowing quietly in the corners.

The cold moonlight shone in from outside the large door, falling onto the floor in the middle of the large hall.

"How's the situation?" Delouse’s lips moved slightly, but her voice carried to the shadows in the corners softly.

"The defense minister is mending the holes in the Air Defense Department, and won't return until tomorrow morning. The Guard Captain Edin’s disciples came across some problems, so Edin went to deal with it. Now there's only that person left by Avic’s side." A sharp and reedy voice came from the dark corners.

"Is everything ready?" Delouse said calmly.

"Everything is fine. As long as we succeed, all the escape routes will be completely activated. Within five minutes, you will be able to leave the Kingdom."

Depose nodded.

"What about Veska's Three Fangdragon Generals?"

"They went with the defense minister."

"In other words, other than the three departments’ defense forces on the outside, there are already no more peak-level totem users in the core of the inner palace?"

"Naturally."

"That's good." Delouse nodded in satisfaction.

Looking at the pearly white moonlight on the floor. Veska’s old-fashioned and stern face flashed past her eyes.

"Veska, we've been fighting for so long, but this time, I want to see how you settle this…" The corners of her lips couldn't help but curve into a confident smile.

***************

Garen led Kid out of the Guild, and the more he thought about it, the more likely it seemed that the assassination would be brought forward. He couldn't bother with anything else anymore, and couldn't even wait for Angel at the War Guild, running straight for the palace.

The whole Kingdom was filled with edits fighters, but only a few could be stronger than him.

That was also why, as soon as he arrived at the entrance to the palace, there were already several elite guards blocking the way.

These people were evidently waiting especially for him.

"It's already late now, may we know why Viscount Garen is here at the palace?" The leader was a man in a full suit of white armor, even his face was wrapped up in a white helmet. His voice was deep, coming through the crack in the helmet so that his bright and sparkling eyes could be seen.

Gran stood at the entrance to the place, and behind him was the meeting area where only nobles could enter, so there were basically no outsiders around, all of them cleared out of the area by the guards.

He glanced at the white-armored guards in front of him. There was a small smile on his face.

"His Majesty had promised me the legacy of a Black Storm Dove totem, but unfortunately I never had the time to take it from the palace warehouse. Today I suddenly remembered it, so I came here and plan to bring one back."

"Black Storm Dove?" The Guard Captain’s eyes flashed with envy. He had heard of this bestowal before too, it was one of those rare times His Majesty generously gave a totem legacy. "So that's how it is, please forgive our insolence."

"No matter." Garen nodded. He turned around and glanced at Kid. "You're with me, or?"

Before Kid came here, Garen already warned him that this time might be slightly dangerous. With Garen’s tone, if he said it was dangerous, then it was probably a huge risk to him. So he didn't force himself at all, shaking his head.

"I'll wait for you outside."

"It's okay, you return to department headquarters first, wait for my news." Garen smiled and told him quietly.

Although Kid didn't know why he arranged it like that, he still nodded seriously, turning away and leaving without hesitation.

Garen looked around him in a circle.

He was surrounded by grey-black tall stone buildings, the palace’s stone walls surrounding this place, forming a small square in the crevice.

On either side of the square, there was a row of white-armored soldiers.

But for some reason, Garen felt as though something was slightly different from normal when he looked at these soldiers.

Yet he couldn't exactly say what was different.

Led by the white-armored guards, he walked straight in through the palace’s main gates.

Going through many black corridors, walking through two large black stone halls. He could also see that the guards in the halls were a lot fewer than before.

He hadn't gotten far when he saw a swordsman in heavy black armor running up from behind him with heavy footsteps.

"Your Excellency Viscount Garen, His Majesty is watching the power competition in the Ocean Wave Hall, and has invited you to join him."

"Power competition?" Garen paused for a moment and knew what kind of competition it was.

There weren't many forms of entertainment in the Kingdom, and Avic was an emperor who extremely enjoyed battles, so he started an internal ranking competition. All the ministers, families and nobles, even royalty, had to join this internal competition, in order to rank the top hundred in Kovistan’s Silver Palace.

Of course, this ranking didn't include real-life fighting experience and was merely a competition. Similar to a sports activity. Those in the top hundred were all given the title of Silver Palace Wingmaster.

It never occurred to Garen that they hadn't brought forward the ceremony to tonight, but were organizing the Silver Palace internal ranking competition instead.

"What a coincidence, I've never seen the Silver Palace competition before." Garen accepted graciously.

Following behind the black-armored guards, Garen turned down another corridor and continued walking.

After going through an open-air corridor, he saw a large and open white stone square in front of him.

In the middle of the arena, there was a tall square platform, with two huge beasts colliding madly into each other, one bear and one tiger, one black and one gold respectively.

The two huge beasts roared continuously, the black bear's speed extremely fast, while the golden tiger was lethargic. He kept trying to light up a golden glow in his mouth, but each time was interrupted by the black bear with one palm.

Two young men in glamorous clothes were standing behind the two totem beasts, one looked confident while the other was deathly pale. Evidently, the match was almost over.

There was a circle of black-armored guards around the platform, and some people in white clothes, surrounding Avic as he sat on another platform parallel to the tall platform, watching the battle on stage from a distance.

Avic was mostly surrounded by nobles in white fabulous clothes and royalty. But the ones closest to him were the princesses in white lace dresses.

The youngest princess was sitting on Avic's lap, he hugged her lightly as her eyes were trained completely on the battle on stage.

The others wore different colored clothes, each befitting nobility, and were obviously people from outside the royal family, just like Garen.

These people were rather young too, looking unexpectedly green.

"Announcing Viscount Trejons!"

A maidservant’s voice reported.

Most of the observing crowd suddenly turned around, looking at the direction Garen was walking in from.

Most of the royal family looked vaguely curious and wary. A few of the young men even had hidden envy in their eyes.

"Haha, it's Garen!" Avic stood up, taking the initiative to beckon Garen over. "Just nice, the Silver Palace ranking competition just began, do you wanna try too?"

"The Silver Palace has too many elite fighters, I'm afraid I'm not strong enough," Garen replied humbly. Led by the maids, he actually walked up to Avic's side and took a seat.

"You're being too modest." Avic patted Garen's shoulder, to show his friendliness. "It's good you came, watch these young participants’ abilities with me. It's perfect, you can be a judge, and give marks."

"Marks?"

There were four princes and six princesses in total around them, and although the First Princess wasn't here, the two royal daughters also very much in favor, the Second Princess and the Fourth Princess were also here. Just then, they heard that Garen was here as a scorer. Their expressions changed slightly.

To be able to become a scoring judge, one's abilities had to be at the forefront of the Silver Palace. At least in the top ten.

Garen's battle results were really impressive, but to say he could rank in the top ten of the entire Silver Palace was pushing it. After all, under Avic's encouragement, Silver Palace had included all of the Empire’s strongest totem users and could be said to be a peak level organization representing all of Kovistan's power. To be able to rank in the top ten there meant he would be top ten in Kovistan in name, in which case his influence would be huge.

Bam!!

Just then the winner had been decided on stage, the black bear actually grew a thick black tail with scales, like that of a crocodile, and swept it at the side of the tiger's body, beating it to a pulp and rendering it unable to retaliate.

The black bear's totem user was raising both hands up in the sky, bowing towards Avic in the distance.

"Newly promoted competitor, Count Leon wins!"

"Now we shall award the royal family’s most technologically advanced crystal -- the Silver Wings!" A male guard at the side announced loudly. There was also a maid carrying the tray with the award onto the platform.

Garen sat down next to Avic and immediately heard Avic ask him.

"Garen, what do you think of those two just now?"

He thought it over for a while.

"At their age, it's already not bad that they can achieve the elite level of Form Two. It's just I don't know which family has descendants with so much potential."

"Just the heir of a small family that recently entered the Kingdom. But since they have potential, they'll naturally be Kovistan's talent and assets. We will certainly raise them properly." Avic shook his head, "The next group!"

"Next group!!" The guard passed down his order.

Soon enough, two more young people, dressed differently, went onto the stage.

One was wearing a white wig, a woman. The other was wearing skintight black leather pants and a short black dagger for unknown purposes strapped on and was also a woman.

After they went onto the stage, they both bowed and paid their respects to each other. Then they released a white wild boar and a black bald eagle with reddish wings each.

The two of them faced off on the high platform.

Garen watched the battle with Avic, but he had no interest whatsoever in these Form Two totem users with ordinary elite totems.

Compared to Form One, Form Two totem users already had a special ability, but they weren't strong, with not much variety, not enough changes and naturally not much to see. Although some totem users made up for it with tactics, totem users who could use tactics were far too few.

Match after match went on, and after six whole matches, there was finally a young man who could use tactics.

But even then, Garen nearly fell asleep watching them.

"Don't worry, the next one up has some connection with you, Garen." Avic glanced at him, chuckling. As though having seen through his disinterest.

"Connection with me?" Garen said, confused.

"That's right, this little fella’s grandfather is Earl Baxy. Their Hildra family and your Trejons family have always been on good terms." Avic explained.

Garen suddenly remembered, this Earl Baxy was related to Vanderman, and was one of the Trejons family relatives in the Kingdom.

Back when he first arrived in the Kingdom, they had even sent an invitation, but he didn't have the time to join them.

His mind running carefully, Garen smiled slightly. Acacia’s mother was Earl Baxy’s daughter, meaning Earl Baxy was this body's maternal grandfather.

"According to our relations, he should call me his older cousin."

Avic laughed.

"His name is Reyn Hildra, he's the totem user candidate with the most promise in this generation of the Hildra family. As members of the same generation, you two should be closer."

"Of course." Garen smiled.

Soon enough, Reyn Hildra went onto the stage. This was a handsome man who also had blonde hair, no older than twenty years, and with rare purple eyes. His slender body wore a white warrior’s uniform, with just another silver-striped leather cloak draped over his right shoulder.

He first bowed at His Majesty, and then added a bow to Garen by himself.

And then he waved his right hand, a pure white owl appearing on his right shoulder. Strangely, this owl kept sparkling with blue lightning.

Garen smiled a little.

Looks like this young guy was abnormally friendly to him, and plus, he was the only one with a decent totem presence to come up to the stage since just now. Garen suddenly had a shard of recognition for him.

That Lightning Owl was evidently not a regular Form Two totem.

"Looks pretty decent," Garen said lightly.

"How about you judge this match?" Avic glanced at him.

"Can I?" Garen was surprised.

"Of course you can."

"That's against the rules, isn't it, Father?" The Fourth Princess said sweetly and softly from the side.

She quickly swept Garen with a glance, her eyes full of wariness.

Chapter 420: Trace 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This Fourth Princess had a rather voluptuous body and was a little beauty. Since she was able to sit next to Avic, that must mean her position was significant as well.

"It’s okay, with Garen’s ability, two lowly Form Two totem users won’t be any trouble," Avic replied nonchalantly.

"But one of the participants is His Excellency Garen’s relative, wouldn’t this be…" Another royal daughter spoke, it was the Second Princess.

This icy beauty wearing a white lace flower crown reminded calmly.

Garen glanced at the two royal daughters, the corners of his lips curving, but he didn’t say anything.

Avic frowned slightly.

"I heard that Your Excellency Garen is extremely capable, but to think you have been recognized by His Majesty as one of the top ten in the Silver Palace. Could we trouble Your Excellency to show us a glimpse of your prowess?" This came from a young man dressed in red, sitting among several nobles by the side.

"That’s Grand Duke Cody’s son, Barton." The little princess next to Garen, the Eleventh Royal Daughter, explained to Garen in a small voice.

She was no older than eleven, but her eyes were crafty and sly, her expression perfectly that of a pure loli, whereas her heart hid some considerable tricks.

"The Grand Duke’s son?" Garen’s gaze grew serious.

Just then, Avic did begin to understand what Barton was getting at.

"This is Barton, Grand Duke Cody’s fifth son. He’s the same age as you, Garen, the two of you should have a lot to talk about. What do you mean, Barton?"

"Wall of Glory." This young man in red said with a faint smile, "The Silver Palace’s Glory Wall is the best way to prove one’s power. Since Your Majesty believes His Excellency Garen has the ability to reach the top ten of the Silver Palace, then let us please have His Excellency show us, and allow us all to witness his greatness."

Avic was evidently very soft with this Barton, seemingly rather wary of Grand Duke Cody behind him as well.

"That’s true, as long as the Wall of Glory leaves behind a mark indicating the top ten, then we will naturally believe in His Excellency Garen’s abilities," the Second Princess added.

"Wall of Glory?" Garen was slightly confused.

The Eleventh Royal Daughter, the loli explained to him again. "The Wall of Glory is an heirloom the Silver Palace uses to measure someone’s ultimate destructive power. It can’t be destroyed, and only someone whose power is in the top hundred among the Silver Palace can even leave a mark on it. Different levels of power will leave marks of different depths."

"It’s something to measure one’s true power?" Garen understood.

"That’s right. All the strongest fighters in the country had been invited here by Father for a test, and there are still the marks from their tests on it. You absolutely can test your power relative to the whole kingdom there." The Eleventh Royal Daughter said with a smile.

"That’s good. I’ll go try it out."

Avic was a decisive person as well and immediately called a temporary stop to the competition.

"Good, then let’s all go to the Wall of Glory, to see just how strong the legendary Nine Headed Hydra is!"

Compared to a match between normal totem users, a move from a peak-level fighter like Garen was evidently more worth watching, so all the royal sons and daughters were instantly interested. Barton and the few others shone with even more anticipation.

The group immediately got up, and the competition participants rested temporarily.

Avic led everyone into another empty arena.

In the middle of the arena, there was a tall square wall like white jade, with marks and dents on it. More fighters than could be counted had left their own marks here.

This wall looked like a very ordinary tall wall, five meters tall and more than four meters wide, with some damage and marks on the sides. It was obviously an outer wall left from some destroyed building.

When Garen and the others arrived, some people were desperately attacking the wall.

Two of them twinkled with light, in a short-lived Spiritualization possession.

Seeing His Majesty approaching, these people immediately called back their totems and bowed at Avic politely.

"Welcome, Your Majesty!"

"Step down for now, I want to use the Wall of Glory." Avic waved at them.

"Yes."

They seemed to be officials in the palace, leaving rapidly without hesitation, giving up their space.

As everyone else watched, Garen went up and stood in front of the white Wall of Glory, examining the marks on it carefully.

Once he saw the marks, his heart gave a small jolt.

These marks were automatically arranged in a straight line from top to bottom. From deep to shallow, it was unexpectedly orderly.

"That there is the magic of the Wall of Glory, once you attack any part of the Wall and leave a mark, then that mark will be automatically moved into this line. From deep to shallow, naturally, the levels of strength can be easily distinguished." Avic explained loudly. "And this wall only records the top hundred strongest, if your attack can’t even reach number one hundred, it won’t be shown here."

"It is indeed magical." Garen nodded in appreciation.

"The three strongest fighters in the Empire have left their strongest marks here, now it’s your turn," Avic said with a smile. "Come, give out the name list!"

A servant immediately gave Garen a name list scroll.

He opened it up and saw that it recorded the information about the owners of these marks.

The first and deepest one was enough for someone to stick a thumb inside, and was left by the Empire’s Grand Duke Benoc. Benoc was Prynne’s grandfather, a terrifying reproductive machine that could create an entire family on his own… He had twenty sons, sixteen daughters, his sons’ kids, his daughters’ kids, and so on, creating a huge family clan. Among all the sons and grandsons, Prynne was part of the more favored group.

The second one was from the defense minister Veska, only a little shallower than Benoc’s.

The third was an unfamiliar name, Georbas Allen. Completely unheard of.

Next, the fourth belonged to the other Grand Duke, Cody.

The fifth one later was the Guard Captain Edin. After that were many nobles and earls, each more unfamiliar to Garen.

Garen didn’t look anymore, putting down the name list and returning it to the guard at the side.

"Can we start now?" Avic asked loudly.

"Of course." Garen smiled, and a gust of fast wind blew about him, puffing up the clothes of everyone around him.

"Retreat to a hundred meters away!" Avic said loudly and was the first to retreat together with some guards.

The princes and princesses all stood behind their personal guards, retreating to a hundred meters away.

The Grand Duke’s son, Cody, didn’t change his expression, and only retreated fifty meters away, two red-bearded old men protecting him on either side.

"Tell me, what position would this person’s power be on the wall?" Barton asked in a low voice.

"Should be above thirty, but no more than twenty-five," one old man said softly.

"If the two of you fought him, what are your chances?" Barton’s eyes sparkled, as he continued asking.

"The records say the Nine-Headed Hydra isn’t that strong and is placed number 137 among the ultimate totems. Even if this person is highly accomplished in close combat, it wouldn’t be too hard to defeat him. I alone would be enough." The old man with the longer beard said arrogantly.

Barton nodded slowly.

"In a fight between Form Four and Form Five fighters, totems practically won’t fight on their own anymore, it would mostly be a fight between totem users themselves. At that time totem users would have twice the defense of totems themselves and would have the same offensive power as the totems. He’s like us, his own physical body is extremely powerful. To have such power at this age, he’s already extremely formidable." The red-bearded old man explained.

Barton’s expression was slightly wistful.

"Too bad he chose the wrong totem, the Nine-Headed Hydra’s potential isn’t enough, he’s already reached the limit at this point."

"That might be even better, the Secret Service has always been rather at odds with us from the Geometry Service. Seeing as he’s already reached this level at this age, if he didn’t choose the wrong core totem, his advancement from here on out would be too terrifying. By the time he changes a core, who knows how many years would have passed."

Barton nodded and didn’t say any more.

Just then, the surrounding servants and maids had long since hidden themselves away in a further place, terrified of being caught in the blast.

Garen stood in front of the tall wall, after taking a look around him, he saw that everyone had backed away.

He smiled slightly. The three dots on his forehead shone with a bloody glow.

The air around him began to ripple and form translucent red salamander heads. There were nine gruesome heads in total, constantly twisting and roaring.

Phew!

A huge breath of air expanded across all directions explosively. Like a blast of wind, blowing everyone around it into taking a few steps back.

The two old men in front of Barton raised one hand each, creating a pale blue circular membrane that blocked the raging wind like a glass wall.

The clothes of everyone around him fluttered loudly in the wind. Although Barton had seen many Form Four fighters make their move before, but such a young face together with such overwhelming power was still enough to make him feel strands of envy and jealousy.

Just then.

In the middle of the arena, Garen raised his right hand, and the nine pale salamander heads became nine blood-red shadows, twisting over his arm.

Bzz…

Garen’s body slowly emitted a soft sound like a tremor. A thick, blood-like aura slowly flowed down his legs, spreading in all directions.

Barton didn’t notice anything, because he couldn’t see this blood-like aura, but the other two old men’s expressions changed drastically. Each one of them held up a hand, grabbing him and rapidly pulling him back fifty meters.

Barton’s face was full of confusion, and he was about to ask. For some reason, he was having difficulty breathing, and couldn’t open his mouth to speak.

"To think… to think!!" The old man with the long beard was filled with shock, staring hard at Garen in the arena, "His own body’s power has actually reached such a level…"

"Big brother?" The other old man spoke, his expression similarly shocked and fearful. "Could he really be that sort of person?"

The old man with the long beard nodded his head slowly.

"Young Master Barton, from now on you must never incite that Garen. Avoid any frontal conflicts with him whenever possible."

"Why?"

"This man has a heart so cruel it has reached an extreme. As a totem user, he still went to study the martial arts and physical fighting skills that even normal people find excruciatingly painful, and he even trained these martial skills to such a terrifying level, such a person’s will has already reached an incomprehensible level!"

"No wonder he could escape from the clutches of God Cloud’s clones." The other one looked as though he finally understood everything. "I saw a totem user like that before, he has extremely powerful martial arts, and after reaching a high level as a totem user, he merged his martial arts and totem together, achieving an extremely powerful level. His endurance is almost limitless and was extremely aware of the battle situation. If someone of the same level wanted to kill someone like this, it was practically mission impossible."

Barton’s expression was unnaturally heavy, this was his first time hearing the two old men next to him use such a serious tone.

"Someone like this already has such powerful survival power, added together with the Nine-Headed Hydra’s survival power…" The old man’s tone got more and more wary.

Just then, a cloud of black-red mist rose in the arena. Enveloping Garen inside.

Roar!!

The gruesome Nine Headed Salamander moved vaguely in the mist.

Finally, the countless black-red mists gathered quickly, solidifying in Garen’s palm.

He smiled, and reached out his right hand lightly, pressing on the face of the wall.

The power of the Nine-Headed Hydra totem was the strongest destructive force, as for the rest of its power they were only about support and recovery. The strongest part of the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon was its terrifying physical power.

So the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon’s power was stacked together with Garen’s own power and added on to the ring Troll Grip’s power. This was Garen’s strongest attack.

And now, Garen used at least half of its power.

The pure and terrifying power crashed into the Wall of Glory mercilessly.

Crack!!

Without any premonition, the ground under Garen’s feet collapsed. Forming a huge semi-circular dent, countless stone shards and dust formed a whirlwind flying everywhere. The place where the palm and the wall met, however, didn’t make too much noise. It was just one soft sound.

Smack.

After the Nine-Headed Dragon evolved, Garen’s actual strongest ability, was actually pure strength!

Be it Life Tear or Poison Mist Corrosion, neither was nearly as terrifying as his own pure strength. It was only half of his power.

Even he was quite excited to know, where his own true power lay among the many elite fighters of the Kingdom.

Pulling back his palm, Garen looked at the wall with a hint of anticipation.

Chapter 421: Postpone 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The collapsed palm print slowly recovered, and the wall returned to being smooth and clean.

And in the row of marks beside, there was a new and clear mark.

The mark appeared in the ninth position from the top, pushing the one who was originally ninth down one spot.

"Ninth?" Only then did Garen’s eyes reveal a hint of surprise.

He reached out his hand and touched the ninth mark, his own, lightly. In terms of depth it wasn’t that far away from number eight, but further up, compared to the seventh, the difference was a lot bigger.

But having hidden half of his power, he believed he could do it.

Touching the fifth one and comparing further, Garen’s heart began to sink.

This person had evidently not used their full power either, but the mark left behind was far deeper than what he would expect his full power to create.

This meant that the other person’s full destructive force was a great chunk stronger than his. Starting from number five, the four above him were far, far stronger in destructive power. Although the Nine-Headed Dragon’s specialty wasn’t destructive power, this result was still way beyond Garen’s expectations.

This meant that in Kovistan, there were at least five people with more destructive power than him!

"The Royal Guard Captain, Edin?" He read out the fifth name.

"That’s right, Edin is the palace master of this Silver Palace." At some point, Avic had arrived behind Garen. "Garen, the fact that you have reached number nine is already way beyond my expectations. To be able to reach such heights at such a young age, impressive."

"You exaggerate, Your Majesty." Garen smiled slightly, took two steps back, and falling behind Avic. No matter what he was a famous part of the loyalist faction, so he had to watch these basic manners.

"Like you, Edin is also my strongest helper. You two are like my left and right hands, whereas Veska is my back. With you, the Empire can truly be stable and safe," Avic said pointedly.

Garen paused a bit, not because of Avic’s attempt at familiarisation, but because his words never mentioned the First Concubine Delouse. That surprised him.

Delouse was extremely capable and prevented the Empire from incurring extreme losses. She had always been known as Avic’s arms. At this time, however, she was ignored completely.

He understood what Avic meant by that, if he was smart enough this time, then from now on his position would be the same Edin, having been promoted to his right or left hand.

A thousand thoughts ran through his mind, and Garen didn’t hesitate in the slightest, immediately bowing to Avic.

"It is the honor and mission of the Trejons family to serve Your Majesty. From the beginning to the end, my father and I are loyal to the Empire." Garen lowered his head and replied.

As soon as he mentioned his father Vanderman, Avic couldn’t help but sigh.

"All of you from the Trejons family, well done!"

The royal sons and daughters who had come with them heard that sentence, their eyes sparkling.

"Oh yeah, I forgot to mention. Your Earldom certificate has already been spread around the whole Empire. From this day forward, the Trejons family territory has an extra piece of plains. And you, are a new Earl of our Kovistan Empire." Avic patted Garen’s shoulder.

"Thank you, Your Majesty!" Garen felt a surge of joy, and bowed again immediately.

Avic took out a purple-gold badge, smiling, and put it in Garen’s hand. "This is the palace’s Purple-Gold Badge, it can control the palace’s elite Black Fire Guard, the elite group in charge of the entire palace’s safety. Unlike the royal guard, they are a powerful team fully comprised of elite totem users! There aren’t many of them, and the structure is simple, but they are powerful. I want to give them to someone worth depending on. Your Excellency Garen, are you willing to accept this burden?!"

With those last words, his voice grew louder.

"I am willing!!" Garen replied loudly.

"Good! My safety, the safety of the entire royal family, they are now all on you." Avic hugged Garen heavily.

Nearby, the Eleventh Royal Daughter was biting her lip tightly.

"I was right, this is gonna be troublesome… Avic gave the Black Fire Guard to the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon. The Royal Guard has Edin. This is especially troubling…"

"Tina!" Avic’s voice came from ahead.

The Eleventh Royal Daughter have a shudder, and immediately reacted.

"Here! Father?" She went up hurriedly, bent her knees and curtsied. "Is there anything you want from me?"

"Didn’t you want to go out and play? From now on you can ask Your Excellency Garen for arrangements whenever you want to go out. The palace hall I arranged for him is not far from yours." Avic smiled, looking at the young one.

"Daisy, Andy. Come over here and meet the new Black Fire Palace Master." Avic called a few more important royal sons and daughters over.

Daisy was the ice-cold Second Princess. Andy was a young prince whose face was growing pale.

The Eleventh Royal Daughter Tina lowered her head. She could feel Avic’s disgusting gaze wandering over her body like a cold snake. She knew this was the sign that Avic had fallen for her. After raising her for so many years, this bestial Emperor with a human face finally couldn’t hold it in.

Her heart went a little cold, normally she was the most neglected one, but now Avic called her first. And recently the benefits her palace hall received increased drastically, more and more people coming to honor her.

She was only eleven, but Tina understood that all this meant clearly that Avic was going to visit her at night.

At first, she thought Edin had something on and would leave, so she would have a temporary chance of escape. But now there was another Garen.

She had long since heard about Garen’s reputation, or rather the Trejons family’s reputation. Garen’s father Vanderman was a loyalist through and through, and though his reputation was in tatters, no one dared to touch him on that fact alone.

His son Garen was even more exaggeratedly evil, legends say that the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon must eat ten virgins and twenty children every day. When he was frustrated, even the elderly couldn’t escape. Wherever he went, blood would flow like rivers. His favorite hobby was collecting human hearts, and last time the Kingdom prison would send him about a hundred prisoners every month, just so he could choose fresh new hearts.

Just thinking about all these rumors, the Eleventh Royal Daughter Tina’s heart began to pound. "If only Stone and the others were here..."

It wasn’t the first time she thought that, that weak and defenseless need to find someone to rely on kept surging from her heart.

When he heard the name Tina, Garen’s body gave a jolt.

He looked closely at the royal daughters and found the Eleventh Royal Daughter Tina.

It was the little one with the cunning eyes who had explained to him. She looked sweet and cute, her body was soft and petite, the young girl’s thin waist wrapped in a white lace dress. Her slender legs wore white silk socks, the black ponytail behind her head had a silver butterfly ornament stuck in it.

Tina’s skin was fair but rosy, and somehow utterly flawless, making her look like a petite snow doll.

Garen glanced at Avic. As expected, this demon father’s eyes had a glimmer of bestial desire.

But for some reason, Avic seemed to be trying his best to hold back this desire. His gaze stopped on Tina briefly, and then quickly moved away. After a blink, it was replaced with a strange determination, as though he had just made some huge decision.

"From now on, Earl Garen, the new Black Fire Palace Master, and the Trejons family will contribute greatly to our Kovistan, you must refer to him as a senior! Do you understand?" Avic said such a surprising thing.

Not just Garen, even Barton and the royal sons and daughters nearby, all looked surprised.

"Alright, I’m tired, I’ll return to the palace now and rest. Come!"

"Here!" A guard jogged over, replying loudly.

"Take the Earl to the Black Fire Palace! Introduce him to his new subordinates!" Avic patted Garen’s shoulder without allowing for any protest, arranged the matters from now on, and left first of his own accord.

"Safe travel, Your Majesty (Father)!" Everyone bowed at the same time, and sent Avic off with their gazes.

Garen straightened up and glanced at everyone, his gaze staying on the Eleventh Royal Daughter Tina’s body for a few more seconds.

"Tina… Tina…" He suddenly remembered the original path of history, the few people who appeared behind Beckstone. One of the girls looked a lot like the Tina he was seeing.

Coincidentally, that girl also had a graceful body language and an elegant aura, her every move emitting the feeling of royalty that normal nobility couldn’t accomplish.

Judging from what he saw now, this Tina…

But now Beckstone and company should still be at the Marquess Black Snake’s place, so they wouldn’t arrive that quickly. Even if she really was that girl, she probably still didn’t know Beckstone at all now, right?

Garen thought about it a bit and then relaxed.

Barton followed behind closely and just smiled at Garen, without saying anything more, before leaving.

The other royal sons and daughters looked at each other. The Twelfth Royal Daughter was adorable at only seven or eight years old, her long white-golden hair combed neatly, and she wore a black silk dress with little leather boots, walking in front of Garen first.

"Uncle Garen, Ivy’s going ahead first."

After the first one, there was the second, the third. Each of the royal sons and daughters began to ask for leave from Garen.

Tina glanced at the Fourth Princess, who was biting down on her lower lip, her face turning green. When Avic left without taking her along, everyone knew clearly that Avic was already bored of playing with her. The fact that he changed his attitude so quickly probably had something to do with the Fourth Princess’ bad attitude towards Garen just now.

Suddenly all the royal sons and daughters made a decision in their hearts.

Tina was the last to go up to Garen.

"Uncle Garen, please take care of me from now on. My Eleventh Princess Hall is just next to your Black Fire Palace."

She tried her best to act obedient and pure, giving him a saccharine smile.

"You’re too kind, Your Highness, Garen will do everything in my power to ensure your safety." Garen smiled, his handsome features and beautiful golden hair making even Tina’s eyes spin a little.

But put together with the rumors she had heard, she instantly gave a shudder, afraid to look anymore as she lowered her head.

Finally, the Fourth Princess walked over, her face pale, as she bowed at Garen.

"Uncle Garen…"

By then, Tina had already walked away. She turned around and looked at the Fourth Princess, her previously arrogant Fourth Sister now had tears pooling in her eyes, threatening to fall at any moment.

She was saying something to Garen quietly, but it was rather far away, so she couldn’t hear it properly.

Chapter 422: Postpone 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Two days later. Avic actually announced that the ceremony and royal audience were to be delayed.

On the way back to her palace, Tina saw many servants and maids whispering to each other.

She had just come back from the bath and had returned to the main door of her palace hall, but she saw her personal attendant Bottler chatting quietly with a maid in a white dress. The two of them were so focused that they hadn’t noticed Tina coming at all.

"Bottler!"

Bottler gave a shudder and quickly ran towards Tina. The other maid ran away hurriedly as though escaping.

"What were you guys gossipping about!?" Tina’s little face was actually rather stern.

"Your Highness, Princess… No… nothing…" Bottler was so scared her face turned white, and she couldn’t speak clearly.

Tina harrumphed and put her little hands behind her back as she walked into her own palace hall.

The truth was, she did know what these people were talking about.

Thanks to the recent installation of Garen as the new Black Fire Palace Master, the palace defenses were undergoing a huge makeover, and the places once protected by the Royal Guard were mostly protected by the Black Fire Guard now. These Guards were almost like emotionless beasts, they never spoke, or chatted. They only knew how to be loyal and dutiful, listening to nobody’s orders except the Black Fire Palace Master Garen and His Majesty.

And recently there had been some rumors in the palace, saying that the Third Princess’ disappearance had something to do with the newly appointed Earl Garen.

Tina didn’t comment on any of these rumors. But deep inside, she knew perfectly well that her Third Sister’s death was closely related to Garen. She had overheard her Second Sister and First Sister arguing, partly over the investigation results on Earl Garen. The Third Princess did indeed die in the Earl’s mansion.

But more terrifying was the way their father and king, Avic, reacted to the death of the then-beloved Third Princess. When he found out the results, he didn’t make any move at all. He didn’t punish Garen in the slightest, making as though nothing happened, until it all slowly died down.

It was starting from that day, that Tina slowly began to mature, and discovered that Father’s gaze on her grew more and more unnerving.

Staying deep within this heavily-guarded palace, she felt like a canary in a golden cage, who could do nothing and dared to do nothing.

Tina walked into her bedroom, closed the door, and walked up to the window, about to draw the curtains, when she suddenly heard talking from below. She froze instantly.

"...The Second Palace’s Guard Captain, Caesure was sentenced to death…"

"Wasn’t Guard Captain Caesure’s the Second Princess’ most trusted guard captain?"

"Who asked the Captain to offend the Earl? In front of His Majesty…" The voice faded.

But Tina knew that everyone in the palace was always plotting something, these words weren’t something she happened to overhear, but rather the people in her palace were purposely letting her hear them.

They were afraid, scared of the newly appointed Earl Garen. They were afraid she carelessly offended the new Earl, they thought she didn’t understand… but in truth, she understood everything.

This new Palace Master was cruel and ruthless, respectful to the royal sons and daughters on the surface, but unbelievably heartless when he actually made his move. The Guard Captain Caesure and the Second Princess were as close as sisters, and she was still killed with one blow this morning.

Tina’s heart felt waves of cold, this was the premonition of danger approaching. Of the royal bloodline, she and Twelve had the strongest prophetic power, and now, this prophetic power was beginning to warn her, but she couldn’t do anything. She knew that danger was approaching, but she couldn’t avoid it.

Just two days after his promotion, Earl Garen was already organizing a massive clean-up.

With Avic’s full support, the Black Fire Palace’s special guards spread out like a spider web, scattering to every part of the palace, every royal son and daughter had someone from the Black Fire in their palaces, watching them.

With Avic’s palace in the center, all the Black Fire Guards formed an indomitable sealing web.

Tina realized with a shock that some blind spots that strong totem users usually didn’t notice, the ones that she had often used to go outside, were now patched up by the Black Fire Guards, the whole palace becoming more and more like an airtight metal barrel, squeezing all the breath out of her.

Beckstone and the others should be coming over soon, but under these circumstances, there wasn’t only the Garland Sword, Edin, but now there was also the Nine-Headed Dragon Garen.

Tina clenched her teeth.

"I need to think of something!"

**************

The assassination wasn’t brought forward as Garen guessed, but the Aegis Ceremony seemed to have been delayed.

Avic planned to meet the Black Prince himself, splitting up the original plan, the ceremony, and the audience, into two parts.

After becoming the Black Fire Palace Master, Garen hinted to Avic several times that something might go wrong with the Aegis Ceremony. But he didn’t clearly state it was Delouse, he just indicated that he noticed some outside powers might interfere with the Aegis Ceremony.

Avic had always been a suspicious person, and after receiving Garen’s hints, added together with his unusual trust in Garen, Garen was given unspoken permission to organize a large-scale clean-up of the inner palace.

Not hoping to do good, but at least do no wrong. With that kind of attitude, the palace security grew more and more stringent.

Under Garen’s guard, Avic was accompanied by Edin to a secret meeting with the Black Prince five days later, and they achieved a series of understandings.

After the meeting, the Black Prince left the Kingdom quickly.

Although Garen didn’t get to see this one of the three heroes, his interference had undoubtedly changed the original route of history.

The Black Prince no longer bore the sin of assassinating the king, and half of Obscuro’s plans fell apart.

**************

One week later

The king’s study

Avic was sitting opposite Garen and Edin.

The three of them were playing a three-player game called Nala, it was a bit like checkers, the aim being to reach a fixed target point first. In the process, however, the pieces could capture each other. Certain criteria had to be fulfilled for capture, though. Just like how chess pieces had differences in level and position.

Avic was wearing white casual clothes, his expression carefree, smiling as he took the lead.

Garen and Edin, on the other hand, were wearing black coats, only the colors of their hems different, one dark red and the other silver.

Both of them were also playing the game breezily.

Of the three, Avic was far ahead, Garen was second, and Edin third.

Even though he was last, Edin didn’t lose his calm at all, his movements still slow and steady. Compared to the Empire’s genius in his thirties, Garen’s personality was a lot more normal.

The pale white morning sunlight shone in from behind Avic’s back, falling on the edge of the white game board, reflecting the faint white light.

The three of them played with full concentration.

Smack.

Garen put down one of his pieces lightly and glanced at Avic. Now, he truly did respect this Emperor.

As a normal person, he managed to force down both of their playing powers. With a mind like that, no wonder he was the ruler of such a big country as Kovistan.

And after taking over the Black Fire Palace, the more Garen knew, the more he felt that Avic wasn’t as clueless to the danger as he acted. He seemed to be playing a much larger game.

There were many things that even a peak-level totem user like him couldn’t see clearly.

In Nala Chess, neither Garen nor Edin held back. Forget holding back, if they relaxed even a little, their important pieces would be immediately swallowed by Avic.

"Garen, how are you handling things over at the Black Fire Palace? No big problems?" Avic asked calmly as he played.

Garen smiled.

"Since you have given the Black Fire Guard as it is now to me, sire, that is your trust in me. Your trust in my Trejons family. So, even if there are problems, they’re not problems."

The true identity of the Black Fire Guard were actually the results of Vanderman’s research, the Green Vine Spheres.

Under the orders of outsiders, these Guards would only be able to use half of their true power. But under Garen’s orders, the Green Vine Spheres were originally personal Aberrated Totems Vanderman had made specifically for Garen. Or rather they were no longer totems, but a scientific experimental result.

In that case, the Black Fire Guard, the living experiments created through parasitic cores, would naturally be a power only Garen could truly understand.

Add that to the Trejons family’s reputation as famous loyalists, and Avic was finally able to fully let go, handing the Black Fire Guard to Garen. Back when the Black Fire Guard was created, and he realized the specialty of the Green Vine Spheres, Avic had already planned to do this.

The invention of the Black Fire Guard was a brand new power in the Empire’s arsenal, there were no more than two hundred of them, but they were all members of the living dead, having undergone countless surgeries and in possession of elite Form Two power. They had no emotion and were only loyal to the owner of the Green Vine Sphere, Garen.

Before the Research and Development Department discovered a way to remove this loyalty limitation, the only one who could take charge of the Black Fire Palace was Garen, this was the conclusion Avic came up with after many attempts.

"Garen, your father Vanderman died for the royal family, and I’ve always felt guilty about that. But if he saw you now, an integral part of the country, I bet he would be proud of you too. So if anything happens in the palace, you can act with abandon." Avic said calmly, "No matter what, I believe that we will always be on the same side."

Garen’s face twitched.

Of course they were on the same side, the Trejons family had a grudge against the Obscuro Society, and an even bigger one with Terraflor. The only power they could rely on was the royal family.

He glanced at Edin beside him.

Edin, Veska, and those two Grand Dukes, were the only four people he had to be wary of in the Kingdom. Of course, this didn’t include that old monster who could be hiding deep in the palace.

According to Garen’s guesses, these four were all stronger than him, and should have important positions in the three departments. Or perhaps they were already the main people at the very top of the three departments.

"I heard Lord Veska has returned to the Geometry Department, in order to temporarily handle some matters," Edin spoke suddenly and randomly.

"That’s right, after waiting for so long, it’s perhaps time for them to make a move." Avic nodded, and said ambiguously. "After waiting so long, drawing it out even longer will cost them all their efforts."

Garen narrowed his eyes slightly.

"So it seems Your Majesty was long since prepared."

"I didn’t want it to be like this either…" Avic sighed. "But no one could have guessed that the one who betrayed me would be the person I trusted the most."

Garen’s heart gave a jolt, so he did know.

"Your Majesty, what you’re saying is?"

"When the time comes, the safety of the palace is fully in your hands." Avic didn’t say any more, but was evidently ready to make a move. His expression seemed to have a hint of weariness and melancholy. It was obvious that he still found it hard to make a move against the person who had been with him for so many years.

Garen’s thoughts ran a mile a minute.

If Avic knew from the start, how could the assassination have succeeded?

Suddenly, he had an intense interest in Delouse from Obscuro. Unfortunately, Delouse still hadn’t met him after so long.

All of a sudden, he thought of the Eleventh Royal Daughter Tina, as well as Beckstone and company. Maybe, this had something to do with them as well?

Chapter 423: Gang Up 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was escorted by four Black Fire Guards away from the Royal Library, towards Black Fire Palace.

It was completely dark in the Black Fire Palace; dark red patterns permeated the dark hall.

From a bird’s eye view, the room looked like a right-angled triangle, surrounded by round, dark red pillars, and on those pillars were inscriptions of different large black symbols with unknown meaning.

Opposite the Black Fire Palace was the Eleventh Palace of the Eleven Princesses. Twin statues stood towering against each other.

Garen left the administrative area, past the public area, and walked up towards the little stone bridge at the Black Fire Palace. Four Black Fire guards followed him from behind, all in heavy battle hoods which gave off a cold, stern air.

The guards and maids along the way all gave their respects to Garen.

To enter the Black Fire Palace proper, he had to pass through the Eleventh Palace first.

It was just dawn then, a maid in a red shirt was escorting a young man towards the Eleventh Palace in the open corridor out in front.

The man looked calm but had a hint of anxiety in his eyes. He looked handsome, but due to the contrast between his expression and his eyes, he gave off an odd feeling of disharmony.

As Garen walked past the corridor, he suddenly glanced at the maid escorting the male from afar.

That maid also bowed out of respect in the distance, even the man she escorted had to bow.

"Who is that person?" Garen stopped and asked one of the guards.

"Sir, that man is a guest that the Eleventh Princess wishes to see, he is a commoner from outside the palace." This male guard was surprised by the sudden question and hurriedly answered.

"A man meeting the Her Eleventh Majesty?" Garen frowned, and thought about his previous guess. "Have him leave the area."

"But… that man is someone Eleventh Her Majesty insisted on meeting personally…" The guard felt troubled, he was a close guard of the Eleventh Palace, and judging from the intonation of Her Majesty when she gave the order, he reckoned that he was someone important.

"Has he made many trips here?" Garen suddenly asked further.

"Yes…." The guard nodded heavy heartedly.

"In the future, do not let this person in without my orders." Garen barked, then strode away.

The four Black Fire Guards stomped away in their heavy armor, leaving a pressuring aura in their wake.

********************************

Pap!

Clang!!

Eleventh Princess Tina vehemently smashed a vase onto the ground.

"Die!"

"Die die die!!"

Tina locked herself inside the reading room, smashing everything she could inside the soundproof area.

"I’m so furious! Damn that Garen! Damn that Black Fire Palace!! How does it concern you who I wish to meet?!"

Shards of crystal porcelain were scattered everywhere on the floor, leaving the entire room in a mess.

She didn’t dare cause a ruckus outside. The Black Fire Heavy Guards were stationed outside the Palace, under orders from the Black Fire Palace to not allow anyone out without permission, and that if need be, to request so from Garen himself.

This made Tina angry to the brink of losing control. She wasn’t able to see Beckstone, whom she wanted to meet, now she was even placed under house arrest in her own palace.

However, she could not complain. In His Majesty Avic’s eyes, the Ten Princesses were not comparable to his left and right arm, let alone Garen, the expert of the kingdom, a top totem user. Don’t even mention house arrests, if Garen wanted her, Avic may not even voice a second opinion, and arrange a marriage.

After lashing out, Tina finally calmed down.

"Now what? I can’t even get out of the palace, they can’t come in…I would need to look into other avenues if I were to escape from here."

In a short few weeks, the Nine-Headed Demon Dragon Garen’s reputation had spread all across the kingdom. He was also regarded as one of the two strongest Generals under Avic, alongside the Garland Swordsman Edin.

Of course, to outsiders’ eyes, to the enemies’ eyes, the two of them were Avic’s most loyal eaglehounds. Or perhaps their status was much higher than that of an eaglehound, but functionally, they were eaglehounds without question.

Although Edin was a genius with strong capabilities, he paid no heed towards macromanagement, and neither was he an expert on it. Garen was different, holding tightly to the status and power. His Black Fire guards were mysterious, each of them exceedingly strong, and their identical Black Fire Wolves were all ferocious. Adding onto the strong equipment produced by the Royal Alliance, each Black Fire Heavy Guard was able to take on two totem users of the same level.

No matter who it was, if they want to take out Avic, They must first go through Edin and Garen, his two defenses.

**************************

Another week later.

Within the Black Fire Palace.

Garen walked into the left hall of the Grand Hall, walking in front of a small room.

The small black door was wide open, inside was a youngster with a black ponytail sitting down.

As Garen walked in, the youngster stood up, his face a reflection of joy.

"Garen, are you done with today’s matters?"

"Haven’t you gone to your grandfather’s place?" Garen walked over and sat opposite the youngster.

A small table was placed in between the two men, and on the tabletop were two cups of steaming hot red tea.

The room was filled with the thin fragrance of the red tea.

This youngster was Prynne, whom he had not seen in a long time.

This was the person who grew up with Acacia and only contacted Garen a few days ago. Garen had visited Prynne’s Grandfather, Benoc, but of course, his main objective was to meet Prynne.

This guy wasn’t just living a regular fulfilling life, even though he wasn’t a totem user, he had a grandfather who adored him, so the family would naturally take good care of him. Adding onto Garen’s visit was a show of power.

His status within the family was only growing in a linear fashion. Although he wasn’t considered a heir to the family, he at least had some influence.

"My grandfather went off to a hunting patrol. The weather these days is pretty good, with many continuous sunny days. A thought came to Grandfather, and off he rode." Prynne shook his head "Unfortunately, I am not a totem user, otherwise, I would be able to experience the outside world for myself.

"Looking for me this early in the morning, do you have something urgent for me?" Garen picked up the glass of tea and took a sip.

"Actually, no, I was just planning to marry Marin." Prynne laughed. This brat was much more matured as compared to before.

"Then, what about Andel?" Garen had an expression as though he expected that, that he was not surprised at all.

"Andel’s family is a tad bit troublesome. Most of her family members passed away during the assault by the monsters. Only her aunt and her are left in the entire household. In the past few times I invited her out to spend some time, she felt more and more depressed." Prynne frowned as he spoke.

The four of them had played with each other since they were young, their relationship with each other was the most tightly knit, but due to the turmoil in these times, each person’s lives had their drastic ups and downs.

If Garen hadn’t stood up for himself, perhaps his family would have been exterminated. Even if they had somehow survived, it would probably be quite similar to Andel’s situation.

Even though Prynne’s household was domineering, with his power and influence currently, it was already a stretch on his limits escort his own good friends around.

"Try to help her as best you can, I guess." Garen sighed.

"Which is why I’m making this trip now." Prynne nodded. "Andel planned to look for something to do in the palace so that she can be independent and not add more burdens on her aunt. Do you reckon you can get her something to do?"

"Entering the palace?" Garen frowned. "It's not that I am unwilling; these kind of things can be settled with a single word of mine. But as close friends, I really hope that she doesn’t enter the palace right now."

Prynne stopped for a moment, showing a quizzical, thinking expression.

Garen continued speaking. "Give me some time, I’ll let her know. The Royal Palace’s Administrative department shouldn’t have any issues."

"How long would it take? You should know, if it were just a regular position, I wouldn’t have even bothered looking for you. I could have settled it myself." Prynne raised his eyebrows.

"Of course it wouldn’t just be some regular position!" Garen laughed.

"She said that it’s best if she can enter the palace as soon as possible. Since she doesn’t do anything at home." Prynne shook his head, "Her household’s situation is not looking very well at the moment. Even if we were hosting her.. Without her own, solid foundation… You know, most of the things are still conflict come from within the household, we’re just mere spectators at this point."

Garen suddenly understood what he meant.

The issue with Nadel must be because of her own family’s passings, causing distant relatives to come to divide the inheritance. According to the law, doing this was the right way to go, but no matter how it was done, there would still be large loopholes for people to play tricks. She urgently needs a nice paying position to earn some power and influence in order to fend off the greedy vultures of the distant relatives.

"I can understand her problems, which is why I still feel that it’s best to arrange her entrance into the palace as soon as possible," Prynne said faintly. He took up the red tea and placed it on his lips, but he wasn’t really drinking it, instead just blowing it gently.

"So what’s the position she wants?" Garen let out a deep sigh, he had to say it out in the end, he understood that Andel was now embarrassed to meet her old friends; only Marin still had a close relationship with her. Since she was pushed to this point, adding to the fact that Prynne was out to proactively voice for her, the issue must have gotten to a troublesome point. Otherwise, she wouldn’t go through so many channels to reach out to him.

"As I understand, she hopes to find a position suitable for a lady," Prynne answered.

Garen nodded slowly.

"A job that suits the ladies.. The only ones left with such openings are the Royal Palace’s Treasury, the Gardening Department, and the Princess's’ Palace. Seeing that it’s my friend coming in, the position must not be low, naturally."

He thought for a while, "I’ll give her three positions; Assistant Supervisor of the Treasury, Botanical Head of Gardening, and Female Supervisor of the Princess’ Palace. These three positions can be decided by me, so go check out which one she’d like."

"Alright, then I shall let her know." Prynne swiftly stood up. He understood that Garen had actually done him a huge favor by giving Andel three options. After all, he was not the only one minding the matters in the Palace, there was still the White Silver Palace, the Princess, and His Majesty. It was also impossible for him to obtain higher positions.

"Rushing off so quickly? Don’t you want to stay a little while longer?" Garen smiled.

"I don’t think so, Marin and Andel are both waiting to hear from me."

"If there’s anything in the future, why not let them look for me directly? We’re all such close friends, why the formalities?" Garen frowned.

"It’s all because your status is different from before, previously Marin planned to bring Andel over to look for you, even if it was just a peek from afar. They definitely wouldn’t dare start anything funny like hitting on you, they would’ve been frightened to death." Prynne spoke without restraint. "With your usual vibe, that look of ‘whoever messes with me, dies’ look, who would dare greet you casually?"e

"That can't be right. Do I look that scary?" Garen touched his chin with confusion.

"The head of Black Fire Palace, the one who would bring around 4 black-robed elites around, who dons two-meter tall heavy armor, and kills people with just a smile." Prynne was speechless, "Are you aware of the rumors about you?"

"What rumors?"

"It’s said that you eat 10 virgins daily, your favourite collections are of the hearts of strong people, that you can kill someone with just a glance sideways when you were unhappy, that you have arms as thick as a man’s waist, thighs so huge a man can’t hug it all the way round, a bite that can pierce steel…."

"Stop stop stop!!" As he watched Prynne’s words get more far-fetched, Garen was shocked enough to immediately stop him from going further. "Who’s spreading these rumours?"

Prynne shook his head

"I don’t know, but it is what it is. Some things about you...to be honest, are really…." He saw Garen’s expression and didn’t continue speaking.

"All I did was kill a couple people, and the rumors are already starting to fly." Garen’s eyes squinted.

Prynne was speechless.

Just killed a couple people? The Fourth Princess was unaware of the current during a Black Fire Guards’ patrol and got into a conflict with Garen and a close guard of hers. She then used her identity to suppress Garen, saying that he is just the Royal Family’s dog, a henchman.

The result was that the Black Fire Guard killed off everyone in the Princess Palace, aside from Fourth Princess herself. Exactly 96 people were all killed in a single night. The entire Fourth Palace lacked even a maid serving tea.

Even so, Avic insisted that Fourth Princess publicly apologize to Garen.

Not only this, in the recent sweep, of whoever harbored any suspicion from the Black Fire Guards, almost none were left alive

In the name of rooting out spies, the Black Fire guards have swept through the entire palace once, and whoever had a differing opinion was executed by Garen. The kill count from the purge reached over 300 people.

In the eyes of a usually peaceful country, Garen had undoubtedly become the murderer! The hangman!

Chapter 424: Gang Up 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

With the absence of Defence minister Veska, plus the fact the Royal Guard Captain Edin was not leaving the White Silver Palace, and that the First Concubine was busy with the preparations of the ceremony, Avic had completely left all authority in the palace to Garen. The entire palace was almost entirely governed by him.

In actual fact, this was all just Garen following the historic scenarios that he had seen, ridding all the Obscuro spies of the entire palace. The majority of those being purged are all eyes and ears for the First Concubine.

The only thing was that his excuses weren’t sufficient; he was also lazy to think of more solid justifications, so he simply thought up a few placeholders and killed the entire bunch of people. Which was what led to his bad reputation. But it didn’t matter, the Trejons’ family reputation was already rotten ever since Vanderman’s human experimentation was exposed; the household’s reputation had been thrown out the window. Garen couldn’t bother with those menial ethics either.

So long as Avic’s heirloom is fine, none of this would be a problem. The guards and maids in the palace could always be replaced. In such a crucial time, Garen couldn’t afford to be soft, he must remove all of the First Concubine’s spies.

He wouldn’t have known if he hadn’t uncovered the fact that First Concubine’s subordinates were all over the palace. He then ruthlessly killed off all of the spies of Obscuro.

Now that Prynne had mentioned it, the outsiders actually described him to be even more terrorizing than a demon, Garen didn’t know if he should be laughing or crying.

"Wouldn’t you guys know what kind of person I am? You actually distrusted me this much, you really make me sad."

Prynne said with a worried tone.

"Actually my grandfather said that too, you are now standing on a cusp, there would be some trouble when Veska returns, you’d better make some earlier arrangements."

"I understand." Garen nodded.

"Alright, I shall make a move, the girls are still waiting for my news. When you have the time, let’s hang out with the rest, it’s been awhile since we got together." Prynne tapped Garen’s shoulder.

"Let me send you off."

Garen sent Prynne off outside the palace and then arranged for a Black Fire Guard to escort him out. Garen then returned.

Within the period of time when he had become a Head of Palace, the Trejons family businesses also grew alongside his position and quickly expanded.

A few days ago, Garen had raided a heavily corrupted treasurer, but in the meantime also took a small part of the spoils, just enough to return all the money to Kid. To his tactics, Avic was turning a blind eye too.

Just by ridding the palace of so many spies, Garen still couldn’t figure out how Obscuro actually planned to make a move.

Back to the grand hall of Black Fire Palace.

He sat on the pitch black throne inscribed with dark red patterns, his fingers crossed. His mind spiralled into a rabbit hole of thought.

On both sides of the grand hall were two rows of Black Fire Heavy Guards.

There were some differences among the Black Fire Guards too, the ordinary ones in heavy armor were form 2 elites, but the ones in heavy armor and a cape, they were all form 3. The entire Black Fire Guards summed up to two hundred people. In reality, their capabilities far exceeded regular totem users in the same realm, and most importantly, they did not fear death.

The kingdom was full of form 2 totem users, but the ones who were truly fearless of death numbered few. Behind each totem user was a massive chain of resources and supplies, with many beneficiaries of various scales. During a life-threatening event, there were definitely few people who would fight to their death without abandon.

The Black Fire Guards were different. They were the kamikaze elites of the Form 2 totem users. Under Garen’s orders, they could unleash explosive amounts of power at anytime.

Despite all that, the Black Fire Guards were of little use to Avic, as the Form 2s in the Kingdom’s totem user regiment stands the majority.

The real reason people fear the Black Fire Guards was the fact that the all had the power to self-destruct. And also because of the Green Vine Sphere, their numbers can always be maintained. If they lost one, they can immediately be replenished with another.

It was too bad the Green Vine Sphere could only control so many Black Fire Guards; with the creation of so many kamikaze units, anyone who was below form 4, even spiritualized would not have dared fight them head-on.

"Unfortunately… these people aren’t sentient.." Garen shook his head as he sighed. " looks like I have to recruit someone to help me manage the human resources within the palace.

As he calmed down, he began preparing the items for his next expedition, he would go out on a monster hunt every two days to increase his potential points, and also to see when would he reach the Secret Techniques’ upgrade threshold.

Perhaps the Nine-Headed Dragon needed too much, for such a long period of gathering potential points, roughly 200 points in total, the Secret Technique had yet to produce any reaction. However, this made him anticipate it even more. As the requirement of potential points increased, so did the degree of change after one finally crossed the critical point needed to reach the next level.

************************************

In a tall restaurant in the Kingdom

By the side of the round beige table in the restaurant, two men with thick black beards were sitting by the table, looking towards a large black palace from afar.

Although it was noon, the sky was covered in clouds. The weather seemed gloomy, and the thick layers of clouds felt like they would collapse to the ground soon, which gave off a depressing atmosphere.

The two bearded men sat towards a corner, ordered a decent, yet normal meal, which did not stand out at all. People came and went around them, hardly noticing their existence.

Nobody realized that the two of them had minute movements on their lips; they were actually communicating using a secret technique.

"Still have no way to contact Eleven?"

"It is extremely difficult." the other man who was slightly shorter looked gloomy. " The most troublesome people in the palace are the White Silver Palace and Black Fire Palace. Eleven’s Palace is situated slightly ahead of the Black Fire Palace, so it is very difficult to rescue her! The Nine-Headed Serpent’s abilities are extremely powerful. If he catches wind of anything out of the ordinary, not only would we fail the extraction, whoever goes in would also have no chance of walking out alive."

"That’s why we must avoid the Nine-Headed Serpent. To avoid him, we must avoid the Black Fire Guards first, but the Black Fire Guards are everywhere, scattered across every corner of the Palace…" The tall bearded man fell into deep thought. "Then we have to ascertain, what kind of people can get into the palace without being checked!"

The other person blinked his eyes.

"Stone, you have an idea?!"

"Let’s go find out exactly what’s going on, we may have a way around this. We shall first investigate Garen’s routines, habits, and behaviors. To win someone, we should try to understand our opponent as much as possible, for that is the most important step."

******************************

Roar!!

A red dragon head dodged.

Within the deep mountain, surrounded by more than ten Black Fire Guards, Garen stepped on a boulder, underneath him were piles of debris.

At a plain nearby, a bovine-shaped monster with the head of a crocodile was slowly lying down on the floor, its body size spanning more than six meters, it had a jet-black body, its thick neck tightly bitten in place by something, protruding to the side.

As its head stretched upwards, and the blood vessels around its burst open. A stream of bright-red blood gushed out from the open wound, but once the blood touched the air, it disappeared as if something swallowed it up.

From the air were faint noises of some large creature’s gulping from a swallowing movement at the throat.

The left side of Garen’s mark on the forehead was flashing with a hint of bright red. As the swallowing sound diminished, so did the red light.

Bam!!

The giant creature hit the ground, and its body shrunk significantly.

Garen took the white handkerchief from a Black Fire Guard and rubbed his hands.

Suddenly, a strong quake was felt from the ground.

"Who! Dares! To Kill my Bovine Croc!!" A large roar was heard from afar.

Garen laughed, this was already the Meteorite Mountains, which was very far away from the Kingdom, which he rode on the fastest Thunderhawk for a little less than half a day to reach. This was beyond the defensive line, where different forces were constantly clashing, with people from different scales of power. However, the monsters itself were not very strong, perfect for training.

This was the northern side of the West Farm Defensive line, which, when compared to the south, had much stronger monsters. There were even pinnacle form 4 monsters here, and there were more than one of them, so even the Royal Alliance didn’t venture too deep into the mountains, and could only shrink their defensive lines.

Deeper into the mountains were monsters even stronger, Form 4 monsters, even Spiritualized ones were found spawning in hordes within a lair. This meant that the elites were the only ones capable of entering.

A single Bovine Croc could earn Garen five Potential Points, which was a fairly decent return compared previous standards.

One Form 1 totem or monster would provide about a quarter point’s worth of potential points, not even a full point.

One Form 2 gave about two points; and five points for form 3. Whereas spiritualized creatures gave a whopping 15 points.

The Bovine Croc itself possessed a combat prowess of about an elite Form 2, with its rough and thick hide, and its high strength, with special resistance towards non-physical attacks. But it actually provided points equivalent to a form 3, so Garen made it a point never to let any of these Bovine Crocs go.

There were actually many creatures with such rough, thick hides, but none of them were as worthy as the Bovine Croc.

As he heard the loud roar, Garen put down his handkerchief and stared at the sky from afar.

Soon, A giant black silhouette appeared from within the gloomy sky.

A giant octopus-like monster appeared, with tens of tentacles each spanning over a metre in diameter wriggling around, just like a bunch of long whips. The giant octopus head was at least 7-8 metres in diameter, and a scrawny old man was sitting on top of it.

The old man had on grey attire, with a gleam in his eyes. The shadow casted by the giant octopus under him have covered Garen and his team.

As the distance closed the distance, the skull-shaped suckers on the octopus’ tentacles became clearly visible.

Once it breached a 50-meter radius, the black octopus suddenly shrunk, with all its tentacles being retracting in an instant, and its body turned from black to bright red.

The old man sitting on its head suddenly had a change of expression. His gaze towards Garen’s team has also turned more cautious.

"So it seems an expert of the same level had arrived, I am the Seven Nights Tower’s Third Tower Head Endjack, how may I address you, kind sir?"

His intonation changed instantly and became much friendlier.

"Seven Nights Tower?" Garen’s eyebrow was raised. That was the biggest force within the Meteorite Mountain, It is said that it was formed from a large academy and a few guilds that were indigenous to this region. They were strong, and were famous for their seven-tower combination defensive tactical arrays.

The north of the defensive lines edged nearer to the polar circle, hence the temperature dipped constantly. It was still fine at this point, but if they advanced further up north, across the Meteorite Mountains, the areas there would no longer be habitable. The lowest temperature reached negative ten below in Celcius, the landscape covered in blizzards for a majority of the year, where the snow caps reigned. Although it was not as crowded as the as tropics, there were still hidden forces hiding away in these remote ranges.

Totem users have always had tricks to alter the natural environments around them; nobody knew how many experts there were hiding in the polar circles.

"I have long heard about Seven Nights Tower reigning over the north as the largest force in the Meteorite Mountains, I’d have never expected to meet an expert, the Tower Head from the esteemed organization only after coming here ten or so times. It is indeed my honor." Garen smiled slightly, " I am the Personal Guard of the Kovitan King, Palace Head of the Black Fire Palace, Garen."

"Kovitan? As in the empire, Kovitan?" The old man paid heed and asked in suspicion.

"Indeed."

That old man’s eyes brightened up. The reason he rushed over was to catch the murderer of all the Bovine Crocs that he’d let out, but they always winded up dead without him being able to catch the perpetrator. Now that he found the murderer, he’d never expect him to be a high ranking official from the Kovitan Empire within the mainland. The way the opponent looked, he was obviously not a weakling. The octopus that he rode on turned red, indicating that the opponent had the abilities to kill the octopus at any time. It was then obvious to him that Garen was at least at the same level as he was.

Looking back at his person, at the many guards surrounding him, although neither one of them were emitting any strong aura, they had a dangerous air of death about them.

If that issue could be resolved with this person’s help….

The old man had a plan.

The reason that he let out these Bovine Crocs was not to nurture these beasts nurtured for so years and to be running around for just anyone, but instead, they carried an important task.

That was, to steal the illusionary tactics of that brat that had stolen the treasures of the Grand Snowy Mountain. He had incomparable talents towards tactical arrays, and this old man didn’t have the necessary manpower to catch the culprit. The treasures from the Grand SNowy Mountain may not have any function to other people, but it may just prove useful for this man in front of him as an exchange.

Garen on the other hand, had his own set of plans; now that the Black Fire Palace was severely short-handed, if he could build a relationship with a strong organization such as the Seven Nights Tower, he can greatly increase his own power and influence. No matter what, having a expandable amount of strong troops will always make things more convenient.

The Trejons Family already had a sour reputation far and wide, but on the outer fields, it was unknown.

If he could secure a channel of communication and a friendship, it will be of great benefit to the Trejons Family

Ever since the two wars and periods of chaos, even though he managed to reduce the impact to Avic’s side, but Ender, Daniela’s side, even as far as East Continent, remained much the same. Hence, he must continuously improve his capabilities and influence, only then can he stop being hunted by Obscuro and Terraflor in the following years.